ANNOUNCER: Previously, on the "Kids Baking Championship"...
播音员:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
DUFF: Your job is to impress us with one chocolate-intensive dessert.
达夫:你的工作就是用一份巧克力密集的甜点给我们留下深刻印象。
Lots of chocolate!
很多巧克力!
You must incorporate one of these spices
你必须加入这些香料中的一种
into your chocolate dessert.
放进你的巧克力甜点里。
DUFF: This is an incredibly sophisticated dessert
达夫:这是一道非常复杂的甜点
for an adult, and you're 10 years old.
对成年人来说，你才10岁。
One of you was really on fire.
你们中有一个人真的火了。
Peggy! [ Applause ]
佩吉![掌声]
So far, I haven't tasted any heat.
到目前为止，我还没尝到任何辣味。
It's a mystery.
这是个谜。
The baker who will be leaving us is...
将要离开我们的面包师是……
Colby.
科尔比。
Bye, Colby. Bye.
再见,科尔比。再见。
Yeah!
是啊!
Welcome back, bakers! And now there are seven.
欢迎回来，面包师们!现在有七个了。
[ Kids cheer ]
[孩子们欢呼]
Who wants to win the title of Kids Baking Champion
谁想赢得儿童烘焙冠军
and that sweet $25,000?
那两万五千美元呢?
That sweet, sweet moola. Sweet moola!
那甜美，甜美的月牙。甜蜜的金钱!
Don't you get that every day, though?
你不是每天都有这种感觉吗?
No. Can you talk to my agent?
不。你能和我的经纪人谈谈吗?
[ Laughing ] Okay.
(笑)好的。
Today, bakers, you have 2 hours to create
今天，面包师们，你们有两个小时的时间来制作
your own beautiful display...
你自己美丽的展示…
...of French macaroons.
…法式马卡龙
Yes! Yes! Macaroons!
是的!是的!蛋白杏仁饼!
Yes, yes, yes!
是的，是的，是的!
I make them, like, every weekend.
我每个周末都做。
Three dozen macaroons.
三打马卡龙。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝。
EMMA: Not cool.
不酷。
36 macaroons is a lot to take on for 2 hours.
两个小时吃36个马卡龙太多了。
DUFF: It's an art to make the perfect French macaroon.
达夫:做出完美的法式马卡龙是一门艺术。
It's got to be crunchy and smooth on the outside
外皮要酥脆光滑
and tender and moist on the inside.
里面又嫩又湿。
They all need to be the same size,
它们都需要相同的尺寸，
and they should have what we call feet,
它们应该有我们所说的脚，
which is a little crispy edge right around the bottom.
就是底部的边缘有点脆。
JANE: Macaroons are kind of mean, because they're like,
简:马卡龙有点刻薄，因为它们就像，
"Eeh, if you do one thing wrong, I won't turn out like this.
“呃，如果你做错了一件事，我就不会变成这样了。
I'll be like a blob, and then you'll go home.
我会变成一团，然后你就可以回家了。
Mwah-ha-ha!"
Mwah-ha-ha !”
And your baking time starts...
你的烘焙时间开始了…
Now!
现在!
Where's the cream of tartar? It's not here.
鞑靼奶油在哪里?不在这里。
Did you take it? Move!
你拿了吗?动!
PEGGY: I start on my macaroon batter
佩吉:我开始做马卡龙面糊
because it has to dry for a while.
因为它得干一段时间。
I am making a classic almond macaroon
我在做一个经典的杏仁杏仁饼
with a salted-caramel filling.
里面有咸焦糖。
I went to a fancy macaroon store,
我去了一家高档的马卡龙店，
and they had a salted-caramel macaroon,
他们有一个咸焦糖杏仁饼，
and it was really, really good, so I'm gonna recreate it.
真的很好吃，所以我要重新做一遍。
I'm combined almond meal, powdered sugar
我是杏仁粉和糖粉的混合物
in a food processor,
在食品加工机中，
and then I start whipping my egg whites.
然后开始搅拌蛋清。
I feel like it's gonna take so much time
我觉得这要花很多时间
to separate my eggs,
为了把鸡蛋分开，
so I just used liquid whites.
所以我只用了液体白色。
Every second counts!
分秒必争!
JANE: Today, I'm going to make
简:今天，我要做
a raspberry white-chocolate surprise macaroon
树莓白巧克力马卡龙
because I love chocolate and raspberries.
因为我喜欢巧克力和覆盆子。
I whip together my egg whites
我把蛋清搅匀
and cream of tartar until it's foamy,
再加入塔塔奶油，直到起泡，
and then I gradually add some sugar.
然后我逐渐加一些糖。
Sugar makes it, like, shine,
糖让它闪闪发光，
and shiny is always a good thing.
闪亮总是一件好事。
I don't love to make French macaroons,
我不喜欢做法式马卡龙，
but, like, I'm good at making them.
但我很擅长做
Just so modest right now.
我现在太谦虚了。
Jane, a watched meringue does not froth.
简，煮过的蛋白霜是不会起泡的。
[ Valerie laughs ]
[瓦莱丽笑]
Making macaroons, they're really precise,
做马卡龙，他们非常精确，
which I like, because I'm a precise baker.
我喜欢，因为我是一个精准的面包师。
I love making French macaroons, and I make them a lot,
我喜欢做法式马卡龙，我经常做，
and they always turn out perfectly.
结果总是很完美。
We have, like, chocolate growing in my grandfather's yard,
我爷爷的院子里种了巧克力，
who lives in Jamaica.
他住在牙买加。
And my other side of the family, who's Ethiopian,
我另一边的亲戚是埃塞俄比亚人，
they drink a lot of coffee,
他们喝很多咖啡，
so I decided to do something that both of my roots were from.
所以我决定做一些我的根都来自的事情。
I am making tiramisu-inspired French macaroons
我要做提拉米苏风格的法式马卡龙
with a chocolate espresso cookie and two fillings --
用巧克力浓缩饼干和两种馅料
a chocolate-hazelnut, mascarpone, nutmeg filling,
巧克力榛子，马斯卡彭奶酪，肉豆蔻馅，
and the other one will be a chocolate-espresso ganache.
另一份是巧克力意式甘纳许。
Hey, Emma, can I come, like, scoop some almond meal?
艾玛，我能过来舀点杏仁粉吗?
Yep. Sure.
是的。确定。
Let's see. I've got a little bit too much.
让我们来看看。我喝得有点多了。
Today, I am going to make a red-velvet macaroon
今天，我要做一个红丝绒马卡龙
with strawberry-cheesecake filling.
草莓芝士蛋糕馅。
Does anybody have the cocoa powder?
有人有可可粉吗?
I do. What flavor are you doing?
我做的事。你在做什么口味的?
Red-velvet. Oh, that sounds good.
玫红色。哦，听起来不错。
I think it'll be really flavorful,
我觉得味道会很好，
but at the same time, I can do it quick,
但同时，我可以做得很快，
and I don't have to stress about it.
我不必为此感到压力。
After the dry ingredients are blended,
干的配料混合后，
I'm going to put them in a sifter
我要把它们放在筛子里
so it's as fine as possible.
所以这是尽可能好的。
90 minutes left, bakers.
还有90分钟，面包师们。
VALERIE: 90 minutes to mesmerize us with macaroons.
瓦莱丽:90分钟用马卡龙迷惑我们。
Taking forever.
永远。
MATTHEW: Sifting.
马修:筛选。
Okay, you know what?
好吧，你知道吗?
Let's go all out with our hands. Yep.
让我们全力以赴吧。是的。
That'll be good. [ Chuckles ]
那太好了。[笑]
Macaroons are my specialty.
马卡龙是我的拿手好菜。
This challenge has Matthew written
马修写了这个挑战
in graffiti on the walls.
墙上的涂鸦。
Dance to the beat of the mixer.
跟着混音器的节拍跳舞。
Oh, wow! That's a special dance.
哦,哇!那是一种特殊的舞蹈。
I decided to make s'mores macaroons.
我决定做s'mores杏仁饼干。
Last week, I didn't do the best with my s'mores brownie.
上周，我的巧克力夹心蛋糕做得不太好。
They just look like they kind of got run over by a car.
他们看起来就像被车碾过一样。
But this week, I'm proving to the judges
但这周，我要向评委们证明
that I can create good s'mores flavor.
我可以做出美味的果子酱
The s'mores redemption.
s'mores的救赎。
Whoa, that's strong!
哇，真厉害!
I'm also going to make chocolate-cherry macaroons
我还要做巧克力樱桃杏仁饼
because I love cherries.
因为我喜欢樱桃。
I'm going to use liquid flavoring
我要用液体调味料
in my macaroon shells.
在我的杏仁饼壳里。
Sometimes it affects the texture,
有时它会影响口感，
but I'm willing to take that risk
但我愿意冒这个险
because these macaroons needs to be perfect.
因为这些杏仁饼必须完美。
Let's check.
让我们检查。
To ensure that my macaroon meringue is stiff enough,
为了确保我的蛋白酥饼足够坚硬，
I hold it over my head.
我把它举过头顶。
Is it gonna fall? No, it's not!
它会掉下来吗?不，不是的!
Oh, is that a test?
哦，这是测试吗?
Yeah, I hope that falls out.
是啊，我希望这能成功。
Matthew, shake it around a little bit.
马修，稍微摇一下。
No! No! No! No, don't!
不!不!不!不,不!
Oh, yeah!
哦,耶!
Luckily, it's never fallen on me,
幸运的是，它从来没有落在我身上
but one day I'm gonna look like the abominable snowman.
但总有一天我会看起来像个可恶的雪人
Then I fold in my dry ingredients.
然后加入干的配料。
I can't under mix,
我不能混在一起，
or else my macaroons are gonna be cracked,
否则我的杏仁饼就会碎，
but if I over mix,
但如果我过度搅拌，
my macaroons are gonna be flat.
我的马卡龙要变平了。
Food Network stars wish they were this good.
美食网的明星们希望自己也能这么好。
I'm making two different macaroons
我要做两种不同的马卡龙
because it's already hard enough making one flavor in two hours,
因为在两小时内做出一种口味已经够难的了，
so I hope I get extra credit for making two flavors.
所以我希望我做两种口味能得到额外的学分。
Once my batter has come together,
面糊搅拌均匀后，
I separate it into two bowls.
我把它分成两个碗。
One bowl is going to be for the creamsicle macaroons,
一碗是用来做奶油杏仁饼的，
which is gonna get orange zest and orange food coloring.
里面会有橙色的皮和橙色的食用色素。
The other bowl is for red-velvet,
另一个碗是放红丝绒的，
which is gonna get cocoa powder and red food dye.
里面会有可可粉和红色食用染料。
Hi, Alex. Hello.
嗨,亚历克斯。你好。
What ya making?
你在做什么?
I'm thinking of spring time.
我在想春天。
Everybody loves an ice cream or something,
每个人都喜欢冰淇淋之类的东西，
and the first thing
第一件事
that popped to my mind was creamsicle.
我突然想到的是冰淇淋。
Mmm! [ Gasps ] That's fun!
嗯![喘气]真有趣!
I love creamsicle. I like that idea.
我喜欢冰淇淋。我喜欢这个主意。
The other is going to be red-velvet.
另一个是红丝绒。
Well, we'll let you get to it.
好吧，我们不打扰你了。
Okay.
好吧。
Today, I'm making chocolate macaroons
今天，我要做巧克力马卡龙
with a cream-cheese rim and raspberry coulis.
配上奶油芝士边缘和覆盆子酱。
My inspiration behind this is I love raspberry coulis.
我的灵感来自于我喜欢覆盆子酱。
It's so tart, and it's got, like, this pop.
太酸了，还有点爆的味道。
Coulis is basically reduced berries.
甜酱基本上是浆果的浓缩物。
And while the raspberries
而树莓
and sugar are cooking down,
糖煮熟了，
I'm starting to pipe my macaroons.
我开始用烟斗吹我的杏仁饼干了。
My first couple macaroons look bad.
我的头几个马卡龙看起来很糟糕。
They're a little out of form, and they're a little too big.
它们有点走样，而且有点太大了。
I am going to keep going
我要继续下去
and hope that it fixes in the oven.
希望它能在烤箱里凝固。
I'm a little worried that Emma hasn't fully mixed
我有点担心艾玛还没完全融入
her macaroon batter.
她的杏仁饼面糊。
I can still see chunks of cocoa powder,
我还能看到大块的可可粉，
chunks of powdered sugar.
大块糖粉。
That should be all one color.
应该是一种颜色。
Ooh, stay down.
哦，趴下。
I'm piping, and my macaroons have, like, little peaks.
我在吹口哨，我的杏仁饼有小尖峰。
You don't want those on macaroons,
你不想在杏仁饼干上放这些东西，
so I try to get them down with my hand,
所以我试着用手把它们放下，
but that's like ruining the texture of the macaroon.
但这就像破坏了马卡龙的口感。
Hopefully, when they bake they go down,
希望它们在烘烤的时候会下沉，
because if they don't,
因为如果他们不这样做
they won't be the perfect macaroon!
它们不会是完美的马卡龙!
How is everyone doing?
大家都好吗?
Good.
好。
Watch Yahshimabet pipe.
看Yahshimabet的烟斗。
She's got a really nice touch.
她的触觉很好。
Right? So you pipe, and then flick.
对吧?所以你管，然后弹。
Pipe, and then flick.
管，然后弹。
I have a feeling she's made a macaroon or two.
我感觉她做了一两个马卡龙。
Or 1,000. [ Laughs ]
或1000年。[笑]
Little lick of the wrist. That's my thing.
舔一下手腕。这是我的风格。
One hour left, bakers!
还有一个小时，面包师们!
To get all the air bubbles out, you get your pan,
为了把所有的气泡都弄出来，你要用平底锅，
and you whack it.
然后击打它。
MATTHEW: Dry for 30 minutes.
马修:晾干30分钟。
You don't need that long in the oven.
你不需要在烤箱里烤那么久。
It's before they go in the oven. They have to dry out.
在它们被放进烤箱之前。它们必须变干。
The reason why need to be dry is because the liquid
之所以需要干燥是因为液体
and the air that you've whipped into it,
你搅入的空气，
that's what makes them go [imitates pop] and pop up.
这就是他们(模仿流行音乐)不断涌现的原因。
Trying to feel the air.
试着感受空气。
One way to make sure
一种确保的方法
that your macaroons are dry enough
你的马卡龙够干了
is you put them an under an air duct.
就是把它们放在通风管道下面。
So I'm just trying to find one.
所以我只是想找一个。
I'm not doing a crazy dance.
我不会跳疯舞的。
I think that's good.
我认为这很好。
My egg whites aren't really getting whipped and stiff.
我的蛋清并没有打得很硬。
My egg whites aren't whipping.
我的蛋清没有打匀。
I see other people have already piped out their macaroons,
我看到其他人已经吐出了他们的杏仁饼，
and I'm still on my batter, which is scary.
我还在打面糊，这太可怕了。
One hour left, bakers!
还有一个小时，面包师们!
One hour to mesmerize us with macaroons!
一小时用马卡龙迷惑我们!
My egg whites aren't really getting whipped and stiff.
我的蛋清并没有打得很硬。
My egg whites, they're just getting foamy on the top,
我的蛋清，上面开始起泡了，
and they're not whipping at all.
而且他们一点都不抽。
Peggy really looks frazzled. I'm worried about her.
佩吉看起来真的很疲惫。我很担心她。
Peggy used liquid egg whites
佩吉用的是液体蛋清
instead of separating eggs,
而不是分开鸡蛋，
and they're not whipping up.
他们并没有被鞭打。
I've found, in my career,
我发现，在我的职业生涯中
liquid egg whites work about 80% of the time.
液态蛋清在80%的情况下都有效。
Sometimes, they just don't whip up.
有时候，他们就是不发火。
It's a real thing.
这是真的。
All right, I got to go talk to her. All right.
好吧，我得去跟她谈谈。好吧。
Oh, hi, Duff. Those aren't whipping up.
哦，嗨，达夫。这些都没有发酵。
I know.
我知道。
If they don't whip up, you should redo that.
如果他们不动手，你应该重做。
Okay, I'm not. I'm not. I'm just gonna restart. It's fine.
好吧，我不是。我不是。我要重新开始。它很好。
Instead of using the liquid whites,
不用液体蛋白，
'cause I think that's what's causing the problem,
因为我认为这就是问题的根源
I switch to regular egg whites.
我改吃普通的蛋清。
I'm regretting using the liquid egg whites a lot.
我很后悔经常用液体蛋清。
It takes way less time than I thought it would.
花的时间比我想象的要少得多。
So, I get those in the mixer and I start whipping them,
所以，我把它们放进搅拌器，开始搅拌，
and ka-bam, they're the way I wanted them to be.
然后，他们就变成了我想要的样子。
It looks good.
看起来不错。
I feel like I just wasted like five minutes,
我觉得我浪费了五分钟，
and that counts so much while you're making macaroons.
这在你做马卡龙的时候很重要。
Really?
真的吗?
[ Whispers ] Wow!
[低语]哇!
Gosh!
天啊!
YAHSHIMABET: Yes!
YAHSHIMABET:是的!
I take my finger, I touch it, and it doesn't stick,
我用我的手指，我摸它，它不粘，
so I then put them into the oven.
然后我把它们放进烤箱。
Now, I'm going to start on my fillings.
现在，我要开始做馅料了。
First, I'm making my chocolate-hazelnut mascarpone.
首先，我要做巧克力榛子马斯卡彭奶酪。
I beat my mascarpone,
我打了马斯卡彭奶酪，
and I add my powdered sugar and the heavy whipping cream.
然后加入糖粉和鲜奶油。
Then I add spoonfuls of chocolate-hazelnut spread,
然后加几勺巧克力榛子酱，
and I get nutmeg because I think the flavors
还有肉豆蔻，因为我觉得肉豆蔻的味道
will go good with the chocolate.
配上巧克力会很好吃。
Ooh! Yum! This looks good.
噢!Yum !这个看起来不错。
Hey! Your macaroons are in the oven already, huh?
嘿!你的马卡龙已经在烤箱里了吧?
Yes, they are.
是的，他们是。
So, you've already done your fillings?
这么说，你已经填好牙了?
I've done one filling. I'm going to start on my other one.
我做了一次补牙。我要从另一个开始。
Wow.
哇。
So you're really managing your clock well today?
你今天真的把时间安排得很好吗?
Yes. Okay, I'm proud of you.
是的。好吧，我为你骄傲。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
There's a reason I made two fillings.
我做两份馅料是有原因的。
It's more impressive.
它更令人印象深刻。
Okay, that's good.
好的，很好。
45 minutes left, bakers!
还有45分钟，面包师们!
The French call them macaroons (maca-runs),
法国人称其为马卡龙(macaroon)，
I call them macaroons (maca-runes).
我称它们为马卡龙(马卡文)。
MATTHEW: I'm going to put these in the oven.
马修:我要把这些放进烤箱里。
ALEX: Finally.
亚历克斯:最后。
Those look really good. Thanks.
看起来真不错。谢谢。
They're still pretty sticky.
它们还是很粘的。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
All right, Rebecca, real quick -- How's it going in here?
好了，丽贝卡，快说，这里怎么样了?
Eh, it's going. [ Chuckles ]
嗯，开始了。[笑]
So, what flavor are you doing?
你要做什么口味的?
Those are red-velvet. Cool.
那些是红丝绒的。酷。
I'm going to be doing
我将要做的事情
a cream-cheese, like, marshmallow fluff,
奶油奶酪，棉花糖之类的，
and then I'm going to flavor it
然后给它调味
with a little bit of strawberry in there
再加一点草莓
to give it kind of a different flavor.
让它有一种不同的味道。
All right. All right, get to work.
好吧。好了，开始工作吧。
Thank you!
谢谢你！
For my filling, I am adding cream cheese and butter,
馅料，我要加入奶油奶酪和黄油，
and I'm going to cream that together,
我要把它们混合在一起，
and once that's creamy, I'll add marshmallow cream.
奶油化后，加入棉花糖奶油。
The marshmallow cream is for fluff,
棉花糖奶油是用来做绒毛的，
and so it just kind of gives it, like, an extra fluffiness.
所以它给了它一种额外的蓬松感。
Once that's creamy, I'll add powdered sugar.
一旦变成奶油状，我就加入糖粉。
Once that's mixed together, I'll add vanilla
混合好后，加入香草
and strawberry puree.
还有草莓泥。
Yes, they're finally getting their feet,
是的，他们终于站稳脚跟了，
which is the crispy edge around the side.
就是边沿的脆皮。
So glad. Yeah.
很高兴。是的。
MATTHEW: Rebecca, can I have the marshmallow cream?
马修:丽贝卡，我可以要棉花糖奶油吗?
Um, I don't know if I'm done using it.
我不知道我是不是用完了。
'Cause I'm using it, like...
因为我在用它，就像…
Matthew really wants the marshmallow cream,
马修很想要棉花糖奶油，
and he's making s'more macaroons,
他在做更多的杏仁饼
which that's kind of a necessity,
这是必须的，
but I mean, I got it first.
但我是说，我先拿到的。
Are you gonna use all of it? Because I need to use it.
你要全部用完吗?因为我需要用到它。
What's a s'more without marshmallows?
没有棉花糖的s'more算什么?
Rebecca, please don't use all of that, Rebecca.
丽贝卡，请不要用这些，丽贝卡。
I just have to start on my chocolate cream,
我得开始做巧克力奶油了，
and hope that Rebecca doesn't use all of that marshmallow.
希望丽贝卡不会把棉花糖都吃光。
Just beating my butter,
只是在搅拌黄油，
powdered sugar, and cocoa powder.
糖粉和可可粉。
That's chocolaty.
像巧克力的。
Hey, I'm gonna take some out of this,
嘿，我要从这里面拿点，
and I'll give the rest to you, okay?
剩下的我给你，好吗?
Okay, thank you. You're welcome.
好的，谢谢。不客气
That's not enough to make marshmallow butter cream.
这还不足以做棉花糖白脱奶油。
I have to come up with something fast,
我必须尽快想出办法
or else it's not going to taste like marshmallow butter cream.
否则尝起来就不像棉花糖白脱奶油了。
It's just going to be vanilla butter cream.
这就是香草白脱奶油。
I am literally making up this recipe right now.
我现在正在做这个食谱。
I'm going to add cream cheese.
我要加入奶油奶酪。
I come up with using cream cheese,
我想到用奶油奶酪，
because I like the acidity of cream cheese,
因为我喜欢奶油奶酪的酸味，
and I think cream cheese and chocolate,
我觉得奶油奶酪和巧克力
like, just explode into one awesome deliciousness.
就像炸成一道美味佳肴。
That seems pretty good.
看起来很不错。
30 minutes, bakers!
30分钟，面包师们!
VALERIE: 30 minutes to show us your best macaroon!
瓦莱丽:30分钟给我们展示你最好的马卡龙!
JANE: I check my shells, and they're finally ready
简:我检查了我的贝壳，它们终于准备好了
to go in the oven.
把它放进烤箱。
Whew!
唷!
This scares me so much.
这让我很害怕。
Step one is complete.
第一步完成了。
Even though it had like 18 steps in it,
虽然里面有18个台阶，
but it was still step one.
但这只是第一步。
While my macaroons are baking,
当我在烤杏仁饼的时候，
I get started on my white-chocolate butter cream.
我开始做白巧克力白脱奶油。
First, I melt down some white chocolate,
首先，我融化一些白巧克力，
and then I take my butter and my powdered sugar...
然后我把黄油和糖粉…
Oh, my!
哦,我的天!
That went great.
很顺利。
...and I whip that together until it's light and fluffy.
…搅拌到又轻又蓬松。
And then I add in my cream...
然后加入奶油……
A little bit more cream.
再加一点奶油。
...and then a few tablespoons of the white chocolate.
…然后加入几汤匙白巧克力。
Perfect.
完美的。
I would, like, eat this stuff by the spoonful.
我想要一勺一勺地吃这东西。
Yummy!
好吃!
They're not dried yet.
还没干呢。
My macaroon shells are not completely dry,
我的马卡龙壳还没有完全干，
but I don't have much time,
但我时间不多了
so I have to put them in the oven no matter what.
所以无论如何我都要把它们放进烤箱。
And my caramel is really soupy and runny and thin.
我的焦糖很浓，很稀，很薄。
I don't think it's going to set up in time.
我不认为它会及时建立起来。
I want to have a back-up plan,
我想有个备用计划，
so I decide to make a chocolate ganache
所以我决定做巧克力甘纳许
because I know you can fill macaroons
因为我知道你能填满杏仁饼
with ganache, and it tastes really good.
加了甘纳许，味道很好。
To make my ganache, I put heavy cream in a sauce pan,
为了制作巧克力酱，我在酱锅里放了浓奶油，
and then I let that come to a simmer.
然后小火慢炖。
I pour it onto my chocolate,
把它倒在巧克力上，
and then I whisk it until it's smooth.
然后搅拌均匀。
I'm making American butter cream.
我在做美式白脱奶油。
It's just heavy whipping cream, vanilla, and butter and sugar.
里面只有鲜奶油，香草，黄油和糖。
So, it'll be sweet and thick like an ice cream.
所以，它会像冰淇淋一样又甜又浓。
Isn't that a lot of sugar
那不是很多糖吗
that he's putting into his American butter cream?
加在他的美式白脱奶油里的东西
I would not use that much if I was making
如果是我的话，我不会用那么多
American butter cream. Yeah.
美国白脱奶油。是的。
[ Muttering ] That's gonna be a really sweet cream.
(喃喃自语)那将是一种非常甜的奶油。
Hiya, Emma! EMMA: Hi!
你好,艾玛!艾玛:你好!
How you doing? Good.
你好吗?好。
That's all the good stuff that you're doing right there.
这就是你所做的一切好事。
That's the stuff that's full of pectin.
这是一种充满果胶的东西。
That's gonna get nice and gelled.
它会变得很好，很粘。
This is the stuff that's delicious.
这才是美味的东西。
I hope so, because if that doesn't gel,
我希望如此，因为如果这行不通，
we're gonna have to eat these macaroons with a spoon.
我们得用勺子吃这些杏仁饼了。
Uh-oh. Is Duff getting on your nerves, yet?
哦。达夫惹到你了吗?
Hasn't he always?
他不是一直都这样吗?
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Emma, I'm here to amuse you.
艾玛，我是来逗你开心的
Is it working?
它有效吗?
On the day where it's a challenge that I don't excel at,
当我遇到不擅长的挑战时，
it's just making it kind of worse.
这只会让事情变得更糟。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Ah, they smell so good!
啊，它们闻起来真香!
Those look awesome.
看起来真棒。
[ Gasps, sighs ]
[喘息，叹气]
Oh, no!
哦,不!
My macaroons look horrible when I pull them out of the oven.
我的马卡龙从烤箱里拿出来的时候看起来很糟糕。
They're puffy and cracked and disgusting.
它们又肿又裂又恶心。
Uh-oh.
哦。
Hi, Alex.
嗨,亚历克斯。
Yours turned out like mine did!
你的结果和我的一样!
Yeah, they kind of connected.
是的，他们有点联系。
Look at mine. They're even worse.
看看我的。他们甚至更糟。
Mine are, like, puffy.
我的眼睛有点肿。
They don't look like macaroons.
它们看起来不像杏仁饼干。
15 minutes, bakers. 15 minutes.
15分钟，面包师们。15分钟。
VALERIE: You guys are baking to stay in this competition.
瓦莱丽:你们要在这场比赛中脱颖而出。
Disaster.
灾难。
These look like drop cookies
这些看起来像饼干
or snicker doodles, or something.
或者窃笑涂鸦之类的。
Oh, no!
哦,不!
This is probably one of the worst things I've ever baked.
这可能是我烤过的最难吃的东西了。
No! No, No, No, No, No, No, No!
不!不，不，不，不，不!
There's nothing I can do to fix it at this point.
现在我已经无能为力了。
So, I'm going to start assembling my macaroons.
所以，我要开始组装我的马卡龙了。
They're crumbling and falling and breaking.
它们摇摇欲坠，破碎不堪。
No!
不!
There goes another one.
还有一个。
This has been a pretty bumpy ride.
这是一段相当坎坷的旅程。
Total disaster.
彻头彻尾的灾难。
I've seen her pull out of a nose dive. She can do it.
我见过她从俯冲中恢复过来。她能做到。
Yes, that's true.
是的，那是真的。
And this is a nosedive.
这是一个俯冲。
[ Sighs deeply ]
[深深叹息]
What I'm doing for the filling is
我要做的是填馅
I'm piping a little cream-cheese frosting border,
我在往奶油芝士糖霜边浇边，
and I'm just gonna put a little dollop
我要放一点
of raspberry coulis in the middle.
中间是覆盆子酱。
My filling tastes pretty good.
我的馅料味道不错。
I hope that's my saving grace.
我希望这是我的可取之处。
Time?
时间吗?
10 minutes, bakers.
10分钟，面包师们。
French macaroons.
法国的杏仁饼干。
My macaroons are not coming off the sheet, which...is...bad.
我的杏仁饼没从被单上掉下来，这…很…糟糕。
If you don't feel good about yours, you should look at mine.
如果你对你的感觉不好，你应该看看我的。
They don't even have feet!
他们连脚都没有!
Well, I can't get mine off the sheet.
好吧，我不能把我的从床单上拿下来。
That's a problem.
这是个问题。
So, I put them back in the oven to dry for a little bit longer.
所以，我把它们放回烤箱，再干一会儿。
The macaroons are sticking to the paper
马卡龙粘在纸上了
because they need more time in the oven.
因为他们需要在烤箱里多烤些时间。
She's actually putting them back in to dry them out. [ Sighs ]
她实际上是把它们放回去晾干。[叹气]
Like when you put a steak on the grill,
就像你把牛排放在烤架上，
and it's stuck, right?
它卡住了，对吧?
Yeah, you're not supposed to move it
是的，你不应该移动它
until it unsticks by itself.
直到它自己解开。
Right, and then it unsticks.
对，然后它就不粘了。
ALEX: They, like, pooled towards each other.
亚历克斯:他们就像互相挤在一起。
It's taking me ages
这花了我很多时间
to get these macaroons off the parchment.
把杏仁饼从羊皮纸上弄下来。
I am worried.
我很担心。
I don't want to go home right now.
我现在不想回家。
I'm halfway to the finish.
我离终点只有一半了。
I've got a food truck to buy.
我要去买一辆餐车。
This is stressful.
这是有压力的。
Yahshimabet, she's painting her macaroons with luster dust.
雅希玛贝特，她在给杏仁饼干涂上光泽粉。
It's pretty. Yeah.
它很漂亮。是的。
YAHSHIMABET: Now that everything is done, I start assembling my macaroons.
现在一切都做好了，我开始组装我的马卡龙。
So, I have a piping bag
我有一个裱花袋
with my chocolate-hazelnut, nutmeg filling.
用巧克力榛子和肉豆蔻做馅。
I know you can taste all the flavors.
我知道你能尝出所有的味道。
They have the cutest feet I've ever seen.
他们的脚是我见过最可爱的。
Look at Yahshimabet's station.
看看Yahshimabet的车站。
Look at Matthew's
看看马修的位置。
Chocolate.
巧克力。
It's like night and day!
就像白天和黑夜一样!
Yahshimabet, she's constantly cleaning as she goes along.
Yahshimabet，她一边走一边不停地打扫。
He's like a little Tasmanian devil in there.
他就像个小袋獾。
Yes! [ Laughs ]
是的![笑]
He's got some sugar, some butter.
他有一些糖，一些黄油。
I think there's butter on the ceiling.
我想天花板上有黄油。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Whenever I'm super messy,
每当我超级乱的时候，
I always come out with a good dish,
我总能做出一道好菜，
so I think this is a good sign.
所以我认为这是一个好兆头。
I feel like Jackson Pollack.
我觉得自己像杰克逊·波拉克。
I'm an artist in messiness.
我是混乱的艺术家。
When I baked off my macaroons,
当我烤杏仁饼的时候，
the peaks didn't totally go away.
山峰并没有完全消失。
But you know what?
但你知道吗?
What fixes macaroons better than luster dust?
还有什么比光泽粉更能固定马卡龙呢?
Oh, that is so beautiful.
哦，太美了。
Marshmallow.
棉花糖。
Original s'mores are graham crackers,
最初的s'mores是全麦饼干，
marshmallow, chocolate, graham cracker.
棉花糖，巧克力，全麦饼干。
I take each macaroon,
我拿着每个马卡龙，
and the sides get coated with the graham crackers.
两边涂上全麦饼干。
It looks awesome.
看起来棒极了。
I have some pretty nice macaroons in front of me.
我面前有一些很好吃的杏仁饼。
Five minutes, bakers!
五分钟，面包师们!
The time is clicking away for the macaroons challenge.
现在是马卡龙挑战的时间了。
REBECCA: I love airbrushing, and I thought I would do that
丽贝卡:我喜欢修图，我想我会修的
to kind of add a little sparkle
为了增加一点亮点
and to kind of show what I got.
展示一下我得到了什么。
And I'm squirting out dollops of frosting
我正在喷出糖霜
and squeezing the cookies together.
把饼干挤在一起。
I wish my filling was a little bit thicker
我希望我的馅再厚一点
just because it's a little bit liquid-y.
因为它有点液态。
Hey bakers, can I have your attention, please?
嘿，面包师们，请注意听我说?
It is time to bring this challenge
现在是迎接挑战的时候了
up to the next level.
更上一层楼。
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
We would like you to turn your macaroons into stackaroons.
我们想让你把你的马卡龙变成堆栈龙。
What?!
什么? !
Part of your display must be at least five inches tall.
显示器的一部分必须至少有5英寸高。
[ Gasps ]
[喘息]
You can't use glue, you can't use frosting.
不能用胶水，也不能用糖霜。
No.
不。
If you can not stack it to five inches,
如果你不能堆叠成5英寸，
you won't be disqualified.
你不会被取消资格的。
You just won't win.
你不会赢的。
This one is just plain evil.
这是纯粹的邪恶。
And we have some rulers here,
这里有一些尺子，
just to make sure that you do not leave us short-stacked.
只是为了确保你不会让我们人手不足。
[ Sarcastic ] Oh, thank you so much.
[讽刺]哦，太谢谢你了。
Peggy.
佩吉。佩吉。
Jane.
简。
[ Whining ] My macaroons, I haven't even started filling them!
(抱怨)我的杏仁饼干，我还没开始填呢!
EMMA: I'm feeling pretty good about this twist.
我对这个转折感觉很好。
I mean, all you have to do is stack macaroons
你要做的就是把杏仁饼堆起来
on top of each other.
在彼此的上面。
Little higher.
高一些。
JANE: So, I'm just piping like crazy,
简:所以，我就像疯了一样吹口哨。
putting a raspberry, stacking.
放入覆盆子，堆叠。
I make sure to put just enough filling,
我要确保放入足够的馅料，
but not, like, a ton of filling it's exploding in your mouth,
但不会有一大堆填充物在你嘴里爆炸，
and all you can taste is the white-chocolate filling.
你能尝到的只有白巧克力馅。
But just enough so it's not like, "Where's the filling?
但要恰到好处，这样才不会说:“馅料在哪里?”
Is it ghost filling? Where is it?
是鬼馅吗?它在哪里?
Did it run away?"
它跑掉了吗?”
Ehh, it's not gonna be high enough.
呃，它不会足够高。
Macaroons. Stacking macaroons.
蛋白杏仁饼干。堆积的杏仁饼干。
Stacking maca-rah.
堆积的杏仁饼干。叠加maca-rah。
Stacking maca-ray-hey! [ Laughs ]
叠加maca-ray-hey ![笑]
It just, like, fell by itself.
它就像是自己掉下来的。
All of these are falling.
所有这些都在下降。
What makes them so difficult to stack
是什么让它们如此难以堆叠
is that they're slightly round,
它们有点圆，
and if you put round on top of round, it just falls.
如果你把圆放在圆上面，它就会掉下来。
You don't, like, stack a ball on top of a ball,
你不会把一个球叠在另一个球上，
and it stays in place.
它保持在原位。
Time?
时间吗?
Three minutes, bakers!
三分钟，面包师们!
Get going, get going, get going! Get those stacked up!
快，快，快!把那些东西堆起来!
REBECCA: If the macaroon stackaroon isn't five inches tall,
丽贝卡:如果马卡龙不是五英寸高，
there's no chance of me winning,
我不可能赢
and I want to at least have a chance.
我想至少有个机会
Rebecca, I think she's got the five inches.
丽贝卡，我觉得她有五英寸高。
She's got them stacked up.
她把它们都堆起来了。
Yes!
是的!
Aah! No!
啊!不!
And they all...fall...over.
然后他们都…倒下了。
[ Crying ]
[哭泣]
Stackaroon your macaroons.
Stackaroon你的马卡龙。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
JANE: Oh, my!
简:噢，天哪!
Why?!
为什么? !
EMMA: Oh, no!
哦，不!
YAHSHIMABET: The precise baker in me hates this --
雅希玛贝特:我内心深处的烘焙师讨厌这个
All my passionate heart.
我所有热情的心。
[ Crying ]
[哭泣]
What is going on?
发生了什么事?
Why is Rebecca crying?
丽贝卡为什么在哭?
Rebecca, you got this.
丽贝卡，你可以的。
Rebecca, we know you can do it, honey. It's okay.
丽贝卡，我们知道你能做到的，亲爱的。没关系。
Three minutes, bakers!
三分钟，面包师们!
If you can not stack it to five inches,
如果你不能堆叠成5英寸，
you won't be disqualified, but you are not eligible to win.
你不会被取消资格，但你没有资格获胜。
All right, let's fall again.
好吧，我们再摔一次。
The macaroons are falling apart.
马卡龙要散了。
I...[muttering]
(喃喃自语)我…
I definitely need a Texas-sized miracle right now.
我现在需要一个德州规模的奇迹。
[ Ding! ]
(叮!］
Hey, do you want me to help you, Rebecca?
需要我帮你吗，丽贝卡?
Here, you need, like, a sturdier base so, like,
在这里，你需要一个更坚固的底座，
they can all hold up.
他们都能撑得住。
Rebecca, look at mine.
丽贝卡，看看我的。
I need, like, a really pretty one to put on top.
我需要一个非常漂亮的放在上面。
I'm gonna make the $25,000 pyramid right here.
我要在这里画出25000美元的金字塔。
Don't fall.
不下降。不下降。
There he goes. Go, Matthew. You got it. You got it.
他走了。去,马修。你说对了。你说对了。
Stack those macaroons, Matthew.
把杏仁饼堆起来，马修。
Yes!
是的!
That's five.
这是五个。
Yay!
耶!
Alex, do you need help? ALEX: Yeah.
亚历克斯，你需要帮助吗?亚历克斯:是的。
I need to get these orange ones off.
我得把这些橙色的脱下来。
Might have been a bit too wet.
可能有点太湿了。
Thank you, Yahshimabet.
谢谢你，Yahshimabet。
We start just throwing macaroons on top of the plate.
我们开始把马卡龙放在盘子上。
This is really hard.
这真的很难。
Dude, these guys are serious.
伙计，这些人是认真的。
I know. Who would have thought a little, tiny macaroon
我知道。谁会想到小小的马卡龙呢
would make all of them so serious?
会让他们这么认真吗?
Bet your parents wish you could focus like this
你父母肯定希望你能这样专注
when you do your homework.
当你做作业的时候。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
There's a whole side that's pretty much collapsed there.
有一整面都坍塌了。
I'll turn it this way.
我把它转过来。
Turn plate, we're good.
转盘，没事了。
Better.
更好。
EMMA: My macaroon shells may not look the best,
我的杏仁饼壳可能看起来不太好，
but I think they taste the best.
但我觉得味道最好。
Time?
时间吗?
1 minute, 15 seconds.
1分15秒。
PEGGY: Only one minute left, and I'm still filling my macaroons
佩吉:只剩一分钟了，我还在填马卡龙呢
to get them on my stack.
把它们放到我的书架上。
I'm freaking out!
我吓坏了!
Aw.
哦。
Oh, look at Peggy.
哦，看看佩吉。
10...
十……
9...8...
9 8…
BOTH: 7...6...
6: 7……
5...4...
5…4…
3...2...1...
3…2…1…
Hands up! Step away!
举起手来!一步!
Oh!
哦!
Well done, bakers.
干得好，面包师们。
Great job, guys.
干得好，伙计们。
Awesome job.
很棒的工作。
ALEX: I did not like this challenge.
亚历克斯:我不喜欢这个挑战。
Measure these stackaroon macaroons.
量一下这些马卡龙。
All right.
好吧。好吧。
That 5 1/2?
5又1/2?
Wow! Yay.
哇!耶。
5 1/2.
5 1/2。
They're beautiful. Let's see here...
他们是美丽的。让我看看……
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Five inches on the dot.
5英寸准。
Way to go, girl. On the dot!
干得好，姑娘。正点!
Boom! Rebecca -- 5 3/4.
繁荣!丽贝卡——5又3/4。
Oh! Good job!
哦!好工作!
Five inches. Yay, Alex.
5英寸。耶,亚历克斯。
Way to go.
干得好。
Okay, Jane.
好吧,简。
Four inches.
4英寸。
If you can put another inch of butter cream in that one,
如果你能在里面再放一英寸的白脱奶油，
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Not quite there. That's all right. Yep, that's all right.
不完全是这样。没关系。是的，没关系。
Doesn't mean you're out of the competition.
不代表你就出局了。
Emma, 4 1/2".
艾玛，4岁半。
So close.
如此接近。如此接近。
EMMA: That makes me feel pretty bad,
这让我感觉很糟糕，
but I know it won't send me home...
但我知道它不会送我回家……
automatically.
自动。
Saw a few tears today.
今天看到了一些眼泪。
Macaroons will do that.
马卡龙就能做到。
Oh, I want to hear from Jane.
我想听听简的消息。
Hey, Jane.
嘿,简。
Hi, pigtails.
嗨,辫子。
Jane, can you tell us what you made?
简，你能告诉我们你做了什么吗?
JANE: What I made for you is
简:我给你做的是
a raspberry-white-chocolate macaroon.
覆盆子白巧克力马卡龙。
The filling is white-chocolate American butter cream,
馅料是白巧克力美式白脱奶油，
and then I also did half of a raspberry in there.
然后我还做了半个覆盆子。
That's looks professional to me.
在我看来这很专业。
I would buy this in a store.
我会在商店里买这个。
Boom, boom, yeah!
砰，砰，耶!
I really hope it tastes good, 'cause looks aren't everything.
我真心希望味道不错，因为外表不能代表一切。
Always worried that anything white-chocolate's
总是担心任何白巧克力的东西
gonna be too sweet, and it's not.
太甜蜜了，但事实并非如此。
It's really good.
真的很好吃。
That mouthful -- The subtle flavors in there.
那一口，那淡淡的味道。
The perfect crunch of the macaroon.
马卡龙嘎吱嘎吱的完美口感。
That's a macaroon. Or, I should say,
那是马卡龙。或者我应该说，
that's a French [French accent] macaroon.
那是法式(法国口音)马卡龙。
You've got the perfect pink color.
你的粉红色很完美。
Matches your shirt.
和你的衬衫相配。
The only comment I would make is I wish there was
我唯一想说的是，我希望有
just a little bit less butter cream in here.
少放一点白脱奶油。
Hey! [ Laughs ]
嘿![笑]
You made a heck of a macaroon.
你做的杏仁饼很好吃。
Alex.
亚历克斯。
So, today, I've made a creamsicle macaroon
所以，今天，我做了一个奶油棒马卡龙
and a red-velvet macaroon,
还有一个红丝绒马卡龙，
and it has a classic American butter cream.
还有经典的美式白脱奶油。
Alex, it looks like your macaroons got a little pinched.
亚历克斯，看起来你的杏仁饼干被捏了一下。
I mean, they're real wrinkly on top,
我是说，它们的顶部皱巴巴的，
and I think your macaroons are way too wet.
我觉得你的马卡龙太湿了
All right?
好吧?
Valerie, I want to taste the creamsicle macaroon.
瓦莱丽，我想尝尝奶油杏仁饼。
Alex, this is really, really sweet.
亚历克斯，这真的很贴心。
I think the sugar is overpowering everything.
我觉得糖太浓了。
Kids like sweetness, so these are like kid macaroons.
孩子们喜欢甜味，所以这些就像孩子们的马卡龙。
It doesn't taste like a creamsicle.
它尝起来不像冰棒。
I can barely taste the orange.
我几乎尝不出橘子的味道。
And I was so looking forward to the creamsicle!
我还一直盼着吃冰淇淋呢!
Let's try the red-velvet.
我们试试红丝绒吧。
It is a little chewy. Right.
有点难嚼。正确的。
But the flavor's all there.
但是味道都在那里。
I like it chewy like that.
我喜欢它那样有嚼劲。
You were definitely much more successful with the red-velvet.
你穿红丝绒肯定更成功。
Least one of them was really, really good.
至少有一个非常非常棒。
Emma.
艾玛。
So, I made a chocolate macaroon
所以，我做了一个巧克力马卡龙
with cream-cheese icing
加上奶油芝士糖霜
and a raspberry coulis in the middle.
中间是覆盆子酱。
Emma, you don't have any feet.
艾玛，你没有脚。
No, I don't.
不，我不知道。
There's something going on with the structure here.
这里的结构有些问题。
I don't know if it just dried weird.
我不知道是不是干得很奇怪。
if it cooled weird.
我不知道会不会很奇怪。
Was the batter too wet?
面糊太湿了吗?
Batter might have been too wet.
面糊可能太湿了。
I give this macaroon an F.
我给这个马卡龙打个F。
* Failure! *
*失败!＊
What it looks like is very important,
它的样子很重要，
but what's really important... is how they taste.
但真正重要的是……是它们的味道。
Mm-hmm!
嗯哼!
Emma, I'm definitely getting the chocolate.
艾玛，我一定要巧克力。
I'm definitely getting the raspberry.
我肯定会得到覆盆子。
It's really good.
真的很好吃。
The star of your dish is the coulis.
这道菜的主角是酱汁。
That is perfectly balanced.
这是完美的平衡。
Just enough sweetness, just enough tartness.
足够甜，足够酸。
Don't you agree? Totally. Delicious.
你不同意吗?完全。美味。
But...technically, it's probably not a macaroon.
但是…严格来说，这可能不是马卡龙。
I'm not feeling so good.
我感觉不太好。
Mmm, French macaroon.
嗯，法式马卡龙。
I say macaroons (maca-runes), 'cause I'm American.
我说马卡龙，因为我是美国人。
Matthew?
马修?
I'm feeling super, super, super confident.
我感觉超级，超级，超级自信。
Oh, you got cleaned up a little bit, did you?
哦，你被清理了一下，是吗?
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
So, Matthew, what did you make today?
马修，你今天做了什么?
I call it redemption on a plate, from last week.
我把它叫做盘子里的救赎，从上周开始。
We'll see.
我们将会看到。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I made chocolate macaroons with, like, a cherry shell
我做了巧克力马卡龙，里面有樱桃壳
and s'mores macaroons with graham crackers on the edge.
还有s'mores蛋白脆饼，边缘是全麦饼干。
Matthew, with your chocolate-cherry macaroon,
马修，你的巧克力樱桃杏仁饼
you got these little bumps on top.
你头顶上有小肿块。
Other than that, the shape is awesome.
除此之外，它的形状很棒。
You've got a nice lift. You've got a nice foot.
你搭了个顺风车。你的脚很漂亮。
Mmm.
嗯。
The macaroon by itself has a really light touch
马卡龙本身就很清淡
with the sugar.
加糖。
I like it. The filling's a little sweet.
我喜欢它。馅料有点甜。
Okay.
好吧。
It's good! It is good!
很好!很好!
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Valerie, let's try... the s'mores macaroon
瓦莱丽，我们试试…s'mores杏仁饼
with a marshmallow/ cream-cheese filling.
里面有棉花糖或奶油芝士。
[ Laughing ] I love that cream-cheese flavor.
(笑)我喜欢奶油奶酪的味道。
Wow!
哇!
Matthew!
马太福音!
I got marshmallow, I got chocolate.
我有棉花糖，还有巧克力。
It's just sweet enough.
这已经够甜了。
And the acidity of the cream cheese
还有奶油奶酪的酸味
is really nice in there. Mmm! Love it.
里面真的很漂亮。嗯!爱死它了。
Your presentation doesn't look as professional,
你的陈述看起来不那么专业，
but dude, you've got flavor in these two.
但是伙计，你这两个人很有味道。
Is it redemption?
是救赎吗?
This is a lot better than hot dog ice cream.
这可比热狗冰淇淋好吃多了。
Yeah!
是啊!
It's s'mores redemption day. Yes.
今天是s'mores救赎日。是的。
Wait, where you been the last couple weeks?
等等，这几周你去哪了?
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Rebecca?
丽贝卡?
In front of you, you have a red-velvet macaroon
在你面前的是红丝绒马卡龙
with strawberry-cream-cheese, fluffy frosting.
加上草莓奶油芝士，松软的糖霜。
Look at that foot.
看那只脚。
Your foot here is really nice.
你的脚真漂亮。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
What would make this better is if the filling
怎样做会更好呢
was a little more solid.
更坚固一点。
Yeah.
是的。
My filling should have been thicker,
我的馅料应该更厚一些，
which I know, but, I mean,
我知道，但是，我是说
this really stinks to actually hear it.
听起来真恶心。
Mmm.
嗯。
Love the cream cheese.
我喜欢奶油奶酪。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
But I'm not tasting chocolate.
但我不是在品尝巧克力。
Red-velvet is red plus chocolate.
红丝绒是红色加巧克力。
I think you could have a little bit more cocoa.
我觉得你可以再来点可可。
I really hope I don't go home.
我真希望我不要回家。
I want to go on to the next round,
我想进入下一轮，
and I do not want to go back to Texas.
我也不想回德州了
I love Texas, but not right now.
我爱德州，但不是现在。
Take it easy. Thanks.
别紧张。谢谢。
Wow! Look how pretty those are.
哇!看那些多漂亮啊。
Someone's feeling good.
有人感觉很好。
Yahshimabet, what'd you make today?
雅希玛贝特，你今天做了什么?
I made for you
我为你做的
a tiramisu-inspired French macaroon.
受提拉米苏启发的法式马卡龙
It's a chocolate-espresso cookie with two fillings.
这是一种巧克力浓缩饼干，有两种馅料。
And there's one that has a chocolate-hazelnut
还有一种是巧克力榛子口味的
filling with a little bit of nutmeg.
里面放一点肉豆蔻。
The other one is a chocolate-espresso ganache.
另一种是巧克力意式甘纳许。
I love the top -- the shiny, glittery gold top.
我喜欢这件上衣，闪闪发光的金色上衣。
Look at that, how beautiful that is.
看看，多漂亮啊。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
I hope they taste as good as they look.
我希望它们的味道和看起来一样好。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Let's try the chocolate-espresso French macaroon.
我们试试巧克力浓咖啡法式马卡龙吧。
Mmm!
嗯!
It's awesome.
这是可怕的。
That being said, texture-wise,
话虽如此，在材质方面，
this is not a classic French macaroon.
这不是经典的法式马卡龙。
It's cakier.
这是凝固的。
It's like a brownie with a crust or something.
就像带皮的布朗尼之类的。
Yeah, it's really good.
是的，真的很好吃。
[ Whispering ] No.
[低语]不。
And this is the chocolate-hazelnut?
这是巧克力榛子吗?
Yes.
是的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I may like this one more than the one with the ganache.
比起加了甘纳许的那个，我可能更喜欢这个。
It's just really smooth
非常光滑
and the flavors that you used in there
还有你在里面用的味道
just kind of subtly go together,
只是巧妙地结合在一起，
and just make for a really mouth-pleasing bite.
这样咬起来就很好吃了。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
[ Whispering ] I can win.
(低语)我能赢。
Thank you so much, Yahshimabet.
非常感谢你，Yahshimabet。
Very mature baker.
非常成熟的面包师。
The way she balances her flavors -- Wow!
她平衡口味的方式——哇!
Peggy?
佩吉?
I have a regular French macaroon
我有一个普通的法式马卡龙
with a chocolate ganache filling.
用巧克力甘纳许填充。
This one's really big.
这个真的很大。
This one's a perfect size.
这个尺寸正合适。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Do I look crazy? Mm-hmm.
我看起来疯了吗?嗯哼。
Oh, no! This is bad!
哦,不!这太糟糕了!
One of the things that we're judging on is consistency.
我们评判的标准之一是一致性。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Luckily, another thing we're judging on is flavor.
幸运的是，我们判断的另一件事是味道。
It's good. It's a lot of chocolate, though.
很好。不过，这里有很多巧克力。
I know you had some trouble getting your macaroons
我知道你吃杏仁饼有困难
off of the paper... Yeah.
从纸上……是的。
...and so it left kind of a hole.
…所以它留下了一个洞。
Yeah.
是的。
And that got filled up with chocolate.
里面塞满了巧克力。
Today is not my day. Not even close.
今天真倒霉。差远了。
However, it is an excellent ganache.
然而，这是一种很棒的甘纳许。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Your problem is not filling.
你的问题不在于填饱肚子。
isn't flavor.
你的问题不是口味。
It's just consistency and presentation.
这只是一致性和表现。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Pbht!
Pbht !
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package
会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包吗
that includes a feature story in Food Network Magazine...
包括《美食网络杂志》的一篇专题报道……
Oh, my gosh!
哦，天哪!
...and... $25,000.
…和…25000美元。
[ Kids screaming ]
[孩子们尖叫]
VALERIE: Just keep working, guys.
瓦莱丽:继续工作，伙计们。
Man, Valerie. Macaroons, huh?
人,瓦莱丽。杏仁饼干,嗯?
It was a very tension-filled day, today.
今天是非常紧张的一天。
I thought there were a few kids
我以为有几个孩子呢
that did an amazing job today.
今天做得很好。
Yahshimabet, Matthew, and Jane.
雅希玛贝特、马修和简。
Matthew! Yes.
马太福音!是的。
The crunch on Jane's macaroons was awesome.
简做的杏仁饼干嘎吱嘎吱的味道棒极了。
She let those things dry for a lot longer
她让那些东西干得更久
than anyone else, and it absolutely showed.
比任何人都好，这一点很明显。
The fresh raspberry was such a nice surprise,
新鲜的覆盆子真是个惊喜，
and such a nice touch.
这招真不错。
But the problem I had with Jane
但我和简之间的问题
was she used way too much filling.
她用了太多的填充物。
Way too much.
太多了。
But she didn't reach five inches, did she?
但她没长到五英寸，对吧?
She didn't. Mm.
她没有。毫米。
And then Yahshimabet's -- so pretty.
然后是Yahshimabet，太漂亮了。
With the sparkle on top, it was very subtle and sheeny.
加上上面的闪光，它非常微妙和闪亮。
But they weren't macaroon-y enough.
但它们还不够有马卡龙味。
It tasted a like a little brownie.
尝起来有点像小布朗尼。
Yeah, but it wasn't unenjoyable.
是的，但也不是不愉快。
No, it was delicious. It was delicious.
不，很好吃。味道很好。
And Yahshimabet's chocolate-coffee ganache?
还有Yahshimabet的巧克力咖啡甘纳许?
[ Sighs ] Out of this world.
(叹气)离开这个世界。
Matthew -- A tornado hits his station
马修——龙卷风袭击了他的车站
and amazing macaroons flew out of it.
美味的马卡龙从里面飞了出来。
I love the way that he put together that s'mores macaroon,
我喜欢他把巧克力夹心杏仁饼做成的样子，
and I love the fact that it wasn't just marshmallow,
我喜欢它不仅仅是棉花糖，
it was marshmallow and cream cheese.
是棉花糖和奶油奶酪。
What I really loved
我真正喜欢的
about Matthew's cherry-chocolate macaroons
马修的樱桃巧克力杏仁饼
was that little surprise of actual cherry inside.
里面有樱桃的小惊喜。
Yeah. The filling was very sweet.
是的。馅料很甜。
But I liked it.
但是我喜欢它。
Who do you think struggled today?
你认为今天是谁在挣扎?
Peggy.
佩吉。佩吉。
It really wasn't a classic macaroon
它真的不是经典的马卡龙
because when they came off the paper,
因为当他们从报纸上出来的时候，
the cookie stayed on the paper.
饼干留在了纸上。
All she had left was a shell,
她只剩下一个躯壳，
and so she filled it with that ganache.
于是她往里面放了巧克力酱。
So, when you look at it, it looked like, "Oh, wow!
所以，当你看着它的时候，它看起来就像，“哦，哇!
These are, like, professional,"
这些都很专业。”
and then you open it up and like, "Oh, no.
然后你打开它，然后说，“哦，不。
It's just a crust and it's full of ganache.
只是个饼皮，里面全是巧克力酱。
Pow!
战俘!
Yeah, but the good thing, the ganache tasted good.
是啊，但好消息是，巧克力酱味道不错。
That was delicious, and it would have been great
太好吃了，本来会很棒的
if the ratio was right.
如果比例合适的话。
You know who else really struggled today?
你知道今天还有谁很挣扎吗?
Emma? Yeah.
艾玛?是的。
Those did not look like macaroons.
那些看起来不像杏仁饼干。
But they were delicious. [ Laughing ] Yeah.
但是它们很好吃。(笑)是的。
Oh, my God. That coulis?
我的天啊。多尼?
Oh, I want her to come out to my house and make coulis.
哦，我想让她来我家做酱汁。
Perfect ratio of sweetness to tartness. Perfect!
甜与酸的完美比例。完美!
So, we got Peggy's ganache bomb, and we got Emma's...
我们有佩吉的巧克力酱炸弹，还有艾玛的…
It's a... BOTH: ..."macaroon."
这是一个…两种:……“蛋白杏仁饼干。”
Here's the tough part.
这是最难的部分。
Ohhhh! La, la, la, la, la, la!
喔!啦，啦，啦，啦!
Yep, I know.
是的，我知道。
We got to let one of them go.
我们得放走他们中的一个。
No! I don't want to!
不!我不想!
I know. I don't want to, either.
我知道。我也不想。
I'm pretty worried,
我很担心，
but that coulis might have saved me.
但那可能救了我。
Bakers, we asked you to make three-dozen macaroons,
面包师们，我们让你们做了30打马卡龙，
and as you well now know, it's not an easy task.
你也知道，这不是一件容易的事。
But three of you did make macaroons
但你们三个做了马卡龙
that really stacked up.
那真的堆积起来了。
Matthew...
马太福音……
Yahshimabet...
Yahshimabet……
and Jane.
和简。
Yes! That's right.
是的!这是正确的。
Yes, I am in the top three.
是的，我是前三名。
I hope I can win this,
我希望我能赢
but I know I can't because it wasn't tall enough.
但我知道我做不到，因为它不够高。
Jane, your raspberry macaroons
简，你的覆盆子杏仁饼
with white-chocolate butter cream
加白巧克力白脱奶油
look like they're made by a professional French baker.
看起来像是专业的法国面包师做的。
The texture was perfect.
口感很完美。
Good job.
好工作。
Yahshimabet...
Yahshimabet……
your chocolate-espresso macaroons -- really elegant.
你的巧克力浓咖啡马卡龙，真的很优雅。
And your chocolate-espresso ganache had
你的巧克力浓缩甘纳许
a really great, balanced coffee flavor.
非常棒，平衡的咖啡味道。
I'm in the top!
我在上面!
Yay!
耶!
Matthew, you did two different macaroon batters,
马修，你做了两种不同的杏仁饼糊，
and they were both delicious.
它们都很好吃。
Your s'mores macaroon had a nice cream-cheese filling,
你的s'mores马卡龙里面有很好的奶油奶酪馅儿，
and we loved the pretty decorations
我们喜欢这些漂亮的装饰
and the cherry surprise in your cherry macaroon.
还有樱桃杏仁饼里的樱桃惊喜。
I really think my macaroons deserve to win.
我真的觉得我的马卡龙应该赢。
But one of you created macaroons that were simply the best.
但你们中有一个人做出了最棒的马卡龙。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Matthew.
马修。
Redemption is yours!
救赎属于你!
Yes!
是的!
I'm the macaroon man!
我是马卡龙男!
Yay! I should've made hot-dog flavored macaroons!
耶!我应该做热狗味的马卡龙!
No! No!
不!不!
Now, bakers, there were two of you
面包师们，你们有两个人
that didn't quite make it to the top,
虽然没能成功，
but your macaroons were tasty enough to keep you
但你的马卡龙很好吃，足以留住你
in the competition for another week.
比赛还将持续一周。
Alex and Rebecca.
亚历克斯和丽贝卡。
[ Sighs deeply ] Oh, my gosh.
(深深叹息)哦，我的天哪。
Unfortunately...that leaves Peggy and Emma.
不幸的是……那就剩下佩吉和艾玛了。
Please step forward.
请往前走。
PEGGY: This is my second time on the bottom.
佩吉:这是我第二次在底部。
I don't like this feeling at all.
我一点也不喜欢这种感觉。
Peggy, your almond macaroons with chocolate ganache
佩吉，你的杏仁杏仁饼配巧克力甘纳许
were almost hollow.
几乎是空的。
The cookie was all crust,
饼干上全是酥皮，
and there was so much filling, that it was overpowering.
里面的馅料太多了，让人难以抗拒。
[ Exhales deeply ]
[深呼一口气]
Emma, your chocolate macaroon with raspberry coulis
艾玛，你的巧克力杏仁饼配覆盆子酱
and cream-cheese frosting was not quite a macaroon.
奶油芝士糖霜也不像马卡龙。
You know, this is one of the most difficult things
你知道，这是最困难的事情之一
we ever have to do.
我们必须做的事。
The baker who will be leaving us today is...
今天要离开我们的面包师是……
...Emma.
艾玛。
Emma, I'm gonna miss your sass.
艾玛，我会想念你的。
So miss your sass!
所以想念你的sass!
I don't know who's gonna keep me in line when you go.
我不知道你走后谁来管我。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Getting sent home was the worst feeling in the world.
被送回家是世界上最糟糕的感觉。
But I made it halfway through,
但我做了一半，
and I'm proud of myself for that.
我为自己感到骄傲。
I'm still gonna go to culinary school
我还是要去烹饪学校
because I love baking,
因为我喜欢烘焙
and I'm definitely gonna be a pastry chef one day.
总有一天我一定会成为糕点师
Hi, bakers!
嗨,面包师!
VALERIE: Meet the new kids on the block.
瓦莱丽:来见见新来的孩子。
Twelve of the best young bakers in America.
美国十二位最优秀的年轻面包师。
The way that you thought about this,
你考虑这件事的方式，
I'm really excited to see what you come up with. Thank you.
我真的很期待看到你的作品。谢谢你！
An infused apple pie with raspberry caviar.
覆盆子鱼子酱苹果派。
Ooh. DUFF: They have the skills...
哦。达夫:他们有技能……
This totally looks like a grilled cheese.
这看起来就像烤奶酪。
Oh!
哦!
...and the confidence...
…还有信心……
Smoked chocolate ganache. Yum!
烟熏巧克力甘纳许。Yum !
Sounds good, doesn't it?
听起来不错，不是吗?
DUFF: ...to wow and amaze.
达夫:…让人惊叹。
Oh, that looks beautiful. Thank you.
哦，看起来真漂亮。谢谢你！
Who will bake their way to $25,000...
他们会烤到25000美元
Hallelujah!
阿利路亚!
Yeah!
是啊!
...and become the Kids Baking Champion?
…成为儿童烘焙冠军?
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
Oh, my gosh, this place.
天啊，这地方。
I didn't think this would ever be happening.
我从没想过会发生这种事。
It's really happening. It's real.
这是真的。这是真实的。
It's like I'm dreaming right now.
我现在就像在做梦一样。
Duff and Valerie are about to come out and say hi to us.
达夫和瓦莱丽要出来跟我们打招呼了。
Oh.
哦。
[ All cheering ]
[众人欢呼]
Valerie is so cool.
瓦莱丽太酷了。
And I'm so excited to meet Duff.
我也很兴奋能见到达夫。
He's, like, my idol.
他是我的偶像。
Welcome to the "Kids Baking Championship".
欢迎来到“儿童烘焙锦标赛”。
[ All cheer ]
[欢呼]
I'm Duff Goldman. And this is Valerie Bertinelli.
我是达夫·戈德曼。这是瓦莱丽·波提纳尔。
You guys are competing for some serious prizes.
你们在竞争一些重要的奖品。
The winner of the Kids Baking Championship
儿童烘焙锦标赛的冠军
will get a story written about them
会有关于他们的报道吗
in Food Network Magazine.
《美食网络杂志》
And take home $25,000.
然后拿25000美元回家。
[ All cheering ]
[众人欢呼]
$25,000?
25000美元?
That's crazy!
这太疯狂了!
I could start one heck of a business.
我可以开始一项伟大的事业。
Jason's Crepes and Bakes.
杰森可丽饼店。
You guys ready for some fun?
你们准备好找点乐子了吗?
ALL: Yeah!
:是啊!
Great because you are just in time...
太好了，你来得正是时候……
for the carnival.
为了嘉年华。
Oh, no. Carnival?
哦,不。狂欢节吗?
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
You get to play the most popular game
你可以玩最流行的游戏
on the carnival midway.
在狂欢节的中途。
Duff Ball.
达夫球。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
So the baker that ends up the closest to the center
最后离中心最近的面包师
will get an advantage in the first big bake.
会在第一次大烘焙中占据优势。
Sorry in advance for hitting you.
先为打你道歉。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
The first person up is Jason.
第一个上来的是杰森。
Well done.
做得很好。
Kaniyah.
Kaniyah。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
The target is not my head.
目标不是我的头。
Okay?
好吧?
Justice.
正义。
Aidan. Okay.
艾丹。好吧。
Awe.
敬畏。
Cole.
科尔。
Audra.
Audra。
Brooke.
布鲁克。
Well done.
做得很好。
Charlotte.
夏洛特。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝。
Dylin, go for it.
迪林，加油。
Whoa, what an arm!
哇，好大的胳膊!
Keili. Let me have it.
Keili。给我吧。
Nope.
不。
Reese.
瑞茜。
Whoa.
哇。
Okay. Maya.
好吧。玛雅。
Aw!
哦!
Yeah!
是啊!
So that means Jason won.
也就是说杰森赢了。
Good job, Jason.
干得好，杰森。
You won an advantage.
你赢得了优势。
But we'll tell you about that later.
但我们稍后会告诉你。
All right, guys. It is time for your first big bake.
好了，伙计们。是时候做你的第一个大蛋糕了。
You have 2 hours to make one dozen cupcakes.
你有两个小时做一打小蛋糕。
[ Gasps ] Ooh.
[喘气]哦。
Yeah.
是的。
And because this is a carnival,
因为这是嘉年华，
you need to decorate your cupcakes
你需要装饰你的纸杯蛋糕
in a colorful, eye-catching way.
以一种丰富多彩、引人注目的方式。
Carnival? What am I supposed to incorporate into it?
狂欢节吗?我应该在里面加入什么?
Hot dogs?
热狗吗?
Remember, this is a competition.
记住，这是一场比赛。
They'll be one baker each week who wins the challenge
每周将有一名面包师赢得挑战
and then one baker who misses the mark
还有一个面包师没做到
and has to leave.
不得不离开。
All right, guys.
好了，伙计们。
Two hours to make one dozen carnival cupcakes.
两小时做一打狂欢节小蛋糕。
And your baking time starts...
你的烘焙时间开始了…
now! Now!
现在!现在!
AUDRA: Lemons.
AUDRA:柠檬。
We have to make two dozen cupcakes in 2 hours
我们得在两小时内做两打小蛋糕
and decorate them so they stand out from all the others.
然后把它们装饰一下，让它们从其他的装饰中脱颖而出。
Red, blue.
红色,蓝色。
I'm making a vanilla tie-dyed cupcake.
我在做香草扎染小蛋糕。
I cream my butter and sugar first
我先把黄油和糖搅匀
because it makes the cupcakes fluffy.
因为它会让纸杯蛋糕变得松软。
I combine flour, salt, and baking powder
我把面粉、盐和发酵粉混合在一起
and add that to my wet ingredients.
把它加到我的湿食材里。
Carnival cupcake version of tie-dyed.
狂欢节纸杯蛋糕版扎染。
I want a nice, deep red.
我想要一个漂亮的深红色。
Oh, that looks nice.
哦，看起来不错。
I also want dark blue and white when they cut open the cupcake.
我还想要他们切开小蛋糕时的深蓝色和白色。
My name is Jason.
我叫杰森。
And I live in Seattle, Washington.
我住在华盛顿州的西雅图。
I love science.
我热爱科学。
And I think baking is like science.
我认为烘焙就像科学一样。
But you get to eat your experiments.
但你可以吃你的实验品。
Delicious.
美味。
Ooh, cupcakes.
哦,蛋糕。
Blue!
蓝色的!
You don't want to blend the colors
你不想把颜色混在一起
because it'll just be like a brown.
因为它会变成棕色。
You kind of layer it.
你把它分层。
Perfect.
完美的。
Red, white, and blue, okay.
红，白，蓝，好的。
Lemons. I need lemons. I love lemon.
柠檬。我需要柠檬。我喜欢柠檬。
I've never made a carnival dessert.
我从来没做过狂欢节甜点。
But cupcakes are my specialty. So I'm not worried at all.
但纸杯蛋糕是我的专长。所以我一点也不担心。
I am making lemon cupcakes
我在做柠檬纸杯蛋糕
and raspberry frosting.
还有覆盆子糖霜。
My name is Audra Tow. I'm 10 years old.
我叫Audra Tow。我10岁了。
And I live in Aurora, Colorado.
我住在科罗拉多州的奥罗拉。
I love my cat.
我爱我的猫。
I'm actually really good at imitating her meow.
我真的很擅长模仿她的喵喵叫。
Meow.
猫叫。
I get my baking inspiration from my Nana.
我的烘焙灵感来自我奶奶。
She taught me to bake when I was 5.
我五岁时她教我烘焙。
And then my love for baking
还有我对烘焙的热爱
just began to, like, grow and grow.
就开始长啊长啊。
I can't wait to show the world what I can do.
我等不及要向世界展示我的能力了。
To make my cupcakes,
来做我的小蛋糕，
I add a little bit of lemon flavor.
我加了一点柠檬味。
That's gonna...
这是要……
Going fast.
要快。
I fill the cupcake liners as fast as I can.
我以最快的速度填满纸杯蛋糕的衬垫。
I hope these cupcakes aren't too small.
我希望这些纸杯蛋糕不会太小。
I'm not sure if I added enough cake batter to each cupcake.
我不确定我在每个小蛋糕里加的蛋糕糊够不够。
Okay, I have to put these in the oven.
好了，我得把这些放进烤箱。
I think I'll be fine after they're baked.
我想烤好后我就没事了。
Perfect.
完美的。
Maple bacon cupcakes.
枫糖培根蛋糕。
My name is Aidan. I'm 12 years old.
我叫艾登。我12岁了。
And I'm from the really small town next to a city,
我来自一个紧邻城市的小镇，
next to a bigger city, all by the beach.
紧挨着一个更大的城市，都在海边。
Watching the "Kids Baking Championship"
观看“儿童烘焙锦标赛”
inspired me to become a very serious baker.
激励我成为一名非常认真的面包师。
And now I'm here.
现在我在这里。
It's pretty amazing.
真是太神奇了。
I'm gonna put maple in the cupcake
我要在小蛋糕里放枫糖
and a big piece of bacon right on it.
还有一大块培根在上面。
I've only cooked bacon once before.
我以前只做过一次培根。
I don't even 100% remember how to.
我都不记得怎么说了。
That's gonna go in there until it's all crispy.
把它放进去，直到它变得酥脆。
All right.
好吧。
Whoo, that's strong.
哇，真厉害。
I'm gonna check my bacon.
我要检查一下我的培根。
Is that bacon?
那是培根吗?
Looks pretty cooked.
看起来很熟。
If you have any extra, I'd like to eat some.
如果你还有多余的，我想吃一些。
Bacon's got my name on it, Audra.
培根上有我的名字，奥德拉。
You get all the bacon. I get it.
你得到了所有的培根。我明白了。
Thirty minutes gone. 90 minutes left, bakers.
30分钟过去了。还有90分钟，面包师们。
Hey, Maya, can I borrow the blue?
玛雅，我能借一下蓝色的吗?
Oh, yeah, sure.
哦，是的，当然。
Thanks. Yeah.
谢谢。是的。
KEILI: My name is Keili Gorczyca.
凯丽:我的名字是凯丽·葛奇卡。
It's a Polish last name.
这是一个波兰姓氏。
It means "mustard seed."
它的意思是“芥菜籽”。
I would describe myself as weird.
我觉得自己很奇怪。
Definitely weird.
肯定奇怪。
I can even get weird with baking.
我甚至会对烘焙感到奇怪。
Like, I'll chop up grasshoppers, coat 'em in chocolate,
比如，我会剁蚱蜢，在它们身上涂上巧克力，
and make a grasshopper chocolate cookie.
做一个蚱蜢巧克力饼干。
I'm making a vanilla tie-dye cupcake.
我在做香草扎染小蛋糕。
The purple mixing in with the blue.
紫色和蓝色混合在一起。
And it's making it turn dark.
它让天变黑了。
But I can't do another batter.
但我不能再做面糊了。
I'm gonna put them in the oven.
我要把它们放进烤箱。
Cupcakes? Piece of cake.
蛋糕吗?小菜一碟。
Literally.
字面上。
There has never been a boy winner
从来没有男孩赢过
to win the Kids Baking Championship.
赢得儿童烘焙锦标赛
Probably because I just got here.
可能因为我刚到这里。
My name is Cole. I'm 12 years old.
我叫科尔。我12岁了。
And I'm the best baker in America.
我是美国最好的面包师。
I'm completely self-taught.
我完全是自学的。
I love to eat my food,
我喜欢吃我的食物，
and that just kind of encourages me to make more.
这也鼓励了我创作更多作品。
Whenever I go to the carnival,
每次我去嘉年华，
I always end up getting a root beer float
我最后总是喝冰沙
or some deep-fried sandwich cookies.
或者一些油炸三明治饼干。
So I'm making a yellow cake with root beer buttercream.
所以我要用沙士奶油做一个黄色蛋糕。
I'm gonna torch these marshmallows
我要烧了这些棉花糖
and air brush 'em to the perfect popcorn color.
然后把它们喷成完美的爆米花色。
And I'm gonna make some fresh deep-fried sandwich cookies
我要做一些新鲜的油炸三明治饼干
and stuff my cupcake.
把我的小蛋糕塞进去。
Your attention please, bakers.
请注意，面包师们。
Step right up, folks, step right up.
过来，伙计们，过来。
Uh-oh, here it comes.
哦，它来了。
We've got carnival treats for everyone.
我们为每个人准备了狂欢节大餐。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
Pretzels, cotton candy.
椒盐脆饼，棉花糖。
[ All groan ]
[大家都在呻吟]
Chocolate-covered bananas.
巧克力香蕉。
Ew!
哟!
Kettle corn.
水壶玉米。
Yep. Uh-oh.
是的。哦。
Caramel apples. Oh, boy.
焦糖苹果。哦,男孩。
Churros. [ Gasps ] I love churro.
油炸饼。我喜欢油条。
These treats are not for you to eat.
这些零食不是给你吃的。
No.
不。
You need to feature these in your cupcakes.
你要在你的小蛋糕里加上这些。
No!
不!
VALERIE: And, Jason, because you won the advantage,
瓦莱丽:杰森，因为你赢得了优势，
you get to hand out all the treats to the other bakers.
你要把所有的点心分发给其他的面包师。
Oh, no!
哦,不!
COLE: I need that kettle corn
科尔:我需要爆米花
because I'm already making marshmallow popcorn.
因为我已经在做棉花糖爆米花了。
Churros!
油炸饼!油炸饼!
Mmm, delicious.
嗯,很好吃。
Great.
太好了。
Caramel apple. Thank you.
焦糖苹果。谢谢你！
Kettle corn for Kaniyah.
Kaniyah的爆米花。
No!
不!
Oh, thanks.
哦,谢谢。
Cotton candy for me.
棉花糖给我。
Ugh, gosh.
啊,天啊。
Cotton candy doesn't go with deep-fried sandwich cookies.
棉花糖不能和油炸三明治饼干搭配。
Thanks a lot, Jason.
谢谢你，杰森。
I had the best cupcakes. And you ruined it.
我吃了最棒的小蛋糕。而你毁了它。
Ai-yi-yi.
Ai-yi-yi。
DUFF: One dozen carnival cupcakes with our carnival treat.
达夫:一打狂欢节纸杯蛋糕和我们的狂欢节大餐。
What's it gonna be? Churros!
会是什么?油炸饼!
Oh!
油炸饼!哦!
Twins!
双胞胎!
Pretzels for me?
椒盐脆饼给我?
Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢。
COLE: Ai-yi-yi.
科尔:Ai-yi-yi。
I had chocolate sandwich cookie stuffed cupcake
我吃了巧克力夹心曲奇小蛋糕
with a root beer buttercream.
加根汁啤酒奶油。
Cotton candy doesn't go with that.
棉花糖可配不上这个。
I'm just gonna put it on top for decoration.
我要把它放在上面装饰一下。
I hope the judges still like it the same.
我希望评委们仍然喜欢它。
KANIYAH: I have never been to a carnival before.
卡尼亚:我以前从来没有参加过狂欢节。
But I can bake with the best of them.
但我可以和他们中的佼佼者一起烘焙。
I'm Kaniyah. I am 10 years old.
我Kaniyah。我10岁了。
I am the tiny Beyoncé of baking.
我是烘焙界的小碧昂丝。
I got a lot of core dance moves.
我有很多核心舞步。
I am the queen of cakes.
我是蛋糕女王。
I'm making a vanilla cupcake
我在做香草小蛋糕
with vanilla cola buttercream.
加香草可乐奶油。
I am sifting my flour
我正在筛面粉
so I don't have any little flour chunks
所以没有面粉块
inside of my cupcake.
在我的小蛋糕里。
You all right?
你没事吧?
'Cause that was pretty funny.
因为那很有趣。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
I whip my egg whites until they form soft peaks.
我把蛋清打至形成柔软的峰状。
Then I fold them into my cupcake batter.
然后我把它们放进蛋糕面糊里。
The cupcake batter is smooth
蛋糕面糊很光滑
and doesn't have thick clumps in it.
而且里面没有厚厚的团块。
I'm gonna crush the popcorn into little small pieces.
我要把爆米花压成小块。
Perfect.
完美的。
And I scoop it on top of the cupcake
我把它舀在小蛋糕上
and put 'em in the oven.
然后把它们放进烤箱。
Okay. Now I have 'em.
好吧。现在我有了。
Maya is so cute.
玛雅太可爱了。
You can barely see her over the counter.
你在柜台上几乎看不到她。
You know one of those little signs,
你知道其中一个小标志，
you know, like before the roller coaster, like,
就像坐过山车之前，
"You must be this high to compete
“你必须有这么高才能参加比赛
on 'Kids Baking Championship'".
参加“儿童烘焙锦标赛”。
She's not actually tall enough to compete on our show.
她还不够高，不能参加我们的节目。
I'm Maya. And I'm the youngest baker in the competition.
我是玛雅。我是比赛中最年轻的面包师。
I'm here to become the Kids Baking Champion,
我来这里是为了成为儿童烘焙冠军，
especially for the tiny people.
尤其是对小个子来说。
This one's for you.
这是给你的。
This actually looks like orange.
这个看起来是橙色的。
I am making a vanilla tie-dye cupcake
我在做香草扎染小蛋糕
with all the colors of the rainbow.
用彩虹的所有颜色。
I decide to incorporate the churros
我决定加入油条
by putting, like, a chunk of it inside the cupcake.
把一大块放在小蛋糕里。
So maybe if I put that in there, the judges will taste that.
所以如果我把它放进去，评委们可能会尝一下。
KEILI: I make buttercream frosting a good deal of the time.
凯莉:我经常做奶油糖霜。
But I wanna make it extra special.
但我想让它更特别。
So I'm gonna make chocolate cookies vanilla buttercream.
所以我要做巧克力饼干香草奶油。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
Pretzels -- What am I gonna do with pretzels?
椒盐卷饼，我该拿椒盐卷饼怎么办?
Oh, yeah. I'm gonna fry my pretzels.
哦,是的。我要煎椒盐脆饼。
I have never had a fried pretzel.
我从来没吃过油炸脆饼。
But I'm gonna coat them in sugar.
但我要把它们裹上糖。
How bad can it taste?
它能有多难吃?
Cooked these for a bit too long, but whatever.
煮得太久了，不过无所谓了。
Uh-oh. Ugh!
哦。啊!
I think that my cupcakes are messy.
我觉得我的小蛋糕太乱了。
But I'm gonna cover it in frosting
但我要在上面撒上糖霜
and then put some pretzels inside my cupcake
然后在我的小蛋糕里放些椒盐脆饼
and on top of the frosting.
放在糖霜上面。
Then I want to add some more pop.
然后我想再加点汽水。
I find these letters.
我找到了这些信。
I tape them onto the mini sticks. And I put 'em in.
我把它们粘在小棒上。我把它们放进去了。
What's the flavor of your cupcakes?
你的小蛋糕是什么味道的?
Lemon.
柠檬。
Mine are lemon.
我的是柠檬的。
Seriously? I thought of it first.
严重吗?是我先想到的。
No, you didn't.
不，你没有。是我先想到的。
My name is Dylin. I am 12 years old.
我叫迪林。我12岁了。
My dad is in the military.
我爸爸是军人。
And I've traveled all over the world because of it.
我因此走遍了世界各地。
I describe my baking as global
我形容我的烘焙是全球性的
because I'm inspired by all my travels.
因为我的旅行给了我灵感。
I am making a lemon cupcake
我在做柠檬小蛋糕
because Valerie loves lemons.
因为瓦莱丽喜欢柠檬。
I was gonna make a lemon frosting.
我要做柠檬糖霜。
I hate kettle corn. Ugh!
我讨厌爆米花。啊!
Thanks a lot, Jason!
非常感谢，杰森!
Jason gives me kettle corn, which I hate.
杰森给了我爆米花，我讨厌。
So now I have to switch my entire plan.
所以现在我必须改变我的整个计划。
What are you gonna do with it? Put it in the buttercream.
你要拿它做什么?把它放进奶油里。
I'm gonna chop some of mine
我要切一些我的
and put it on top of the frosting, too.
把它也放在糖霜上面。
To make my buttercream special, I add my kettle corn.
为了让奶油奶油与众不同，我加入了爆米花。
Kettle corn and lemon do not go together.
爆米花和柠檬不能一起吃。
But I made it work.
但我成功了。
Ooh, they look so good!
哦，它们看起来太棒了!
Thank you!
谢谢你！
You'll know when they taste good, too.
你也会知道它们什么时候好吃。
I don't like to decorate that much.
我不太喜欢装饰。
But at the same time, I have to make my cupcakes stand out.
但同时，我得让我的小蛋糕脱颖而出。
I decorate my cupcakes
我装饰我的纸杯蛋糕
with shredded bits of kettle corn,
用爆米花的碎粒，
chopped licorice, and colored chocolate chips.
切碎的甘草和彩色巧克力片。
JUSTICE: My name is Justice.
JUSTICE:我叫JUSTICE。
And I really love weather.
我真的很喜欢天气。
I am from Napa, California.
我来自加州的纳帕。
I could never live in Los Angeles.
我永远无法在洛杉矶生活。
It gets rain like an inch a year.
那里每年下一英寸的雨。
Because that's nothing. I couldn't live here.
因为这没什么。我不能住在这里。
DUFF: Justice, what's going on, man?
达夫:正义，怎么回事，伙计?
I decided to go with swirl cupcakes.
我决定做漩涡小蛋糕。
It's like forming a hurricane over water.
就像在水上形成飓风一样。
Are you a weather freak?
你是天气狂吗?
Yeah. Why does it get so hot here?
是的。为什么这里会变得这么热?
During summer, the high pressure system
夏季，高压系统
blocks away all of the, like, rain.
挡住了所有的雨水。
Ah! All right. Looks good, man.
啊!好吧。看起来不错，伙计。
Good luck, buddy. Okay, thank you.
祝你好运，伙计。好的，谢谢。
JUSTICE: Jason gave me caramel apple.
法官:杰森给了我焦糖苹果。
I think it's cool to have two ingredients out of one thing
我觉得一件东西有两种成分是很酷的
because now I can use the caramel in the buttercream.
因为现在我可以在奶油里加入焦糖了。
And then I cut the apple into little cubes.
然后我把苹果切成小方块。
I'm gonna deep-fry them for the top of my cupcakes.
我要把它们炸一下，放在小蛋糕上面。
I will do a multicolored buttercream frosting.
我要做一个五颜六色的奶油糖霜。
Because when you're at a carnival,
因为当你在嘉年华时，
you normally see, like, fun colors
你通常会看到有趣的颜色
and exciting things.
还有令人兴奋的事情。
I start to frost the cupcakes.
我开始给纸杯蛋糕涂糖霜。
But then I realize it's melting.
但后来我意识到它在融化。
I'm putting icing on a hot cupcake.
我在热蛋糕上撒糖霜。
This can only mean disaster.
这只能意味着灾难。
I'm going to throw my cupcakes into the blast chiller
我要把我的小蛋糕扔进冷冻机
and just hope and pray that they'll cool down in time.
希望并祈祷它们会及时冷却下来。
I'm making a Swiss meringue instead of an American.
我要做瑞士蛋白霜，而不是美国的。
American buttercream is just butter and sugar.
美式奶油就是黄油和糖。
Ew.
电子战。
Cook the egg whites so it's safe to eat.
把蛋清煮熟，这样吃起来就安全了。
Try Swiss meringue buttercream,
试试瑞士蛋白派奶油，
and you'll never go back to American.
你就再也回不了美国了
It's lighter. And it has a much silkier texture.
这是打火机。而且它的质地更柔滑。
Bananas don't really go with bacon maple,
香蕉和培根枫树不太搭，
but it'll work.
但它会起作用的。
I pipe the frosting and take a big slice of bacon
我涂上糖霜，拿了一大块培根
and a big chunk of chocolate-covered banana
还有一大块巧克力香蕉
and use that to garnish my cupcakes.
用它来装饰我的小蛋糕。
Lemon! I got the lemons!
柠檬!我拿到柠檬了!
I love making anything with citrus.
我喜欢用柑橘做任何东西。
I love citrus so much.
我非常喜欢柑橘。
So I'm making a lemon cupcake.
所以我要做一个柠檬小蛋糕。
A little bit more flour mixture.
再加一点面粉混合物。
My batter is so good.
我的面糊太好吃了。
Wanna taste mine?
想尝尝我的吗?
Okay. Thanks.
好吧。谢谢。
Welcome.
受欢迎的。
Mine's better, no offense.
我的更好，无意冒犯。
I'm Brooke. I'm 9 years old.
我是布鲁克。我9岁了。
And I live in Old Greenwich, Connecticut.
我住在康涅狄格州的老格林威治。
I've been baking since I was 2 with my grandma.
我从两岁起就开始和我奶奶一起烘焙。
And now, I have a successful baking business.
现在，我的烘焙生意很成功。
I am so excited to be here.
我很高兴来到这里。
I just wanna, like, have a dance.
我只是想，跳支舞。
So I'm making Swish meringue buttercream.
所以我要做Swish蛋白派奶油。
Forty-five minutes left, you guys!
还剩45分钟，伙计们!
The egg whites are finally done, and...
蛋白终于做好了，然后…
Ah, no!
啊,不!
...I dropped my egg whites.
…我的蛋清掉了。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝。
There's still a little bit left in my bowl.
我的碗里还剩下一点。
It's all I have now.
这是我现在的全部了。
But this isn't going to be enough for the frosting.
但这还不够做糖霜。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
DUFF: Thirty minutes left, bakers.
达夫:还剩30分钟，面包师们。
We want one dozen carnival-tastic cupcakes.
我们要一打狂欢节口味的小蛋糕。
Ugh!
啊!
I spilled my egg whites.
我把蛋清洒了。
It's all I have now.
这是我现在的全部了。
Ugh.
啊。
I have so much decorating to do.
我有很多装饰工作要做。
And I do not have time
我没有时间了
to make another Swiss meringue buttercream.
来做另一种瑞士蛋白霜奶油
Now I'm just going to make a fluffy vanilla frosting.
现在我要做一个松软的香草糖霜。
It's just butter and sugar.
只是黄油和糖。
And it's very quick and very easy.
而且非常快捷，非常简单。
I still don't have my filling done.
我还没补牙呢。
So honestly, I'm really worried.
老实说，我真的很担心。
I wish they could've tasted my Swiss meringue buttercream.
真希望他们能尝尝我的瑞士蛋白派奶油。
REESE: My favorite cupcake is red velvet.
里斯:我最喜欢的纸杯蛋糕是红丝绒蛋糕。
So that's what I'm gonna serve to Duff and Valerie today.
这就是我今天要给达夫和瓦莱丽做的。
Reese's cupcakes, he's the only one doing red velvet.
里斯的小蛋糕，只有他做红丝绒。
Good thinking, man. Smart kid.
好主意，伙计。聪明的孩子。
I'm Reese Smith.
我是里斯·史密斯。
And I am from Bloomfield Hills, Michigan.
我来自密歇根州的布卢姆菲尔德山。
My mom owns a bakery.
我妈妈开了一家面包店。
And she taught me everything about baking.
她教会了我烘焙的一切。
I am also a competitive athlete
我也是一名竞技运动员
with a lot of trophies and ribbons.
有很多奖杯和绶带。
So I know I'm a winner.
所以我知道我是赢家。
He gave me churros.
他给了我油条。
He gave me bananas.
他给了我香蕉。
What the heck? I do not like bananas.
搞什么鬼?我不喜欢香蕉。
But since I still have to make my buttercream...
但既然我还得做奶油…
Ew.
电子战。
...I'm gonna add my chocolate-covered bananas
…我要加入巧克力香蕉
to my frosting.
敬我的糖霜。
Ooh, it smells banana-y.
闻起来有香蕉味。
That's actually pretty cool.
这真的很酷。
Yeah. And it works.
是的。这是有效的。
I think I like this flavor.
我想我喜欢这个口味。
I put a gummy fish on 'em
我在上面放了块软糖
because I was at a carnival about a month ago
因为一个月前我参加了一个狂欢节
and actually won a fish.
还赢了一条鱼。
That looks cool.
看起来很酷。
I'm making an orange cupcake
我在做一个橙色的小蛋糕
because it's, like, bright and fun
因为它既明亮又有趣
and tastes really good.
味道真的很好。
My name is Charlotte d'Arabian.
我叫夏洛特·阿拉伯。
I have a passion for fashion designing.
我对时装设计很感兴趣。
It really helps me with my baking
它对我的烘焙很有帮助
because it helps me think creatively.
因为它帮助我创造性地思考。
I scoop a little bit less into my cupcake tins
我在纸杯蛋糕罐里舀的少一点
so I have a little bit of wiggle room
所以我还有一点回旋的余地
for extra frosting.
额外的糖霜。
I'm making Swiss buttercream frosting.
我在做瑞士奶油糖霜。
To make my cupcakes look carnival,
为了让我的小蛋糕看起来像狂欢节，
I'm adding red food coloring
我在添加红色食用色素
to make my frosting turn pink.
让我的糖霜变成粉红色。
So a nice, yummy carnival cupcake.
一个美味的狂欢节小蛋糕。
And I add in churro.
然后加入油条。
[ Sighs ] God.
(叹气)天哪。
And it's not structuring as I hoped it would be.
它的结构不像我希望的那样。
It's so thin.
它太薄了。
Charlotte's piping her frosting.
夏洛特在吹糖霜。
And it looks really, really thin.
它看起来非常非常薄。
VALERIE: It's runny.
瓦莱丽:是稀的。
Oh, my God, this is so liquidy.
天啊，流动性太好了。
I don't have time to redo it.
我没时间重做了。
So I'm calling it a glaze.
所以我叫它釉。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
COLE: Not enough root beer.
没有足够的沙士。
I want my cupcakes to stand out.
我想让我的小蛋糕脱颖而出。
So I decided I'm gonna paint streaks of dye
所以我决定画一条条的染料
into my piping bag
放进我的裱花袋里
and then add my frosting to give that lollipop look.
然后加上糖霜，让它看起来像棒棒糖。
Yes. That's awesome.
是的。太棒了。
It's very hard to incorporate cotton candy.
很难加入棉花糖。
So I just decide to put it on top.
所以我决定把它放在最上面。
With the deep-fried sandwich cookies and marshmallow popcorn,
油炸三明治饼干和棉花糖爆米花，
I think that the judges are gonna love the decorations.
我觉得评委们会喜欢这些装饰的。
I take my cupcakes out of the oven.
我把小蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来。
Whipped cream.
鲜奶油。
To finish, I make my vanilla whipped cream.
最后，我做了香草生奶油。
I take one cupcake out.
我拿出一个小蛋糕。
I put a little whipped cream on it.
我在上面放了一点鲜奶油。
Now, the cotton candy is just gonna melt.
棉花糖马上就要融化了。
That's not gonna work.
这没用的。
I'm gonna have to figure a way.
我得想个办法。
This whipped cream is not working.
这鲜奶油不管用。
I'm nervous that my cotton candy would just melt in it.
我担心我的棉花糖会融化在里面。
Jason chose cotton candy.
杰森选择了棉花糖。
But it looks like he's struggling with it.
但看起来他很挣扎。
That might be a little bit of a challenge.
这可能有点难度。
He thought he was just gonna get to eat it.
他以为他可以吃了它。
That would've been my downfall.
那会是我的失败。
The cotton candy might just disintegrate.
棉花糖可能会分解。
I'm gonna have to do without.
我只能将就了。
Just gonna get rid of the whipped cream
我要把搅打过的奶油去掉
and use stars
用星星
so that it stays together and doesn't fall off.
这样它就能粘在一起，不会脱落。
This twist, I should've gone with something else.
这个转折，我应该用别的。
BROOKE: Frosting is done. I need to start to decorate.
霜已经做好了。我要开始装饰了。
Clowns say "carnival" to me.
小丑对我说"狂欢节"
Its a crumble filling.
这是酥皮馅。
I wanna make sure my cupcake look like a clown.
我想确保我的小蛋糕看起来像个小丑。
The first thing I do is scoop out the center
我要做的第一件事就是把中间挖出来
so I can fill it with my sweet pretzel filling.
这样我就可以把我的甜脆饼馅填进去了。
You have to look amazing, cupcakes.
小蛋糕们，你得打扮得美美的。
I take a little bit of frosting
我取一点糖霜
of my little ice cream scoop of cake.
我的小冰淇淋勺蛋糕。
Put it on top of the cupcake.
把它放在小蛋糕上面。
Take blue chocolate candies as my eyes
以蓝色巧克力糖为我的眼睛
and take one of these starfish candies
再拿一块海星糖
and use it as a hat.
把它当帽子用。
I think I'm gonna finish.
我想我要结束了。
Ah, God.
啊,上帝。
Eek. My cupcakes are really short.
唷。我的纸杯蛋糕真的很短。
So I'm hoping that my frosting will make up for that.
所以我希望我的糖霜能弥补这一点。
Come on.
来吧。
I hate green apples.
我讨厌青苹果。
I am now making a caramel frosting
我现在在做焦糖糖霜
topped with apple bits.
上面撒上苹果粒。
I get out my powdered sugar and measure out 3 cups of it.
我拿出糖粉，量出3杯。
Add butter, then I add caramel from my caramel apples
加入黄油，然后加入焦糖苹果中的焦糖
and mix that all up.
把它们混合起来。
Wait a sec.
等一下。
Did I not put one of the cups of powdered sugar in?
我不是放了一杯糖粉进去吗?
I forgot to add a whole cup of powdered sugar.
我忘了加一整杯糖粉。
Epic fail!
史诗般的失败!
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
Wait.
等待。
Now thinking about it, I can't remember.
现在想想，我不记得了。
I'm going to put that in.
我要把它放进去。
So I just add more.
所以我要加更多。
I just need to finish these.
我只需要完成这些。
Perfect.
完美的。
KANIYAH: My cupcakes come out of the oven.
我的小蛋糕刚从烤箱里出来。
And they look really good.
它们看起来真的很不错。
And I put them in the blast chiller so they can cool faster
我把它们放进冷却机里，这样它们就能冷却得更快
because I'm running out of time.
因为我没时间了。
I need to hurry and make my frosting.
我得快点做糖霜了。
I'm adding cola because I want to add some carnival flavor.
我加可乐是因为我想加点狂欢节的味道。
My buttercream is mixing.
我的奶油开始混合了。
And it starts to separate.
它开始分离。
It feels like cake batter.
感觉就像蛋糕糊。
I think the cola is messing it up.
我觉得可乐把它弄乱了。
Um...
嗯…
Twenty minutes left!
还剩20分钟!
I am running out of time.
我快没时间了。
And I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
ANNOUNCER: Popcorn, caramel, and apples
解说员:爆米花、焦糖和苹果
become caramel popcorn balls on a stick after this.
在这之后变成一根棍子上的焦糖爆米花球。
ANNOUNCER: How to make caramel popcorn balls on a stick.
解说员:如何用棍子做焦糖爆米花球。
Gather together apples, popcorn, caramel,
把苹果，爆米花，焦糖，
a sheet tray, and lollipop sticks.
一个纸盘，还有棒棒糖棒。
Dice your apple into bite-size pieces.
把苹果切成一口大小的小块。
Pop your corn.
打开你的玉米。
Combine the apples and popcorn and pour on some melted caramel.
把苹果和爆米花混合，倒上一些融化的焦糖。
Mix until evenly coated.
搅拌均匀。
Spoon into even-size balls and serve on a stick.
用勺子舀成均匀大小的球，放在棍子上食用。
For more fun treats like this,
想要获得更多这样的乐趣，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
VALERIE: Fifteen minutes left, bakers!
瓦莱丽:还剩15分钟，面包师们!
We want one dozen carnival-tastic cupcakes!
我们要一打狂欢节口味的纸杯蛋糕!
Um...
嗯…
My buttercream is, like, soupy and separated.
我的奶油有点浓汤，而且分开了。
I put it back on the mixer because I don't know what to do.
我把它放回搅拌器上，因为我不知道该怎么办。
How ya doing? Oh, baby.
你好吗?哦,宝贝。
My frosting is not working.
我的糖霜坏了。
Your frosting is not working?
你的糖霜坏了?
Okay, what is your most favorite frosting to make?
好吧，你最喜欢做什么糖霜?
The easiest for you to do?
你最容易做到的是什么?
Buttercream. Then do it.
奶油乳酪。那就去做吧。
Just get it done. You can do it.
把它做完。你能做到的。
I would've just gave up.
我早就放弃了。
You got this. You got it.
你能行的。你说对了。
I have to restart.
我得重新开始。
Valerie made me feel so much better.
瓦莱丽让我感觉好多了。
This time, I'm making a vanilla buttercream.
这次，我要做香草奶油。
I need to hurry.
我得快点了。
Ten minutes, bakers!
十分钟，面包师们!
I feel like I'm in "The Hunger Games" right now.
我觉得我现在就像在《饥饿游戏》里。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
It's like down to, like, danger point.
就像降到危险点一样。
So I decide I'm just gonna do an easy whipped cream
所以我决定做一个简单的生奶油
because, like, I only have a few minutes left.
因为，我只剩下几分钟了。
[ Gasps ]
[喘息]
Ooh!
噢!
The whipped cream is gonna be too runny
生奶油太稀了
to put in a piping bag.
装在裱花袋里
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
So I'm just gonna dollop it on.
所以我要把它涂上去。
And I think that carnivals are a bit messy,
我觉得嘉年华会有点乱，
so it kind of goes with the decoration.
这和装饰很搭。
Sixty seconds, bakers. You got one minute!
60秒，面包师们。给你一分钟!
This frosting is a little messy.
这个糖霜有点乱。
But it's gonna taste good.
但味道会很好。
Thirty seconds!
三十秒!
I have no time left.
我没有时间了。
5...4...3...2...1!
5…4 3…2…1 !
Hands up!
举起手来!
Whoo!
哇!
Step away from the cupcakes.
离纸杯蛋糕远点。
We'll see you at the judging table.
我们在裁判台上见。
Dun-dun-dun!
Dun-dun-dun !
Carnival cupcakes -- Who'd have thought?
狂欢节纸杯蛋糕——谁能想到呢?
What are we getting ourselves into?
我们这是在给自己找麻烦?
I don't know.
我不知道。
I think we should bring in Aidan. Mm-hmm.
我觉得我们应该叫上艾登。嗯哼。
Aidan, come on in.
艾登，请进。
I'm really excited
我真的很兴奋
because I know Duff loves bacon.
因为我知道达夫喜欢培根。
So I think it's gonna be good.
所以我觉得会很好。
First of all, nobody knew from the giant huge pieces
首先，没有人知道这些巨大的碎片
of bacon sticking out of your cupcakes.
培根从你的小蛋糕里伸出来。
It literally says "bacon."
字面意思是“培根”。
I approve of this message.
我赞成这个消息。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
At the same time, you didn't render the bacon all the way.
与此同时，你也没有把培根烤熟。
You don't wanna see that congealed fat.
你不会想看到凝结的脂肪的。
Got it. Why don't you give us the rundown
明白了。你给我们简要介绍一下吧
on your carnival cupcakes
在你的狂欢节纸杯蛋糕上
that incorporate real carnival treats?
包括真正的狂欢节美食吗?
It's a vanilla maple cupcake
这是香草枫糖纸杯蛋糕
with maple chocolate banana buttercream
加枫巧克力香蕉奶油
and a bit of bacon
再来一点培根
and a chocolate-covered banana slice on top.
再在上面放一块巧克力香蕉片。
When you slice the banana and it starts to get brown,
当你切香蕉时，它开始变黄，
it just doesn't look really appealing.
只是看起来不怎么吸引人。
That savory bite of bacon
那一口美味的培根
with that maple tastes really good.
枫木的味道真的很好。
Dude, you got the flavor there.
伙计，你真有味道。
Yeah, your buttercream is really good.
是的，你的奶油很好吃。
I can really taste that banana and chocolate in there.
我真的能尝到香蕉和巧克力的味道。
It's good. Thanks.
很好。谢谢。
Good job, Aidan. Bye.
干得好，艾登。再见。
See ya.
再见。
You just ate my bacon. Mm-hmm.
你刚吃了我的培根。嗯哼。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
How's it going, Audra? Good.
最近怎么样，奥德拉?好。
What did you make for us?
你为我们做了什么?
A lemon cupcake
柠檬纸杯蛋糕
with caramel frosting
加上焦糖糖霜
topped with chopped up apple.
上面撒上切碎的苹果。
Nice, clean piping. Thank you.
漂亮干净的管道。谢谢你！
But that's a lot of frosting on a little, short cupcake.
但小蛋糕上的糖霜太多了。
I know.
我知道。
It's like, "Would you like some cupcake with your frosting?"
就像"你想要加糖霜的小蛋糕吗"
Exactly.
完全正确。
I love the lemon flavor of the cupcake.
我喜欢这小蛋糕的柠檬味。
Not real sure about the frosting.
不太确定要不要加糖霜。
I think your frosting is a tad sweet.
我觉得你的糖霜有点甜。
How much sugar did you put in? Three cups.
你放了多少糖?三杯。
I might've put in a little more than three cups.
我可能放的比三杯多一点。
To how much butter? Half a pound.
要多少黄油?半磅。
That's a lot of sugar.
那是很多糖。
But I am tasting caramel. And I'm tasting apple.
但我尝到了焦糖的味道。我正在品尝苹果。
And I love how colorful it is.
我喜欢它的色彩。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Audra, thank you so much.
Audra，非常感谢你。
Thank you! Bye! Great job.
谢谢你！再见!伟大的工作。
Charlotte!
夏洛特!
Hi!
嗨！
You look really excited.
你看起来很兴奋。
I am super nervous.
我超级紧张。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
[ Giggles ]
[咯咯笑]
Tell us about your cupcake.
跟我们说说你的小蛋糕。
It's an orange cupcake with glaze
这是一个涂了釉的橙色小蛋糕
with a hint of cinnamon sugar because I had churros
加上一点肉桂糖，因为我吃了油条
with churro on top
上面放上油条
and then white-chocolate swirls around it.
然后白巧克力绕着它打转。
It's a tiny cupcake.
这是一个小蛋糕。
Usually when you're baking a cupcake, you want the batter
通常当你烤小蛋糕的时候，你需要面糊
just to go right up to the top of the paper.
只需要直接到纸的顶部。
Okay, thanks.
好的,谢谢。
Looks like your frosting did something weird.
看来你的糖霜做了些奇怪的事。
Yeah. It was supposed to be a buttercream.
是的。本来应该是奶油的。
I kind of overestimated the sugar,
我有点高估了糖的含量，
so I sort of made it a glaze.
所以我把它做成了一种釉。
Oh, I see.
哦，我明白了。
I think I made a big mistake.
我想我犯了个大错误。
I'm like, "Ah!"
我说:“啊!”
Okay, Charlotte.
好的,夏洛特。
We asked you to make us carnival cupcakes.
我们让你给我们做嘉年华小蛋糕。
And it looks like your frosting did something weird.
看起来你的糖霜做了些奇怪的事。
Yeah, sort of.
是的，算是吧。
Are you gonna eat the cupcake the right way,
你会用正确的方式吃蛋糕吗，
or are you just -- Well, it's a little too thin.
还是你只是有点太薄了
Yeah.
是的。
But maybe I can do that.
但也许我能做到。
All right. Let's see.
好吧。让我们来看看。
Listen, I think your sponge is delicious.
听着，我觉得你的海绵很好吃。
Nice orange flavor.
很好的橙味。
Yeah. Definitely reads churro.
是的。绝对是油条。
But I think your biggest problem is just that
但我认为你最大的问题是
your frosting really isn't a frosting.
你的糖霜真的不是糖霜。
Okay. All right.
好吧。好吧。
Thank you. Thank you, Charlotte.
谢谢你！谢谢你，夏洛特。
Brooke, did you have fun today? Yeah.
布鲁克，你今天玩得开心吗?是的。
You did? Tell us about your cupcake.
你做了吗?跟我们说说你的小蛋糕。
I made a lemon cupcake with a vanilla buttercream
我做了一个柠檬小蛋糕加香草奶油
and sweet pretzel filling.
还有甜脆饼馅。
The cupcakes have faces. It's kind of cute.
纸杯蛋糕有脸。挺可爱的。
Oh, I see.
哦，我明白了。
I don't.
我不喜欢。
The star is the mouth, and the chocolates are the eyes.
星星是嘴巴，巧克力是眼睛。
The eyes are the chocolates,
眼睛是巧克力，
and the star is just like a hat.
星星就像一顶帽子。
Oh! It's like that!
哦!就是这样!
Yeah.
是的。
I like the decoration.
我喜欢这里的装饰。
They're a little underbaked.
他们有点不成熟。
You can kind of taste the flour a little bit.
你可以尝出一点面粉的味道。
Oh, okay. You know what I mean?
哦,好的。你懂我的意思吗?
I like that pretzel in there, though.
不过我喜欢里面的椒盐卷饼。
That's really good. Thanks.
那真是太好了。谢谢。
What's going on with your frosting?
你的糖霜怎么了?
I may have under-mixed it.
我可能没调好。
Yeah, you definitely under-mixed it.
是啊，你肯定没调好。
I just got a big bite of butter.
我刚咬了一大口黄油。
Just pure butter.
就是纯黄油。
Yay.
耶。
I love butter, but...yeah.
我喜欢黄油，不过…
All right.
好吧。
Thanks, Brooke. You're welcome.
谢谢,布鲁克。不客气
Cole, what kind of cupcake did you make?
科尔，你做了什么样的小蛋糕?
It's a yellow cake stuffed with a deep-fried sandwich cookie
这是一个塞满了油炸三明治饼干的黄色蛋糕
with root beer buttercream,
用沙士奶油，
topped with a deep-fried sandwich cookie,
上面放着油炸三明治饼干，
cotton candy, and marshmallow popcorn.
棉花糖和棉花糖爆米花。
We got cotton candy -- make at the carnival --
我们有棉花糖，在嘉年华上做
deep-friend sandwich cookie -- they make at the carnival --
好朋友三明治饼干，他们在嘉年华做的
yellow cake, so vanilla... Yes.
黄色的蛋糕，香草味的……是的。
...which makes, like, a root beer float
…这就像漂浮沙士吗
that you would also get at the fair.
你在集市上也能买到。
The way that you thought about this,
你考虑这件事的方式，
I'm really excited to see what you come up with next.
我真的很期待看到你接下来的作品。
But with how creative you are,
但以你的创造力，
I feel like you could've come up with a more creative use
我觉得你可以想出更有创意的用法
for the cotton candy. Okay.
为了棉花糖。好吧。
There are so many flavors going on here.
这里有很多不同的口味。
I'm wondering, what's the star?
我在想，星星是什么?
I got it.
我明白了。
Only you, Duff Goldman.
只有你，达夫·高曼。
Boy, do I taste root beer.
天啊，我尝起来像根汁汽水。
This cupcake is moist, it's not overbaked.
这个小蛋糕很湿，没有烤过头。
It's just a little too much root beer flavor.
只是沙士味有点太浓了。
Okay. All right. Cole, Thank you so much.
好吧。好吧。科尔，非常感谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
What's up, Dylin?
怎么了，迪林?
My cupcake is a lemon cupcake
我的小蛋糕是柠檬小蛋糕
with a kettle corn frosting.
配上玉米糖霜。
And I have a bunch of candy on top.
我在上面放了一堆糖果。
What are the colorful little guys?
这些五颜六色的小家伙是什么?
Those are colored chocolate chips.
那些是彩色巧克力片。
You know... lemon and chocolate.
你知道的…柠檬和巧克力。
Lemon and chocolate, they go together.
柠檬和巧克力是搭配的。
Come on. They're just fine. Sure they do.
来吧。他们很好。当然有。
What was your inspiration to go with lemon?
你用柠檬的灵感是什么?
Valerie loves lemon.
瓦莱丽喜欢柠檬。
Of course. Here we go.
当然可以。开始吧。
There's a little bit of chocolate in there,
里面有一点巧克力，
so let's see how this goes.
我们来看看这是怎么回事。
Mmm. Yeah?
嗯。是吗?
Mm-hmm. It's all right?
嗯哼。没事吧?
You know why?
你知道为什么吗?
Because the kettle corn.
因为爆米花。
I -- okay, listen. I'm -- I respect your opinion.
我，好吧，听着。我尊重你的意见。
But I don't think the chocolate and lemon go good together.
但我觉得巧克力和柠檬不太搭。
Okay. All right.
好吧。好吧。
I think it's a really good cupcake.
我觉得这个小蛋糕很好吃。
I think your frosting is wicked sweet.
我觉得你的糖霜太甜了。
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
嗯哼。谢谢你！
That wasn't a compliment.
那不是恭维。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
But the cupcake itself is really good.
但是小蛋糕本身真的很好吃。
Great job. Thank you so much.
伟大的工作。非常感谢。
All right, thank you so much. Thank you.
好的，非常感谢。谢谢你！
Reese, tell us about the decoration on your cupcake.
里斯，跟我们说说你小蛋糕上的装饰吧。
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事?
I use fish like what you can win at a carnival.
我用的鱼就像你在嘉年华上赢的一样。
Yeah. You always take them home in the baggies.
是的。你总是把它们装在袋子里带回家。
Right. That's very clever.
正确的。这很聪明。
I did that, like, a month ago, actually.
我大概一个月前就这么做了。
Is he still alive? No.
他还活着吗?不。
Well, this is an homage to your fish.
这是向你的鱼致敬。
So what kind of cupcake did you make?
你做了什么样的小蛋糕?
I did a red velvet cupcake with American buttercream
我用美式奶油做了个红丝绒小蛋糕
with bananas and chocolate in it.
里面有香蕉和巧克力。
Mmm. Mmm. That's tasty.
嗯。嗯。这是美味的。
It is tasty. Thank you.
它很好吃。谢谢你！
Are you surprised?
你感到惊讶吗?
I think so, yeah.
我想是的。
Well, I got to tell you, I love the way the banana
我得告诉你，我喜欢香蕉的样子
and the chocolate meld together.
巧克力就会融合在一起。
Thank you. Yeah, you know what this tastes like?
谢谢你！你知道这是什么味道吗?
A banana split.
香蕉劈开。
Yeah! You know? Really good.
是啊!你知道吗?真的很好。
Good job. Okay. Bye.
好工作。好吧。再见。
Justice, what did you make for us today?
法官，你今天为我们做了什么?
I made vanilla cupcakes with caramel buttercream,
我用焦糖奶油做了香草小蛋糕，
with deep-fried apples
油炸苹果
and a little caramel ball on top.
再在上面放一点焦糖球。
Your buttercream separated a little bit.
你的奶油有点分开了。
You know, it looks like it broke.
你知道，它看起来像坏了。
But the colors are really nice, you know.
但是颜色真的很漂亮。
I think the pink and blue is really cool-looking.
我觉得粉色和蓝色看起来很酷。
What was your inspiration here?
你的灵感是什么?
My inspiration was just kind of, like, fun at the fair,
我的灵感就是，在集市上找点乐子，
and maybe it got a little hot at the fair, so...
也许集市上太热了，所以…
And it was windy. And things went wild.
而且风很大。事情变得疯狂起来。
That's fun.
这是有趣的。
Whoa. Really moist.
哇。很潮湿。
It's saying "caramel apple" to me.
它在对我说“焦糖苹果”。
This is awesome. Mm-hmm.
这太棒了。嗯哼。
Thank you. It's delicious.
谢谢你！它是美味的。
Mmm! Like, seriously, really good.
嗯!说真的，真的很好。
Which is great, because that buttercream is ugly.
这很好，因为奶油很丑。
Yeah. You pulled it out with the flavor.
是的。你带着味道把它拔出来了。
Yeah. Thanks, Justice.
是的。谢谢,正义。
Bye.
再见。
Hello. Kaniyah, how's it going?
你好。Kaniyah，最近怎么样?
Hi.
嗨。
A little eh.
有点，嗯。
You had a little meltdown.
你有点崩溃。
Yes.
是的。
But you kept going.
但你还是坚持了下来。
And you didn't let it phase you.
你没有让它影响你。
That is really impressive. Thank you.
真是令人印象深刻。谢谢你！
So what kind of cupcake did you make?
你做了什么样的小蛋糕?
I made a vanilla bean kettle corn cupcake
我做了个香草豆爆米花小蛋糕
with a vanilla bean buttercream with marshmallows.
香草豆奶油和棉花糖。
That is gorgeous and fluffy.
这是华丽和蓬松的。
It looks moist.
它看起来很潮湿。
The ratio of cupcake to frosting looks perfect.
蛋糕和糖霜的比例看起来很完美。
Yeah.
是的。
Mmm. Oh, my goodness, Kaniyah.
嗯。哦，我的天哪，Kaniyah。
That is a good cupcake.
那是一个很好的纸杯蛋糕。
I think you can probably tone the sugar down a little bit.
我觉得你可以少放点糖。
Really? Yeah, I think it's a little too sweet.
真的吗?是啊，我觉得有点太甜了。
I love it. And the crunch of the kettle corn
我喜欢它。还有爆米花的嘎吱声
is really kind of fun.
真的很有趣。
You hit it out of the park.
你打得太棒了。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
It's good.
很好。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Thanks a lot, Kaniyah. Thank you.
非常感谢，Kaniyah。谢谢你！
You're welcome.
不客气
KEILI: I feel nervous
凯莉:我感到紧张
because, are they gonna like the decoration?
因为，他们会喜欢这里的装饰吗?
I don't know what they're gonna think.
我不知道他们会怎么想。
What made you do this?
你为什么要这么做?
Well, I just decided to personalize the cupcakes.
我刚决定把小蛋糕个性化。
Keili, flattery will you get everywhere.
凯里，奉承会让你无处不在。
Everywhere.
无处不在。
What did you make for us today?
你今天为我们做了什么?
A vanilla tie-dye cupcake
香草扎染小蛋糕
with chocolate cookie buttercream
加上巧克力曲奇奶油
and sugar-dusted fried pretzel in the inside
里面还有撒了糖的油炸脆饼
and on top.
在上面。
I like the pretzel.
我喜欢椒盐卷饼。
But I think you could've crushed it up a little.
但我觉得你可以把它压碎一点。
That way, you would get, like, a bite of pretzel
那样的话，你就能吃一口椒盐卷饼了
with every bite. Okay.
每一口。好吧。
It's a really moist, delicious cupcake.
这是一个非常湿润、美味的小蛋糕。
It's just a really odd color.
只是颜色很奇怪。
I know. I think over-dyed it a bit.
我知道。我觉得有点染过头了。
Was it chocolate? No.
是巧克力吗?不。
Maybe our eyes are playing tricks on us
也许是我们的眼睛在捉弄我们
because it looks like it's chocolate.
因为它看起来像巧克力。
But it tastes good.
但是味道很好。
You know what? When purple gets caramelized,
你知道吗?当紫色被焦糖化时，
it gets really dark really fast.
天黑得很快。
So then it looks like chocolate. Oh!
所以它看起来像巧克力。哦!
All right. Keili, thank you so much.
好吧。凯丽，非常感谢你。
Thank you.
谢谢你！谢谢你！
See ya. Bye.
再见。再见。
All right, Maya. Why don't you give us the rundown
好吧，玛雅。你给我们简要介绍一下吧
on your carnival cupcake?
在你的嘉年华小蛋糕上?
What did you make? I made a vanilla cupcake
你做了什么?我做了一个香草小蛋糕
with a churro piece in the middle.
中间放一块油条。
I dyed each one the color the rainbow.
我把它们都染成了彩虹的颜色。
And there's vanilla whipped cream
还有香草生奶油
with churro pieces on the top.
上面放着油条。
I wanna see the inside of the cupcake.
我想看看小蛋糕的内部。
Look at all those pretty colors.
看看这些漂亮的颜色。
That's so pretty!
太漂亮了!
That's tasty.
这是美味的。
You can kind of taste that cinammony flavor. Mm-hmm.
你可以尝出肉桂的味道。嗯哼。
I think maybe you might've
我觉得你可能
beat the batter a little too long
把面糊打得太久了
because I think your cupcake got a little tough.
我觉得你的小蛋糕太硬了。
What kind of frosting is this?
这是什么糖霜?
Whipped cream. Okay.
鲜奶油。好吧。
I would've maybe liked something more frosting-y.
我可能会喜欢更有糖霜味的东西。
Yeah. Well, thank you, Maya.
是的。谢谢你，玛雅。
Thank you. Thanks, Maya.
谢谢你！谢谢你,玛雅。
Okay, Jason, what did you make for us today?
好吧，杰森，你今天给我们做了什么?
I made a tie-dyed cupcake
我做了一个扎染小蛋糕
with the traditional colors of the fair.
用集市的传统颜色。
And I had cotton candy as the twist.
我还用棉花糖来做道具。
I like your cupcakes. They look like little aliens.
我喜欢你的小蛋糕。他们看起来像小外星人。
Take me to your leader.
带我去见你们的首领。
They're really cute.
它们真的很可爱。
But, you know, there's one thing I think you're missing.
但是，我觉得你漏掉了一件事。
I think I'm missing the same thing.
我想我错过了同样的东西。
Frosting. I know.
结霜。我知道。
I wanted to put frosting on there.
我想在上面涂上糖霜。
But the frosting makes cotton candy melt.
但是糖霜会让棉花糖融化。
But cupcakes are all about frosting.
但纸杯蛋糕的关键是糖霜。
I know.
我知道。
Yeah, I completely agree.
是的，我完全同意。
You need frosting.
你需要加糖霜。
You need frosting!
你需要糖霜!
Are you trying to use the force?
你想动用武力吗?
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I think I did pretty good with the tie-dye part.
我觉得我扎染的部分做得很好。
Oh, look at that. It is red, white, and blue.
哦，看那个。它是红色、白色和蓝色的。
Mmm. That's a really good cupcake.
嗯。这个小蛋糕真的很好吃。
But as moist as it is, it tastes a little dry
虽然它很湿润，但尝起来有点干
because you don't have the frosting to play with it.
因为你没有糖霜来玩它。
Yeah. Jason, thanks so much.
是的。杰森，非常感谢。
Bye.
再见。
I'm worried.
我很担心你。
I really do not want to go home
我真的不想回家
on the first challenge.
第一次挑战。
That's a lot of kids.
那可是很多孩子啊。
Handsome bunch.
英俊的群。
Thank you, I know.
谢谢，我知道。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Bakers, most of you created some incredible cupcakes.
面包师们，你们大多数人都做了很棒的小蛋糕。
But three of you in particular
尤其是你们三个
delivered the excitement and flavors of a carnival.
传递了狂欢节的兴奋和味道。
Reese, you chose to do red velvet cupcakes
里斯，你选择做红丝绒小蛋糕
that went so well with chocolate-covered bananas.
巧克力香蕉太好吃了。
Justice, you made an awesome, moist vanilla cupcake.
贾斯蒂斯，你做了个美味的香草小蛋糕。
And it really said "caramel apple."
上面确实写着“焦糖苹果”。
Kaniyah, your vanilla kettle corn cupcakes
Kaniyah，你的香草玉米小蛋糕
were really pretty.
我们真的很漂亮。
And the use of your kettle corn was right on.
你的爆米花的用处也很好。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
But one baker's cupcakes
但是一个面包师的小蛋糕
took our taste buds for a thrill ride.
带着我们的味蕾来了一场刺激之旅。
I bet you guys wanna know who it is, don't you?
我猜你们肯定想知道是谁，对吧?
Yeah! Please!
是啊!拜托!
That baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Kaniyah!
…Kaniyah !
[ All cheering ]
[众人欢呼]
Yes!
是的!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
耶!耶!耶!
Kaniyah, great job. Thank you.
Kaniyah，干得好。谢谢你！
The following bakers took us
下面的面包师带我们去了
on a little bit more of a roller coaster ride.
就像坐过山车一样。
But in the end, your carnival creations
但最终，你的狂欢作品
are good enough to keep you safe.
足以保证你的安全。
And those bakers are Cole...
那些面包师是科尔…
...Maya...
玛雅…
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
...Aidan...
艾丹…
Ah!
啊!
...Keili...
Keili…
Yeah. Good job.
是的。好工作。
...Dylin...
Dylin…
and...
和…
...Audra.
Audra。
Yes! Oh, my gosh.
是的!哦，我的天啊。
Sorry for that reaction. But I'm so happy.
很抱歉刚才的反应。但是我很高兴。
Unfortunately, that leaves Jason,
不幸的是，杰森，
Charlotte, and Brooke.
夏洛特和布鲁克。
Please step forward, guys.
请往前走，伙计们。
All of your cupcakes were more like a fun-house mirror.
你做的小蛋糕更像一面镜子。
They were cool. But something was a little off.
他们很酷。但有些地方有点不对劲。
Jason, we're not even sure
杰森，我们都不确定
if we can call your cupcake a cupcake.
如果我们能把你的小蛋糕叫做小蛋糕的话。
It had no frosting.
它没有结霜。
That's a muffin.
那是松饼。
Brooke, your lemon cupcake with pretzel crumble
布鲁克，你的柠檬小蛋糕配椒盐脆饼
had undermixed frosting.
没有混合的糖霜。
And it could've used more time in the oven.
它本可以在烤箱里多烤一段时间。
Charlotte, your orange cupcake didn't have frosting.
夏洛特，你的橙色小蛋糕没有糖霜。
It had a thin layer of what you called glaze
它有一层薄薄的你称之为釉的东西
on top of a very short cupcake.
放在很短的小蛋糕上。
I just need one more chance.
我只需要再一次机会。
This is never easy.
这从来都不容易。
But this is a competition.
但这是一场比赛。
The baker that will be leaving us today is...
今天要离开我们的面包师是…
...Brooke.
布鲁克。
Aw, no.
哦,不。
Brooke, I'm sorry.
布鲁克，我很抱歉。
We really enjoyed meeting you
我们很高兴见到你
and watching you dance your way around the kitchen.
看着你在厨房里跳舞。
Just stay adorable, sweetie.
保持可爱就好，亲爱的。
I'm proud of what I did.
我为我所做的感到骄傲。
Bye.
再见。
This isn't the end of the road for me.
对我来说，这不是人生的终点。
I'm only 9.
我只有9岁。
I've got a lot of baking ahead of me.
我还有很多烘焙的事要做。
#ThisWeekWasCrazy.
# ThisWeekWasCrazy。
VALERIE: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
瓦莱丽:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
Your first big bake!
你的第一个大蛋糕!
I didn't think this would ever be happening.
我从没想过会发生这种事。
It's real.
这是真实的。
One dozen cupcakes with a carnival treat.
一打纸杯蛋糕加上狂欢节大餐。
Kettle corn for Kaniyah.
Kaniyah的爆米花。
Oh, my goodness. That is gorgeous.
哦，我的天哪。太棒了。
One baker really met the challenge --
有一个面包师真的遇到了挑战
Kaniyah! -Congratulations!
Kaniyah !祝贺你!
Charlotte's frosting looks really, really thin.
夏洛特的糖霜看起来真的很薄。
Jason, your cupcake had no frosting.
杰森，你的小蛋糕没有糖霜。
That's a muffin.
那是松饼。
Ah, no! Ugh.
啊,不!啊。
The baker leaving us today is Brooke.
今天离开的面包师是布鲁克。
Oh!
哦!
-Oh, wow! -What is this?
-哦,哇!-这是什么?
I'm worried.
我很担心你。
Hello, bakers!
你好,面包师!
-Yeah. -[ Gasps ]
-是的。——[喘息]
-Hey, bakers! -No!
-嘿,面包师!-不!
No, no, no!
不，不，不!
DUFF: Okay, I've combined two of my favorite things,
达夫:好吧，我把我最喜欢的两样东西结合在一起，
cake and volcanoes.
蛋糕和火山。
-Oh. -Uh-oh.
-哦。啊哦。
What do you think?
你觉得呢?
I'm excited and nervous at the same time.
我既兴奋又紧张。
Right. You should be.
正确的。你应该这样。
You have two hours...
你有两个小时……
-Oh, God. -Oh, gosh!
-哦,上帝。-哦,天哪!
...to make a volcano Bundt cake.
…做一个火山蛋糕
You're going to take a big Bundt cake
你要吃一个大的邦特蛋糕
and put a small Bundt cake on top.
在上面放一个小蛋糕。
Make it look like a volcano.
让它看起来像一座火山。
And when you present it, it better be smoking.
当你展示它的时候，它最好是冒烟的。
-Boom! -Uh...
繁荣!-嗯……
Hey, man.
嘿,男人。
No one said $25,000 was supposed to be easy.
没人说两万五千美元是件容易的事。
But it wasn't supposed to be this hard!
但没想到会这么难!
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
And your time starts...
你的时间开始了……
BOTH: ...now!
两种:…现在!
BOY: I don't even know what I'm getting.
男孩:我甚至不知道我得到了什么。
I guess flour. -This is so crazy!
我猜是面粉。-这太疯狂了!
-That was nuts. -Go, go, go, go!
-那太疯狂了。-快，快，快，快!
I want that volcano to be smoking!
我要那座火山冒着烟!
Smoking hot.
吸烟热。
I'm so happy we get to make volcano cakes
我很高兴我们能做火山蛋糕
because I've made one before.
因为我以前做过一次。
Volcano cakes are made by creating your cake
火山蛋糕是通过制作你的蛋糕来制作的
and hollowing out the center to put dry ice and water in
把中间挖空，放入干冰和水
so it smokes just like a volcano.
所以它像火山一样冒烟。
I'm making a chocolate-cinnamon cake
我在做巧克力肉桂蛋糕
with a chocolate-covered strawberry buttercream.
还有巧克力草莓奶油。
Great, tastes just like a chocolate-covered strawberry.
太棒了，尝起来就像巧克力草莓。
I make this cake all the time. It's one of my favorite cakes.
我经常做这个蛋糕。这是我最喜欢的蛋糕之一。
And I can make it in my sleep.
我睡觉的时候都能做到。
Safety first.
安全第一。
These cakes take a while to bake.
这些蛋糕要烤一段时间。
So I need to get them in the oven fast.
所以我得快点把它们放进烤箱。
You know, you sort of remind me of a volcano.
你知道吗，你让我想起了火山。
-Really? Why? -You're full of hot air.
-真的?为什么?-你满口空话。
Here comes the eruption of all the volcano puns.
所有的火山双关语都爆发了。
Really? 'Cause I lava you.
真的吗?因为我爱你。
-Oh, God. -Oh.
-哦,上帝。-哦。
Usually when you get a lava cake,
通常当你得到熔岩蛋糕时，
it's usually a chocolate.
通常是巧克力。
So I'm going to be making
所以我要做
a chocolate cake with chocolate ganache.
巧克力蛋糕加巧克力甘纳许。
Chocolate!
巧克力!
After I get the cakes in the oven,
等我把蛋糕放进烤箱，
I start up on my ganache.
我开始吃巧克力酱。
I heat up the heavy cream,
我加热浓奶油，
then pour it into the chocolate chips.
然后倒进巧克力片里。
And once it's been sitting for a few minutes, I mix it up.
等它静置几分钟后，我把它搅拌一下。
And there you go.
好了。
You have a ganache.
你有一块巧克力酱。
Chocolate!
巧克力!
Making ganache.
制作巧克力酱。
Looks good.
看起来不错。
Normally, a volcano erupts by its subduction zone,
通常情况下，火山是从俯冲带喷发的，
where one plate is going under the other plate.
一个板块在另一个板块下面。
Volcanoes have both geology and weather.
火山既有地质特征又有气候特征。
And I'm into both of those things.
这两件事我都喜欢。
I'm making a raspberry sour cream Bundt cake
我在做覆盆子酸奶油蛋糕
with a raspberry buttercream
还有覆盆子奶油
because raspberry, of course,
因为覆盆子，
definitely complements raspberry.
绝对是树莓的补充。
And raspberry is one of my favorite flavors.
覆盆子是我最喜欢的口味之一。
-Cool. -Hey.
很酷的。-嘿。
-Hi. -How you doin'?
-你好。-你好吗?
-Good.
改善情况。改善情况。
I think it's really smart to know
我觉得知道这一点很明智
what everyone else is baking
别人都在烤什么
because you got to know what you're up against.
因为你得知道你面对的是什么。
What are you doing, Cole?
你在干什么，科尔?
Chocolate cake with lava rocks.
熔岩巧克力蛋糕。
Wow.
哇。
It's only two hours. You got to cook two cakes.
只有两个小时。你得做两个蛋糕。
And then you have to shape it.
然后你要塑造它。
And then you have to decorate it.
然后你还要装饰它。
So you would think it would be easy,
所以你会认为这很简单，
but really not so much.
但实际上并没有那么多。
I have never made a volcano cake before.
我以前从来没有做过火山蛋糕。
But it can't be that hard.
但这并没有那么难。
How hard can it be to make a Bundt cake and frost it
做一个邦特蛋糕并给它上糖霜能有多难
and make it look exactly like a volcano?
让它看起来像一座火山?
I mean, really, how hard can all of that be?
我是说，真的，这一切能有多难?
I've seen a volcano in, uh, real life.
我在现实生活中见过火山。
And I go to Hawaii about once every year.
我大约每年去一次夏威夷。
So I see it. I've been to a volcano park.
所以我看到了。我去过火山公园。
And I've walked over volcanoes.
我还走过火山。
And I feel really confident.
我感到非常自信。
I'm making a lemon Bundt cake
我在做柠檬蛋糕
with a chocolate ganache frosting
加上巧克力甘纳许糖霜
and a buttercream lava.
还有奶油熔岩。
And it tastes pretty good because it's, like, a dark,
味道很好，因为它是一种黑色的，
rich flavor against this tart flavor of lemon.
浓郁的味道与柠檬的酸味相得益彰。
I put everything in. And I made sure I covered it
我把所有东西都放进去了。我确保我掩盖了它
with a towel because there was a lot of stuff inside my bowl.
用毛巾，因为我的碗里有很多东西。
I don't want anything to go flying.
我不想让任何东西飞起来。
That's a good way to make sure that nobody sees what I'm doing.
这是确保没人看到我在做什么的好方法。
[ Maya sighs ]
[玛雅叹气]
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
I'm doing the basic sour cream vanilla...
我在做最基本的酸奶油香草…
-Ah. -...Bundt cake.
——啊。-…一盘蛋糕。
Just gonna build off that in decoration.
就在装饰的基础上。
Just really weirded out by this volcano.
只是被这座火山吓到了。
Anyone could really make cupcakes.
人人都能做纸杯蛋糕。
But a volcano cake that explodes
而是一个会爆炸的火山蛋糕
and then it, like, looks like it, that takes skill.
然后，看起来，这需要技巧。
I can do this.
我能做到。我能做到。
I can do this, totally do this.
我能做到，完全能做到。
I am making a vanilla sour cream Bundt cake
我在做香草酸奶油蛋糕
with a vanilla buttercream.
加香草奶油。
The sour cream is gonna make this cake really moist.
酸奶油会让蛋糕变得非常湿润。
That's good.
这很好。
30 minutes gone, 90 minutes left.
30分钟过去了，还有90分钟。
-Oh, my God. -30 minutes already?
-我的天啊。-已经30分钟了?
Give us a volcano cake that is worthy
给我们一个有价值的火山蛋糕
of "Kids Baking Championship."
"儿童烘焙锦标赛"的冠军
Passion fruit, that smells good.
百香果，闻起来很香。
When I think of volcanoes, I think of lava erupting.
当我想到火山时，我想到的是熔岩喷发。
And I think of a tropical place.
我想到了一个热带的地方。
So I'm making a passion fruit volcano cake
所以我要做百香果火山蛋糕
with a banana buttercream.
配上香蕉奶油。
I'm making a very basic yellow cake.
我在做一个非常简单的黄色蛋糕。
It's, like, cake flour, eggs,
像是蛋糕粉，鸡蛋，
butter, sugar, buttermilk.
黄油，糖，白脱牛奶。
But I'm going to add
但是我要补充一下
about 2 cups of passion fruit puree.
大约两杯百香果泥。
That smells good.
闻起来好香。
I've never actually baked with passion fruit.
我从来没有用百香果做过烘焙。
But I bet this will turn out well.
但我打赌结果会很好。
All righty then.
那好吧。
Now to get these baked off.
现在把它们烤熟。
There's an actual volcano that's building more land
有一座真正的火山正在造出更多的土地
in Hawaii right now, isn't there?
在夏威夷，不是吗?
-Yeah.
-是的。-是的。
Reach the water. -Buy real estate yet?
够到水。-买房地产了吗?
Want to get in while it's hot.
想趁热进去。
KANIYAH: One of my favorite ingredients is strawberries.
我最喜欢的食材之一是草莓。
I am making a strawberry cake
我正在做草莓蛋糕
and a chocolate flake buttercream.
再来一份巧克力奶油。
I'm macerating my strawberries
我在泡草莓
so that they can go in my cake.
这样它们就可以放进我的蛋糕里了。
I bake for my family a lot of the time.
我经常给家人烤面包。
And they love my strawberry cakes.
他们喜欢我的草莓蛋糕。
My daddy, he's always like, "Whoa, that's good!
我爸爸，他总是说，“哇，太棒了!
Strawberries!"
草莓!”
I've never made volcano cake before.
我从来没做过火山蛋糕。
But I have made one in science class.
但我在科学课上做过一个。
I'm gonna bake a vanilla-flavored Bundt cake.
我要烤一个香草味的邦特蛋糕。
And I hope it looks like a volcano.
我希望它看起来像一座火山。
I hope.
我希望。
You get to carve your cake.
你可以切你的蛋糕。
That'll be cool.
那太酷了。
9,000 pounds of batter right here.
这里有9000磅的面糊。
-Reese! -Hi, Reese! -Hello.
瑞茜!-你好,瑞茜!-你好。
-What's going on in here? -Are you on your icing?
-这是怎么回事?-你吃糖霜了吗?
Yeah, I'm making an American buttercream icing.
我在做美式奶油糖霜。
-Awesome. -For what flavor cake?
太棒了。-什么口味的蛋糕?
-Vanilla Bundt cakes. -Mm.
-香草蛋糕。毫米。
Reese, where'd you learn how to bake?
里斯，你从哪学的烘焙?
-My mom. -Is your mom a baker?
——我的妈妈。-你妈妈是面包师吗?
-Yes. -What's her specialty?
-是的。她的专长是什么?
-Sculpted cakes. -Sculpted cakes?
雕刻蛋糕。雕刻蛋糕吗?
My mom owns a bakery.
我妈妈开了一家面包店。
And that's how I learned to bake.
我就是这样学会烘焙的。
And that's where I hang out.
那就是我常去的地方。
I have seen her make millions of sculpted cakes.
我见过她做过无数的雕刻蛋糕。
She's made dogs, purses.
她做过狗，做过钱包。
So they thought she was selling purses once.
所以他们以为她曾经卖过钱包。
If your mom does sculpted cakes,
如果你妈妈做雕刻蛋糕，
I bet she wants you to do a good job.
我打赌她一定希望你干得好。
-Yeah. -All right.
-是的。-好的。
-Represent. -Good luck.
质点。好的运气。
Okay.
好吧。
This is taking forever.
这要花很长时间。
The cake flavor of my volcano cake
我的火山蛋糕的味道
is gonna be, wait for it, ginger.
会是，等等，金吉。
My batter is flour, salt,
我的面糊是面粉，盐
baking powder and ginger.
发酵粉和姜。
I start mixing together my eggs and my sugar.
我开始搅拌鸡蛋和糖。
Then once that's done,
一旦完成，
I'll add in the vanilla and the Greek yogurt.
我要加入香草和希腊酸奶。
And then once that's fully incorporated,
一旦完全混合，
I gradually mix in my oil.
我逐渐加入油。
So the Greek yogurt is gonna give me moisture
希腊酸奶会给我带来水分
and a nice tang.
味道很浓。
That looks good.
看起来不错。
Done.
完成了。
DUFF: One hour left, bakers.
达夫:还有一个小时，面包师们。
We are not just looking for a volcano.
我们不只是在找火山。
VALERIE: We would love to see,
瓦莱丽:我们很乐意看到，
and must see, an active volcano.
而且一定要看，一座活火山。
Cool.
酷。
Cole already put his cakes in the blast chiller.
科尔已经把蛋糕放进冷冻机了。
He's not fooling around.
他不是在胡闹。
AIDAN: Do you have your batter in the oven?
艾丹:你的面糊在烤箱里了吗?
No.
不。
Oh, you probably want to get that in soon.
你可能想快点把它放进去。
Yeah, I'm just about -- I'm almost done.
是啊，我就，我就快做完了。
-Hey, Audra. -Hey.
-嘿,Audra。-嘿。
What you doin'?
你在干什么?
I am making a raspberry Bundt cake.
我在做覆盆子蛋糕。
But it's going to be a sour cream flavor, too.
但它也会有酸奶油的味道。
-Mm. -Oh. That sounds delicious.
毫米。-哦。听起来很好吃。
-Nice and moist. -You are so cute.
-又好又湿。-你太可爱了。
You need to have your own animated show.
你需要有自己的动画节目。
Yay.
耶。
Did you see the light bulb go on?
你看到灯泡亮了吗?
I saw it. -That's so cute.
我看到了。-太可爱了。
All right. Have fun.
好吧。玩得开心。
We'll get out of your way. -Good luck, Audra.
我们会给你让路的。-祝你好运，奥德拉。
Get those cakes in the oven.
把蛋糕放进烤箱。
I add about 3 tablespoons
我加了大约3汤匙
of raspberry puree to my cake batter.
覆盆子泥和蛋糕面糊。
I'm hoping that that's enough raspberry flavor to it.
我希望有足够的覆盆子味。
KID: Oh, no.
孩子:哦，不。
Why do I have to carry this thing?
为什么要我拿着这个?
-Oh, no. -All right.
-哦,不。-好的。
Bakers, listen up.
面包师们，听好了。
Bakers, smoke and ash and lava aren't the only things
面包师、烟雾、灰烬和熔岩并不是唯一的东西
that spew out of a volcano.
那是从火山喷出的。
I'm scared.
我很害怕。
You also get rocks and boulders.
你也可以看到岩石和巨石。
You have to bake at least four edible boulders...
你至少要烤四块可食用的巨石…
[ Gasps ]
[喘息]
...to go along with your volcano.
…和你的火山一起。
-How are we gonna... -Duff, I hate you.
-我们要怎么…-达夫，我恨你。
Did you -- did you take all the fondant?
你把糖都拿走了吗?
-No!
-不!-不!
AUDRA: I'm running out of time.
我快没时间了。
I'm already doing so badly on time.
我在时间上已经做得很差了。
And now I have to make another thing.
现在我要做另一个东西。
This is the worst challenge ever.
这是有史以来最糟糕的挑战。
DUFF: 45 minutes left, bakers.
达夫:还有45分钟，面包师们。
You have to bake at least four edible boulders
你至少要烤四块可食用的巨石
to go along with your volcano.
和你的火山一起。
-I'm getting, like... -Can I get some fondant?
-我在…能给我点糖吗?
This is the worst challenge ever.
这是有史以来最糟糕的挑战。
I just put my cakes in the oven.
我刚把蛋糕放进烤箱。
And now I have another thing to add to my list.
现在我的清单上又多了一件事。
I'm totally running out of time.
我快没时间了。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
DYLIN: I need the airbrush.
迪琳:我需要喷枪。
Dude, what are you looking for to do the boulders?
伙计，你在巨石上找什么?
I don't know what to do with the boulders.
我不知道该怎么处理这些巨石。
Boulders? No one has time for boulders.
巨石?没人有时间玩巨石。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Then I see rice cereal.
然后我看到了米粥。
Marshmallows! I see marshmallows.
棉花糖!我看到棉花糖了。
Yay! To make my boulders,
耶!为了做我的巨石，
I'm gonna use rice cereal treats.
我要用米粉做点心。
Oh, my gosh. Look at my pot.
哦，我的天啊。看我的锅。
I'm pretty much mimicking you.
我在模仿你。
I hope your recipe tastes good because I'm using it, too.
我希望你的食谱味道不错，因为我也在用。
Mine is melting good.
我的熔化得很好。
Me and Dylin are making the same thing, rice cereal treats.
我和迪林也在做同样的东西，米粉点心。
But I think that's okay. They're still different.
不过我觉得没关系。它们还是不同的。
DYLIN: Thanks for letting me steal your idea, Reese.
谢谢你让我窃取你的想法，里斯。
That's okay.
没关系。
I add my rice cereal
我加入我的米粥
to my melted marshmallows and start to stir quickly.
加入融化的棉花糖，开始快速搅拌。
I'm gonna make my boulders big.
我要把我的巨石做大。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
Look at the size of Reese's boulders!
看看里斯的巨石有多大!
DUFF: They're bigger than him.
达夫:它们比他还大。
I think he thought that the boulder that I brought out,
我想他以为我拿出来的巨石，
he actually needed to make them that size.
他确实需要把它们做成那样的尺寸。
Yeah.
是的。
Mine are going to be about this big.
我的大概有这么大。
DYLIN: Whoa!
DYLIN:哇!
My boulders are going to be way smaller than that.
我的巨石要比它小得多。
I checked the cakes. And the cakes are done.
我检查了蛋糕。蛋糕做好了。
So for my boulders, I start to use the cake.
所以我开始用蛋糕做巨石
And I roll it up into a ball form.
我把它卷成球状。
And I start to mush it together.
我开始把它们搅在一起。
And then I wrap my nice, thin fondant
然后把软糖包好
around the cake balls
围绕着蛋糕球
to make sure that they're nice and secure.
确保它们完好无损。
Justice, is that, uh... What is that, igneous rock,
正义，是指…那是什么，火成岩，
or sedimentary rock or...
或者沉积岩或者……
It's definitely not sedimentary
它绝对不是沉积的
because sedimentary is mostly in areas
因为沉积主要是在区域内
that are flat. -Okay.
那是平的。-好的。
It's probably volcanic ash.
可能是火山灰。
If this is volcano eruption,
如果这是火山喷发
it's, like, all these particles go into the air.
就像，所有的微粒都进入了空气。
And the wind just pushes it.
风就会推动它。
And then they, like, rub against each other.
然后他们就会互相摩擦。
Like, in real thunderstorms,
比如，在真正的雷暴中，
the ice particles rub against each other.
冰粒相互摩擦。
And the static electricity makes lightning.
静电产生闪电。
JASON: Time to melt some more chocolate.
杰森:是时候再融化一些巧克力了。
For my boulders... Hot.
为了我的巨石……热。
...I melt down some chocolate on a double boiler
…我用双层锅融化巧克力
and pour them into the molds
把它们倒进模具里
after I get them out of the blast chiller...
等我把他们从冷冻机里拿出来
Ooh.
哦。
...and wrap the chocolate in fondant.
…把巧克力裹在软糖里。
When they bite into it, they'll have a surprise,
当它们咬进去的时候，会有一个惊喜，
a chocolaty surprise.
巧克力的惊喜。
Boulder.
博尔德。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm deciding to make boulders two different ways.
我决定用两种不同的方法做巨石。
For my first way, it's gonna be black
我的第一种方式，是黑色的
and white fondant mixed together.
和白色方糖混合在一起。
And then for my second way, it's gonna be chocolate in the molds.
第二种方法，就是模具里的巧克力。
So this, I think,
所以我认为，
will really help my boulders stand out
真的能让我的巨石脱颖而出吗
from the other bakers' boulders.
从其他面包师的巨石。
KEILI: Holy moly!
凯莉:天哪!
For my boulders, I roll out my fondant.
做巨石的时候，我会擀出软糖。
And I shape it into little balls.
然后把它捏成小球。
And I added chocolate chips to give it that rough texture.
我还加了巧克力屑，让它有一种粗糙的质感。
It totally looks like a boulder.
它看起来就像一块大石头。
Those are my boulders.
那些是我的巨石。
My hands are disgusting.
我的手好恶心。
To make my boulders, I'm using black vanilla fondant
我用的是黑香草软糖
and chocolate flakes.
还有巧克力片。
I'm dipping my boulders inside the water
我把巨石浸在水里
so the flakes will stick.
所以薄片会粘在一起。
And it looks nice.
它看起来很漂亮。
Between you and me, you already know this about me.
悄悄告诉你，你已经知道我这一点了。
I am not happy about boulders
我不喜欢巨石
being made purely out of fondant.
完全由软糖制成。
DUFF: Fondant's beautiful.
达夫:方丹糖很漂亮。
I can make really awesome stuff with it.
我可以用它做出很棒的东西。
But, like, I feel like pure fondant's kind of a cop-out.
但是，我觉得纯方糖有点逃避现实。
Yeah, I mean, if you're going to put an edible boulder,
是啊，如果你要放一块可食用的巨石，
make it a palatable boulder.
让它成为一块美味的巨石。
-Mm-hmm. -You know?
-嗯。-你知道吗?
COLE: Boulders, when I think boulders,
科尔:巨石，当我想到巨石时，
I immediately think truffles
我马上想到了松露
because they're not perfect, just like rocks.
因为它们并不完美，就像石头一样。
I'm gonna make my edible boulders
我要做我的可食用巨石
out of chopped pecans and buttercream
用切碎的山核桃和奶油
and top them off with white chocolate and airbrush.
最后再涂上白巧克力和喷枪。
I love using the airbrush
我喜欢用喷枪
because it adds so much more detail.
因为它增加了很多细节。
And I'm pretty good at it.
我很擅长这个。
There we go.
好了。
Cream-filled chocolate cookies.
奶油夹心巧克力饼干。
I grab the chocolate sandwich cookies.
我拿起巧克力三明治饼干。
And I crush those up.
我把它们压碎。
And I add some heavy cream to them.
我在里面加了些奶油。
And then I separate it into four different rocks
然后我把它分成四块不同的石头
and put them in the blast chiller.
然后把它们放进冷冻机里。
Almost everyone has such good ideas for boulders.
几乎每个人对巨石都有这样的好主意。
And I'm still working on my frosting.
我还在做糖霜呢。
My boulders, I don't want to use fondant or gum paste
我的巨石，我不想用软糖或口香糖膏
because I don't consider those edible things.
因为我觉得那些东西不能吃。
I wouldn't eat them.
我不会吃的。
Cream-filled cookie boulders will have to work.
奶油填充的饼干巨石必须起作用。
And Audra's using cream-filled cookies and something else.
而奥德拉用的是奶油曲奇和其他东西。
So I think that I could make
所以我觉得我可以
some crushed up cream-filled cookies
一些压碎的奶油曲奇
with some icing.
加一些糖霜。
And those all go well together in my opinion.
在我看来，这些都很好地结合在一起。
They smell really good.
它们闻起来真香。
20 minutes, guys!
20分钟，伙计们!
Volcano cakes and edible boulders.
火山蛋糕和可食用的巨石。
I really want my cake to look like a volcano.
我真的希望我的蛋糕看起来像火山。
So I'm gonna take some white chocolate ganache,
所以我要拿一些白巧克力甘纳许，
and dye it red, orange and yellow
然后把它染成红色、橙色和黄色
and drizzle it on top for lava.
把它淋在上面，形成熔岩。
And it looks, like, good.
看起来还不错。
Hashtag blessed.
标签有福。
This will be the cutest volcano.
这将是最可爱的火山。
I haven't seen a volcano before.
我以前没见过火山。
But when my parents were married,
但当我父母结婚时，
they went on a honeymoon to Hawaii.
他们去夏威夷度蜜月了。
And then they told me all the different colors they saw.
然后他们告诉我他们看到的所有不同的颜色。
Purple and pink were the big colors.
紫色和粉红色是最主要的颜色。
It's much happier.
这样会快乐得多。
For my boulders, I have some extra buttercream
做巨石的时候，我多准备了一些奶油
and some coconut flakes.
还有一些椰子片。
And I rolled them up into a ball together.
我把它们一起卷成一个球。
Oh, my gosh. It's working.
哦，我的天啊。这是工作。
I covered 'em in gum paste
我用口香糖糊了它们
and used two chocolate-covered blue candies
用了两块蓝色的巧克力糖
to make it look like ashes just fell down on it.
让它看起来像是灰烬掉在上面。
And it's, like, really blue.
它真的很蓝。
You got 15 minutes left, bakers.
还有15分钟，面包师们。
Give us a volcano cake
给我们一个火山蛋糕
worthy of the "Kids Baking Championship."
配得上"儿童烘焙锦标赛"
Oh, no.
哦,不。
I stacked my Bundt cakes.
我把我的邦特蛋糕堆叠起来。
* No, no, no, no, no, no, no *
不不不不不不不不不
And it starts falling apart.
它开始分崩离析。
It's raw.
它是原始的。
I don't have enough time to make another cake.
我没有足够的时间再做一个蛋糕。
Ugh.
啊。
No.
不。
No-o-o-o-o.
No-o-o-o-o。
It's raw.
它是原始的。
You got 15 minutes left, bakers,
你们还剩15分钟，面包师们，
volcano cakes and edible boulders.
火山蛋糕和可食用的巨石。
I don't have enough time to make another cake.
我没有足够的时间再做一个蛋糕。
I'm going to throw this cake back into the oven
我要把蛋糕扔回烤箱里
and see if I can cook it until it's done.
看看能不能煮熟。
I'm just worried it won't be cooked in time.
我只是担心不能及时煮熟。
Ugh, has to be good enough.
嗯，必须足够好。
I cannot keep those in any longer.
我不能再把它们藏在心里了。
So I just take 'em out.
所以我就把它们拿出来。
And it's broken. It's broken.
它坏了。它坏了。
It's not fully cooked.
还没完全煮熟。
My volcano has, like, imploded.
我的火山喷发了。
This is trash.
这是垃圾。
I have a second cake. And I'm just wishing
我有第二块蛋糕。我只是希望
that my second cake
这是我的第二个蛋糕
doesn't crumble like the first
不会像第一个那样崩溃
or else I will have no cake to serve.
不然我就没有蛋糕吃了。
Oh, God. Oh, this is --
哦,上帝。哦，这是
this is falling a-- uh, it's broken.
这是坠落，它断了。
All right, bakers, can I have your attention for a sec?
好了，面包师们，能听我说几句吗?
I don't want your volcanoes to look like Bundt cakes.
我可不想让你的火山看起来像邦特蛋糕。
I want them to look like volcanoes.
我想让它们看起来像火山。
VALERIE: Cake is very moldable.
瓦莱丽:蛋糕很容易成型。
So don't worry if your cake didn't turn out perfectly.
所以，如果你的蛋糕做得不完美，也不用担心。
Mold it to the way you want it.
塑造成你想要的样子。
And volcanoes come in all different shapes
火山有各种各样的形状
and sizes, just like people.
大小，就像人一样。
Yep.
是的。
Let's go with the one-layer cake.
我们来做单层蛋糕吧。
I'm running out of time.
我快没时间了。
And I decide to just go with my small one.
我决定用我的小的。
I start pouring the ganache over the cake
我开始往蛋糕上倒巧克力酱
and then start decorating it with some red fondant.
然后开始用一些红色的方糖装饰它。
A little circle around it.
它周围有一个小圆圈。
CHARLOTTE: I decide to make cake balls out of my crumbled cake
夏洛特:我决定用我的碎蛋糕做蛋糕球
to help make up for the dent.
来弥补凹痕。
After that, I'm just, like, frost it quickly.
在那之后，我就把它迅速涂上霜。
Make all my decorations as quickly as possible.
尽快做好我所有的装饰品。
At least I know it came out.
至少我知道我说出来了。
I get my cake out of the oven. And it looks pretty good.
我把蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来。看起来很不错。
I would like to have a tall volcano.
我想要一座高大的火山。
So I get the idea
我明白了
to use my rice marshmallow treats
用我的大米棉花糖
to form them into a top layer.
使它们形成一个顶层。
I think it'll help me stand out.
我想这会让我脱颖而出。
It looks perfect.
看起来很完美。
For my decorations,
为了我的装饰，
I chose royal icing to dye and use as lava,
我选择了皇家糖衣来染色并用作熔岩，
which doesn't take too long
这不会花太长时间吗
except that it's super, super, super thin.
除了它超级，超级，超级薄。
Mine looks okay. -Look at mine.
我的看起来还行。-看看我的。
It's like the whole entire cake erupted.
好像整个蛋糕都裂开了。
-On TV, it looks so easy. -You know, and in real life,
-在电视上，看起来很容易。-你知道，在现实生活中
it's, like, ugh.
就像，呃。
DUFF: 10 minutes, bakers, you got 10 minutes,
10分钟，面包师们，你们有10分钟，
volcano cakes and edible boulders.
火山蛋糕和可食用的巨石。
AIDAN: There's just one thing I wanted to do.
艾丹:我只想做一件事。
But I don't know if I'm gonna have enough time.
但我不知道我是否有足够的时间。
I wanted to make isomalt fire.
我想用异麦芽糖生火。
Isomalt is a special type of sugar
异麦芽糖是一种特殊的糖
that when you melt it down, it does not turn brown.
当你把它融化的时候，它不会变成棕色。
And it can stand against humidity.
而且它可以抵抗潮湿。
I dye it red.
我把它染成红色。
And I pour it over my ice and let that cool.
我把它倒在冰块上，让它冷却。
And when I come back to it, I take it out.
当我回到它的时候，我把它拿出来。
And it looks so cool.
它看起来很酷。
Oh, my gosh!
哦，天哪!
Whoa. Aidan, that's awesome!
哇。艾登，太棒了!
It's gonna be my lava exploding out of the cake.
我的熔岩会从蛋糕里喷出来。
Okay, this looks the cutest.
好吧，这个看起来最可爱了。
My cake is going to be
我的蛋糕会是
the prettiest volcano in the room.
房间里最漂亮的火山。
The flowers will help it look Hawaii-y.
这些花会让它看起来像夏威夷。
I want to test that my dry-ice container can fit.
我想测试一下我的干冰容器能不能装下。
So I just put it in there.
所以我把它放在这里。
And it fits, which I'm so happy about.
而且很合身，我很高兴。
Yay! Okay.
耶!好吧。
Bakers now have to understand special effects.
面包师现在必须了解特效。
VALERIE: Well, then you've ruined baking for everybody.
瓦莱丽:那你就毁了大家的烘焙。
Literally my fault, literally my fault.
是我的错，是我的错。
It's all your fault.
都是你的错。
You can't just bake a three-tier cake anymore.
你不能再烤三层蛋糕了。
Like, "What? It doesn't move?
“什么?它不动?
It doesn't have a laser in it?"
里面没有激光吗?”
Five minutes left, bakers.
还有五分钟，面包师们。
Make me a volcano.
把我变成一座火山。
Make me some boulders.
给我弄些石头来。
And make it smoking!
让它冒烟!
I want to make my volcano look realistic.
我想让我的火山看起来更真实。
So I'm spray painting it black and gray.
所以我要把它喷成黑色和灰色。
It looks like a real volcano.
它看起来像一座真正的火山。
I'm doing the volcano dance.
我在跳火山舞。
* Da, da, da, da, da, da, da *
*达，达，达，达，达，达*
It's a volcano.
这是一座火山。
They're messy. They're sloppy.
他们是混乱。他们是草率的。
Things melt. They're hot.
东西融化。他们是热的。
They all look different.
它们看起来都不一样。
But what about a volcano cake?
那火山蛋糕呢?
I'm doing my finishing touches
我正在做最后的润色
by putting glitter on top for lava.
通过在熔岩顶部放亮片。
It's Mount Colesaur. It can have --
那是科尔索尔山。它可以——
anything can happen.
任何事情都有可能发生。
In my mind, I want a perfect volcano
在我心中，我想要一座完美的火山
on a perfect tropical island,
在一个完美的热带岛屿上
just for me.
就我一个人。
Perfect.
完美的。
Wow.
哇。
DUFF: One minute!
达夫:一分钟!
Final touches, make sure
最后的润色，确保
your volcanoes look like volcanoes,
你的火山看起来像火山，
which means melty and sloppy.
这意味着融化和草率。
AIDAN: You know, if Duff wants a messy volcano,
艾丹:你知道，如果达夫想要一个混乱的火山，
he's gonna get a messy volcano.
他会得到一个混乱的火山。
Man, you guys, I'm stoked about these volcanoes,
伙计们，我对这些火山很感兴趣，
they look awesome.
他们看起来棒极了。
AUDRA: Cream-filled chocolate cookies.
奶油夹心巧克力饼干。
Throwing stuff together and hope it's good.
把东西凑在一起，希望它是好的。
5...4...
5…4…
-3... -2...1...
3……1 2……
Hands up!
举起手来!
My cake is really short.
我的蛋糕真的很短。
And it looked more like a Bundt cake than a volcano.
它看起来更像一个蛋糕，而不是一座火山。
Not the best cake.
不是最好的蛋糕。
So we asked for volcanoes,
所以我们问火山，
smoking and boulders.
烟雾和巨石。
-Yep. -Edible.
是的。可食用的。
-Yes. -Are you ready for this?
-是的。你准备好了吗?
Audra!
Audra !
Hello!
你好!
This is our second time facing the judges.
这是我们第二次面对评委。
And you'd think it would get a little bit easier.
你可能会认为它会变得简单一些。
But it's just nerve-wracking.
但这很伤脑筋。
There's no really way to react -- relax.
没有办法做出反应，放松。
To be honest, it's not my best work.
老实说，这不是我最好的作品。
But I feel like it's a big step up from my cupcake.
但我觉得这比我的小蛋糕好多了。
Well, I want to fire it up.
我想把它点燃。
I want to see what it looks like smoking like a volcano.
我想看看冒烟的火山是什么样子。
Yeah! Let's see it.
是啊!让我们看看。
Oh, that was awesome.
哦，太棒了。
That volcano is angry.
那座火山生气了。
Probably from me frosting it with so much lava.
可能是因为我在上面撒了那么多熔岩。
I want to taste this cake. This is just too much fun.
我想尝尝这个蛋糕。这太有趣了。
It is a raspberry sour cream Bundt cake
这是覆盆子酸奶油蛋糕
with a plain vanilla frosting.
加上香草糖霜。
Here you go.
给你。
-Thank you very much, Audra. -Thank you, Audra.
-非常感谢，Audra。-谢谢你，奥德拉。
Uh-oh, Audra.
哦,Audra。
I think it's a little underbaked.
我觉得有点不成熟。
-It is. -A little raw right here.
——是。-这里有点生涩。
Well, you got an undercooked one.
你有个没煮熟的。
And mine tastes a little overcooked.
我的尝起来有点煮过头了。
Right in the middle, it's perfect.
就在中间，很完美。
Eat that middle then, okay?
把中间的吃了，好吗?
Drill -- drill it down the middle.
从中间往下钻。
Tell me about your boulders.
跟我说说你的巨石。
I made them with cream-filled chocolate sandwich cookies.
我用奶油夹心巧克力三明治饼干做的。
The boulder, I'm wondering
巨石，我在想
if it should have been baked or something
如果它应该烤一下什么的
because it just tastes like raw cookie dough.
因为它尝起来就像生曲奇饼。
It's less like a boulder and more like a mudslide.
它不太像巨石，更像泥石流。
-Thank you.
-谢谢。-谢谢。
Justice.
正义。
That's so fun!
太有趣了!
Justice, how does a volcano affect the weather?
法官大人，火山是如何影响天气的?
If it erupts, like, all the ash will go into the sky
如果火山爆发，所有的火山灰都会飞向天空
and block out the sun. Like, it happened once.
并遮挡阳光。就发生过一次。
"The year of no summer" is what they called it
他们称之为“无夏之年”
because it made everything so cold.
因为它让一切都变冷了。
-I love you, Justice. -It's amazing.
-我爱你，法官。——太神奇了。
I love science. What flavor cake is it?
我热爱科学。这是什么口味的蛋糕?
I made a raspberry cake with raspberry buttercream.
我用覆盆子奶油做了覆盆子蛋糕。
And for the boulders, I took cake scraps.
至于巨石，我用的是蛋糕屑。
And I molded them together and put fondant on top of it.
我把它们拼在一起，在上面放上软糖。
Justice, I really like the fact
正义，我真的很喜欢这个事实
that you used cake pops as your boulders.
你用棒棒糖蛋糕当石头。
Smart thinking. It doesn't look like you
聪明的想法。它看起来不像你
put too much fondant on there.
放太多软糖了。
Thank you. So it's all the same cake, yeah?
谢谢你！都是一样的蛋糕，对吧?
-Yeah. -Taste the raspberry.
-是的。-尝尝覆盆子。
Yeah, you do.
是的，你有。
I got good raspberry flavor in here.
这里有很好的覆盆子味。
I can really taste it.
我真的能尝到它的味道。
Um, but I think you probably
但我觉得你可能
could've pulled this out about 10 minutes earlier.
十分钟前就可以拔出来了。
-Okay. -Cake got a little bit dry
-好的。-蛋糕有点干
and a little bit torched on the bottom.
底部有点烧焦了。
Other than that, man, I really like your volcano.
除此之外，我真的很喜欢你的火山。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
It's nice because you went tropical.
很好，因为你去了热带。
You know, so you got palm trees on there.
你知道，你在那里种了棕榈树。
You got boulders. And I think it's good
你有巨石。我认为这很好
that you took the time to do the yellow and the red.
你花时间做了黄色和红色。
Great job. -Thank you.
伟大的工作。-谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
All right. You ready to call in Charlotte?
好吧。准备好叫夏洛特来了吗?
-Yes. -Charlotte!
-是的。夏洛特!
CHARLOTTE: I'm really nervous they're not gonna like my cake.
夏洛特:我真的很担心他们会不喜欢我的蛋糕。
I'm just like, ah, blegh.
我就想，啊，天哪。
Before we taste it, I think we should make it smoke.
在我们品尝之前，我想我们应该让它冒烟。
Okay.
好吧。
All right. Let's see it.
好吧。让我们看看。
Yeah. Look at that.
是的。看那个。
I've actually always wanted to do that.
其实我一直想这么做。
So I'm really excited.
所以我真的很兴奋。
Tell us all about your volcano.
跟我们说说你的火山吧。
It's a ginger cake with a chocolate frosting.
这是一个有巧克力糖霜的姜饼。
And the boulders are black and white chocolate and fondant.
这些巨石是黑白巧克力和软糖。
Charlotte, look.
夏洛特,看。
I dig your volcano. I think it looks good.
我喜欢你的火山。我觉得它看起来不错。
You know, you got some nice colors on there.
你知道吗，你身上的颜色很漂亮。
You got yellow. You got orange.
你是黄色的。你是橙色的。
I think it's a little short, though.
不过我觉得有点短。
It's a crumbling volcano because it's a very old volcano.
这是一座摇摇欲坠的火山，因为它是一座非常古老的火山。
Gotcha. Now, did you work on that story
明白了。那篇报道是你写的吗
after you made the volcano?
在你造了火山之后?
Um, I worked on the story after I made the cake.
我做完蛋糕后再写故事。
So...
所以…
Ginger and chocolate, I'm excited.
姜和巧克力，我很兴奋。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
I see raw bits.
我看到了未加工的部分。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
Okay, I'm really nervous.
好吧，我真的很紧张。
Hmm.
嗯。
Oh, I wonder if it's done all the way, Charlotte.
哦，我想知道是不是已经做完了，夏洛特。
Charlotte, you got -- your cake is very underbaked.
夏洛特，你的蛋糕还没烤好。
So ginger chocolate. Mm-hmm.
姜巧克力。嗯哼。
Mm.
毫米。
I don't think that's a good look on your face.
我觉得你脸上的表情不太好。
I'm nervous. -No, no.
我紧张。-不,没有。
Are you doing the nervous hand dance?
你在跳紧张的手舞吗?
Yeah. I'm ah, ah!
是的。我是啊，啊!
Hmm.
嗯。
Charlotte, your cake is very underbaked.
夏洛特，你的蛋糕烤得太烂了。
How long did you bake it for?
你烤了多长时间?
About 45 minutes.
大约45分钟。
This cake is 90% raw.
这个蛋糕90%是生的。
Duff, no offense,
达夫，无意冒犯，
but that is at least 50% baked.
但至少烤了一半。
Chocolate's good, though. I like your flavors.
不过巧克力也不错。我喜欢你的口味。
I think the frosting was really good.
我觉得糖霜真的很好吃。
But I would've liked the cake baked a little bit longer.
但我希望蛋糕烤得再久一点。
Okay.
好吧。
I don't taste much ginger, either.
我也尝不出姜的味道。
I can taste the chocolate.
我能尝到巧克力的味道。
Um, yeah, I'm really used to not putting too much ginger.
是的，我已经习惯不放太多姜了。
But if you're going to make a ginger cake...
但如果你要做姜饼……
Yeah.
是的。
...you got to have it ginger flavor.
…你一定要姜味的。
-Okay. Thank you. -Thanks, Charlotte.
-好的。谢谢你！-谢谢,夏洛特。
Maya?
玛雅?
I didn't see her there for a second.
我一秒钟都没看到她。
Yeah, where... Maya, you can come on out.
是的,…玛雅，你可以出来了。
Oh, there you are! -Oh, there you are!
哦，你来了!-你来了!
Yeah, she gets it all the time.
是啊，她总是被人骂。
She's done.
她所做的。
I think we should see
我想我们应该看看
what this volcano looks like when it smokes.
火山冒烟的时候是什么样子。
-Oh, it's so pretty! -If I was going
-噢，真漂亮!-如果我要去
to have to perish in a lava accident,
在熔岩事故中丧生，
I would much rather have, like,
我更希望，
happy pink lava than, like, angry red lava.
快乐的粉色熔岩比愤怒的红色熔岩要多。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
I have made, for you,
我为你做了，
a vanilla sour cream Bundt cake
香草酸奶油蛋糕
with a vanilla buttercream frosting.
加上香草奶油糖霜。
How did you make your boulders?
你是怎么做巨石的?
I put coconut flakes and buttercream
我放了椰子片和奶油
and then put gum paste over there.
然后把口香糖糊放在那里。
I taste the sour cream.
我尝了尝酸奶油。
And I do like that extra flavor in there.
我喜欢里面额外的味道。
It seems like it's a little overcooked.
看起来有点煮过头了。
It's not as moist as I would expect it to be.
它不像我想象的那么潮湿。
-Okay. -But it's good flavor.
-好的。-但味道不错。
I can taste the vanilla. I can taste it in your frosting.
我能尝到香草味。我能从你的糖霜里尝出来。
I can taste it in your cake.
我能从你的蛋糕里尝出来。
I love the coconut boulders...
我喜欢椰子巨石……
-Yeah, look at that. -...because I love coconut.
-是啊，看那个。-…因为我喜欢椰子。
I like the coconut in here.
我喜欢这里的椰子。
But I think you could've toasted it.
但我觉得你可以举杯庆祝一下。
Mm.
毫米。
Give you a lot more round flavor in there.
让它的味道更圆润。
Maya, great job. -Thank you.
玛雅，干得好。-谢谢。
-Thanks, Maya.
-谢谢。-谢谢,玛雅。
Hello, Dylin. Let's see if it smokes.
你好,Dylin。让我们看看它能不能冒烟。
Okay.
好吧。
Yes, look at that.
是的，看那个。
-I love it! -Yeah, it looks great.
-我喜欢!-是的，看起来很棒。
I have a vanilla Bundt cake
我有一个香草蛋糕
with a rice-cereal treat second layer.
第二层是米粉。
And for boulders,
对于巨石，
I have rice cereal treats covered in fondant.
我有裹着软糖的米麦片。
I don't know if it was finished cooking.
我不知道是不是煮好了。
I could've left it in the oven a little bit longer.
我本可以在烤箱里多烤一会儿的。
-Yeah, you could've. -Maybe a lot longer.
-是的，你可以的。-也许更久。
All right. So Dylin, you've got a couple problems.
好吧。迪林，你有几个问题。
Your cake was underbaked.
你的蛋糕没烤好。
And your royal icing turned into liquid.
你的皇家糖霜变成了液体。
You know, your ratio was way off.
你知道吗，你的比例太离谱了。
You know, this is, like, translucent.
你知道，这是半透明的。
You want royal icing to be opaque.
糖霜应该是不透明的。
Your flavors are great, you know, good job.
你的口味真棒，干得好。
I love your boulders. I love the way they look.
我喜欢你的巨石。我喜欢他们的样子。
Your cereal treats
你的麦片点心
could've used a little bit more marshmallow
能不能再加点棉花糖
and a little bit more butter.
再加一点黄油。
Yeah, just a few issues with your baking.
没事，只是你的烘焙有点问题。
Keili.
Keili。
-Yeah! -Whoo!
-耶!-哇!
Uh, that looks like a volcano!
嗯，那看起来像火山!
That looks like a craggy, gnarly volcano.
那看起来像一座崎岖不平的火山。
Looks really good!
看起来真不错!
I made a lemon Bundt cake
我做了一个柠檬蛋糕
with a chocolate ganache frosting
加上巧克力甘纳许糖霜
and a reddish-orangish buttercream lava.
还有红橙色的奶油熔岩。
And my rocks are fondant with chocolate chips in it.
我的巧克力是糖里面有巧克力屑。
And it's, like, sprinkled.
就像撒了一些。
I'm not a big fan of fondant being overly used.
我不赞成过度使用软糖。
Some people really like lemon and chocolate.
有些人非常喜欢柠檬和巧克力。
I, personally, don't think
我个人不这么认为
it really goes that well together.
它们真的很搭。
Lemons might be just a little too acidic for chocolate.
柠檬对巧克力来说可能有点太酸了。
-I like it. -Of course you do.
-我喜欢。-你当然知道。
The edge is really crispy and crunchy.
边缘非常酥脆。
So it really tastes good.
所以味道真的很好。
But the cake is definitely overcooked
但蛋糕肯定是煮过头了
because it's a little on the dry side.
因为它有点干。
I think you have a cake that is really interesting.
我觉得你做的蛋糕很有趣。
And I think your frosting is really, really good.
我觉得你的糖霜非常非常棒。
Okay.
好吧。
But the chocolate with the lemon,
但是柠檬巧克力，
I think it's a little weird.
我觉得这有点奇怪。
-I do not. -My partner in crime here...
-我没有。-我的同伙…
Thank you, Keili.
谢谢你，凯丽。
Hi, Reese! -Hello.
嗨,瑞茜!-你好。
More, more, there you go.
更多，更多，好了。
-Woo-hoo! -Yeah!
呜呼!-耶!
That's so good!
太好吃了!
I made a vanilla Bundt cake
我做了一个香草蛋糕
with a American chocolate buttercream.
配上美式巧克力奶油
My boulders are rice-cereal treats covered in black fondant.
我的巨石是覆盖着黑色软糖的米粉点心。
I'm a little concerned about the scale of the boulders
我有点担心这些巨石的规模
to the volcano. -Okay.
去火山。-好的。
The volcano doesn't look as big and massive
火山看起来没有那么大
because the boulders are so big.
因为这些巨石太大了。
I'm sure I could change my mind if it tastes really good.
如果真的很好吃，我肯定会改变主意的。
Boulder is -- Ooh. It exploded.
博尔德是——哦。它爆炸了。
Okay, this is a very hard treat.
好吧，这是一种很难的款待。
Did you put any butter in this?
你放黄油了吗?
-No. -You didn't put any butter in?
-不。-你没放黄油吗?
I forgot my butter.
我忘了带黄油。
This is horrible.
这太可怕了。
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary chocolate cakes melt
普通的巧克力蛋糕会融化
into molten lava Bundt cakes.
变成了熔岩蛋糕。
Right after this.
就在这之后。
ANNOUNCER: How to make mini Bundt lava cakes.
解说员:如何制作迷你邦特熔岩蛋糕。
Gather together mini Bundt pan, chocolate cake batter,
把迷你烤盘，巧克力蛋糕糊，
rock candy, white chocolate chips
冰糖，白巧克力片
and red food coloring.
红色食用色素。
Fill your Bundt pan with batter and bake off the cakes.
在平底锅里装满面糊，然后烤制蛋糕。
Use a mallet to crush your rock candy.
用木槌敲碎冰糖。
Melt your chocolate chips in the microwave.
用微波炉把巧克力片融化。
And add food coloring to make red lava.
然后加入食用色素做成红色熔岩。
Scoop the tops of the cake out and let the lava flow.
把蛋糕的顶部挖出来，让熔岩流出来。
Add the crushed rock candy for texture.
加入碎冰糖增加质感。
For more fun treats like this,
想要获得更多这样的乐趣，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
DUFF: That is...
达夫:那是……
Reese, when we asked you to make boulders,
里斯，我们让你做巨石的时候，
we didn't mean an actual boulder.
我们说的不是真正的巨石。
Did you put any butter in this?
你放黄油了吗?
No, I forgot to.
不，我忘了。
The marshmallows are just sugar.
棉花糖只是糖。
You know how sugar can get really hard?
你知道糖有多硬吗?
-Yeah. -Without any butter,
-是的。-没有黄油，
there's nothing for it to play with.
它没有什么可玩的。
Okay.
好吧。
Reese, I think you made a really good cake.
里斯，我觉得你做的蛋糕很好吃。
The flavor's awesome.
味道太棒了。
It's just a little on the dry side.
只是有点干。
And, man, these boulders,
天啊，这些巨石
remember, next time, you got to put butter in there.
记住，下次你得放黄油进去。
-Thank you, Reese. -Thank you.
-谢谢你，里斯。-谢谢。
How's it going, Cole?
怎么样，科尔?
Good.
好。
Nice.
好了。
That is the most sparkly volcano I've ever seen.
那是我见过的最闪亮的火山。
It's a chocolate-cinnamon cake
这是巧克力肉桂蛋糕
with chocolate-covered strawberry buttercream.
还有巧克力草莓奶油。
And the lava is white chocolate ganache.
熔岩是白巧克力甘纳许。
It looks like a really clean, really beautiful cake
它看起来非常干净，非常漂亮
and not as much of a volcano.
而不是像火山一样。
But you definitely have some skills.
但你确实有些技巧。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
The cinnamon and the chocolate together is so perfect.
肉桂和巧克力的搭配太完美了。
It's such a moist cake. -Thank you.
这蛋糕太湿了。-谢谢。
Uh, for me, I think it's a little bit too much cinnamon.
对我来说，我觉得肉桂有点太多了。
No!
不!
It's okay to disagree with me sometimes.
有时候不同意我也没关系。
It's okay. Like, we have difference of opinion.
没关系。比如，我们有不同的意见。
-I trust you. -All right.
-我相信你。-好的。
Let me see about this boulder here.
让我看看这块巨石。
A pecan truffle.
核桃松露。
I love the idea
我喜欢这个主意
of the pecans covered in the white chocolate.
白巧克力覆盖的山核桃。
It tastes so good.
味道好极了。
It's like a really great piece of candy.
就像一块很棒的糖果。
Cole, you are an impressive baker, man.
科尔，你真是个了不起的面包师。
Thanks a lot. -Thank you.
非常感谢。-谢谢。
Kaniyah.
Kaniyah。
Yeah!
是啊!
How fun is that?
多有趣啊?
Mind-blowing!
令人兴奋的!
I made a strawberry Bundt cake
我做了一个草莓蛋糕
with chocolate flake buttercream
加上巧克力片奶油
to present the dirt and sand
呈现泥土和沙子
and used red chocolate for the lava.
用红巧克力做熔岩。
Frosting is really good. I can taste the chocolate.
糖霜真的很好。我能尝到巧克力的味道。
It goes really, really nice with the strawberries.
和草莓一起吃真的很好吃。
I love it!
我喜欢!
I get that little bit of fruit in there
我在里面放了一点水果
with the really moist cake.
蛋糕很湿。
What about your boulders?
你的巨石怎么办?
I used black vanilla fondant
我用了黑香草软糖
and covered it in chocolate flakes.
然后在上面撒上巧克力片。
Feels like a boulder.
感觉像一块大石头。
Looks like a bowling ball covered in sprinkles.
看起来像个洒了糖屑的保龄球。
That's all fondant, huh?
那都是糖，是吧?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
是的。我很抱歉。
Oh, don't ever apologize, honey.
哦，永远不要道歉，亲爱的。
I don't necessarily want to taste one of your boulders.
我可不想尝尝你的石头。
But it looks really great.
但它看起来真的很棒。
Look. I think you made a cool-looking volcano.
看。我觉得你做了个很酷的火山。
-Absolutely. -It's dark.
-当然。——它的黑暗。
It's got a lot of boulders on it.
上面有很多巨石。
-Thank you very much. -Thanks, Kaniyah, great job.
-非常感谢。-谢谢，Kaniyah，干得好。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Aidan, I want to see that thing smoke.
艾登，我要看那东西冒烟。
Nice. -I love it!
好了。-我喜欢!
I love how it's going around all the sugar
我喜欢它绕着糖的样子
and the boulders.
还有那些巨石。
-Oh, yeah! -Yeah.
-哦,是的!-是的。
Tell me how you made the sugar.
告诉我你是怎么做糖的。
AIDAN: I melted isomalt and added some red dye.
艾丹:我融化了异麦芽糖，加入了一些红色染料。
Okay.
好吧。
And then I poured it over a tub of ice.
然后我把它倒在一桶冰上。
I didn't learn how to do that until I was about probably,
直到我大概，
like, 25 or so.
大概25岁左右。
Where did you learn how to do that?
你从哪学来的?
Uh, I actually saw it on a baking championship.
我在烘焙冠军赛上看到过。
And I was like, "Wow, that's cool!
我当时想，“哇，太酷了!
I want to try that." -Huh.
我想试试。”嗯。
Good job, man.
干得好，伙计。
It's a passion fruit cake.
这是百香果蛋糕。
And it has a banana buttercream.
还有香蕉奶油。
Mm!
毫米!
Aidan, that is such a moist cake!
艾登，这蛋糕太湿了!
Tastes like it was soaked in passion fruit.
尝起来像浸过百香果。
The passion fruit's awesome!
百香果太棒了!
The banana's awesome!
香蕉太棒了!
Everything really goes together, man.
每件事都很协调，伙计。
It really, really tastes good.
真的，真的很好吃。
Tell me about your boulders.
跟我说说你的巨石。
It's cream-filled cookies.
这是奶油夹心饼干。
And I crushed up the cookies and mixed it with the frosting.
我把饼干碾碎，和糖霜混合在一起。
I hope that there's a company
我希望有这样一家公司
that makes these sandwich cookies watching right now
这些三明治饼干都在看呢
because these sandwich cookies
因为这些三明治饼干
with the banana-flavored frosting
还有香蕉味的糖霜
all crushed up is amazing.
所有碾碎的东西都很神奇。
Mm-hmm, yeah.
嗯哼,是的。
Somebody needs to make those ASAP.
得有人尽快把这些做好。
-I agree. -And then...
我同意。——然后……
-Wholeheartedly. -...pay you for the idea.
全心全意。-…为你的想法付钱。
I wish the volcano was a little taller,
我希望火山再高一点，
looked a little bit more like a volcano.
看起来更像一座火山。
But once you bite into that cake, it doesn't matter.
但一旦你咬了那块蛋糕，就无所谓了。
That tastes so good!
味道好极了!
-Good job, Aidan. -Well done, well done.
-干得好，艾登。-干得好，干得好。
-Bye.
再见。再见。
Jason, I want to see that thing smoke.
杰森，我要看那东西冒烟。
-Woo-hoo! -That never gets old.
呜呼!-永远不会老。
That never gets old. Look at me.
这永远不会过时。看着我。
I've been doing this for years. And I still love it.
我做这个已经很多年了。我仍然喜欢它。
I'm looking at that beautiful Bundt cake.
我在看那个漂亮的邦特蛋糕。
And I'm not feeling volcano a lot.
我也不怎么觉得火山爆发了。
It's not very tall because my first Bundt cake
它不是很高，因为我的第一个邦特蛋糕
came out raw. -Hmm.
生出来的。嗯。
And I kept checking on it and it wasn't cooking.
我一直在检查它，但它没有煮熟。
Maybe because you kept checking on it.
也许是因为你一直在查看。
Yeah, okay.
是的,好的。
So tell us all about your cake.
跟我们说说你的蛋糕吧。
It's a chocolate Bundt cake.
这是一个巧克力蛋糕。
And I have red fondant for the lava.
我用红色的方糖做熔岩。
You're looking more like a brownie.
你看起来更像个小棕仙。
There's a lot of chocolate in there.
里面有很多巧克力。
It is chocolaty!
这是巧克力味的!
Oh, boy.
哦,男孩。
That's not good.
这可不太好。
Wow.
哇。
That's -- that's intense chocolate flavor.
那是强烈的巧克力味。
You wanted chocolate cake. You gave us a chocolate cake.
你要的是巧克力蛋糕。你给了我们一个巧克力蛋糕。
And tell us all about your boulders.
跟我们说说你的巨石。
The boulders are chocolate molded
这些巨石是巧克力铸成的
and gray fondant around it.
周围是灰色的方糖。
I'm gonna cut into this boulder.
我要切开这块巨石。
Okay, so the chocolate is really chocolaty.
好的，巧克力很有巧克力味。
-Yeah. -And I'm a little --
-是的。-我有点——
I'm... Now here's the thing.
我…事情是这样的。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
After a mouthful of chocolate like that,
吃了这么一口巧克力之后，
I kind of feel like a solid chocolate boulder
我感觉自己就像一块坚硬的巧克力巨石
might be a little much.
可能有点多。
What do you think?
你觉得呢?
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
When you've got chocolate on chocolate
当你有巧克力的时候
on chocolate,
关于巧克力，关于巧克力，
it doesn't give your palate any time
它不会给你的味觉任何时间
to enjoy the actual chocolate
去享受真正的巧克力
because your palate is so overwhelmed.
因为你的味蕾已经不堪重负了。
So you want to be able to release that
所以你想要能够释放它
a little bit with different flavors
有一点不同的味道
so your tongue just doesn't become bored with chocolate,
所以你的舌头不会对巧克力感到厌倦，
if that's possible. -Rah!
如果可能的话。好啊!
I hope my volcano cake doesn't blow it for me.
我希望我的火山蛋糕不会毁了我。
Chocolate!
巧克力!
Look at these guys.
看看这些家伙。
Two celebrities are just staring at us.
两个名人正盯着我们看呢。
And smiling.
和微笑。
Bakers, three of you were on fire today.
面包师们，你们三个今天火了。
Cole, your chocolate-cinnamon volcano cake
科尔，你的巧克力肉桂火山蛋糕
is picture perfect, almost too perfect.
这是一幅完美的画面，近乎完美。
And your cake and frosting were really nicely executed.
你的蛋糕和糖霜做得很好。
REESE: Good job.
里斯:干得好。
Aidan, your passion fruit cake
艾登，你的百香果蛋糕
with banana buttercream was erupting with flavor.
有了香蕉，奶油就散发出浓郁的香味。
Thanks.
谢谢。
And your lava sugar work, that was really impressive.
还有你的熔岩糖，真的很厉害。
Kaniyah, your airbrushed strawberry cake
Kaniyah，你的喷枪草莓蛋糕
was moist and so tasty.
又湿又好吃。
And it really looked like a volcano.
它看起来真的很像一座火山。
-Good job.
改善工作。改善工作。
However, there was one baker's volcano cake
然而，有一个面包师的火山蛋糕
that really blew the lid off of this challenge.
这才真正揭开了挑战的面纱。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Aidan.
艾丹。
AIDAN: When I first saw this challenge, my thought was,
艾丹:当我第一次看到这个挑战时，我的想法是，
"I can't make a volcano cake."
“我不会做火山蛋糕。”
And I won!
我赢了!
Now, the following bakers had an uphill battle
接下来的面包师们面临着一场艰难的战斗
but still gave us cakes
但还是给了我们蛋糕
that were good enough to make the grade.
已经足够好了。
And those bakers are...
那些面包师是……
Keili... -Yay.
Keili……耶。
-...Maya... -Good job.
玛雅…-…改善工作。
-...Justice... -Oh, thank you.
-正义……-哦，谢谢。
-...Audra... -Oh, my God, yay!
——Audra…-我的天啊，耶!
...and Reese.
…和瑞茜。
Yay!
耶!
Okay. So that leaves Charlotte, Dylin, Jason.
好吧。那就剩下夏洛特，迪林，杰森了。
Please step forward.
请往前走。
No!
不!
VALERIE: Charlotte, we couldn't taste
瓦莱丽:夏洛特，我们尝不出味道
the ginger in your ginger cake.
姜饼里的姜。
And it was extremely underbaked.
这是非常不成熟的。
Dylin, your vanilla Bundt cake
迪林，你的香草蛋糕
was dense and also underbaked.
又浓又不熟。
And your royal icing lava was way too thin.
你的御冰熔岩太薄了。
Jason, your chocolate cake
杰森，你的巧克力蛋糕
looked more like a Bundt cake than a volcano.
看起来不像火山，更像蛋糕。
Your boulders were just big hunks
你的巨石都是大块的
of chocolate and fondant.
巧克力和软糖。
And the whole thing was just a huge chocolate overload.
整件事就是巧克力超载了。
Unfortunately, one baker was swept away
不幸的是，一个面包师被冲走了
by today's challenge.
通过今天的挑战。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Charlotte.
夏洛特。
-Oh. -Sorry, darling.
-哦。对不起,亲爱的。
You did so good. But it's tough.
你做得很好。但这很难。
And we're really gonna miss you, sweetie.
我们会很想你的，亲爱的。
CHARLOTTE: This is not gonna stop me from baking,
夏洛特:这不会阻止我烘焙，
just 'cause I got eliminated.
就因为我被淘汰了
-We all did good. -It's okay.
我们都做得很好。——没问题。
CHARLOTTE: I love baking.
夏洛特:我喜欢烘焙。
I have a very big passion for it.
我对它有很大的热情。
And I want to inspire other kids to bake.
我想激励其他孩子也去烘焙。
-Keep baking!
小烤!小烤!
DUFF: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
DUFF:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
VALERIE: You have to make a volcano bundt cake.
瓦莱丽:你得做一个火山蛋糕。
And when you present it, it better be smoking.
当你展示它的时候，它最好是冒烟的。
Smokin' hot.
非常火爆的。
-Nice. -Ah! I love it!
-。——啊!我喜欢!
Aidan, it is such a moist cake.
艾登，这蛋糕太湿了。
Aidan really blew the lid off of this challenge.
艾登真的揭开了这场挑战的秘密。
Time to melt some more chocolate.
是时候再融化一些巧克力了。
Jason, the whole thing
杰森，整件事
was just a huge chocolate overload.
只是巧克力吃多了。
It's not fully cooked.
还没完全煮熟。
Charlotte, your cake is 90% raw.
夏洛特，你的蛋糕90%是生的。
Unfortunately, one baker was swept away by today's challenge.
不幸的是，一位面包师在今天的挑战中被淘汰了。
Charlotte, sorry, darlin'.
夏洛特，对不起，亲爱的。
**
**
Welcome back, bakers.
欢迎回来，面包师们。
Duff and I are hangin' out at the diner,
达夫和我在餐厅里闲逛
eating our favorite comfort food --
吃我们最喜欢的安慰食物——
fish and chips.
炸鱼和薯条。
What is going on here?
这是怎么回事?
Hmm.
嗯。
These fries are sweet, not salty.
这些薯条是甜的，不咸。
Why?
为什么?
Because this really isn't a plate of fish and chips.
因为这真的不是一盘炸鱼薯条。
-Yep. -Any idea what it might be?
是的。-知道是什么吗?
-Dessert Imposters!
甜点骗子!甜点骗子!
Of course, because the only thing more comforting
当然，因为唯一更让人欣慰的事
that comfort food is...dessert.
那种安慰的食物是……甜点。
-Whoo! -Yes.
-哇!-是的。
We're doing Dessert Imposters.
我们要做甜点骗子。
I'm so excited,
我很兴奋，
because it's not the "Kids Baking Championship"
因为这不是"儿童烘焙锦标赛"
without Dessert Imposters.
没有甜点骗子。
Tell us how you did it, Duff.
告诉我们你是怎么做到的，达夫。
Well, the fish fillet
嗯，鱼片
is actually a piece of cake
真的是小菜一碟吗
covered in batter and deep fried.
裹上面糊油炸。
-Uh-huh. -So good.
-嗯。所以很好。
Not bad, right? The fries --
还不错，对吧?薯条——
Any idea what it might be?
知道是什么吗?
Fried cake batter?
炸蛋糕面糊?
Fingers.
的手指。
Fingers? [ Laughter ]
手指?[笑声]
I don't know. Something like that.
我不知道。差不多就是这样。
The fries are fried apple sticks.
薯条是炸苹果条。
-I knew it! -Ah.
-我就知道!——啊。
And the coleslaw is dyed and shredded coconut.
凉拌卷心菜用的是染色的椰丝。
-It's all dessert. -They're so good.
-都是甜点。-他们太棒了。
All right, bakers. Now it's your turn.
好了，面包师们。现在轮到你了。
I'm excited but nervous
我既兴奋又紧张
'cause I'm going for a shot at redemption this time,
因为这次我要试着赎罪
because I haven't been doing very good.
因为我最近过得不太好。
-Here, on this order wheel... -I knew it.
-这里，在这个订单轮上…-我就知道。
I knew it. ...are the comfort-food classics
我就知道. ...这些美食是经典吗
that you are gonna be turning into Dessert Imposters.
你们会变成甜点冒名顶替者
-Aah! -Yeah!
啊!-耶!
For this big bake,
为了这个大蛋糕，
we are giving you 2 hours to work your magic.
我们给你两个小时施展你的魔法。
Remember, you are baking to stay in this competition
记住，你要努力留在比赛中
and possibly win $25,000.
还可能赢得25000美元。
-Yay! -Yay.
耶!耶。
-I like money. -"I like money."
我喜欢钱。-“我喜欢钱。”
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
All right, guys. Two hours.
好了，伙计们。两个小时。
And your time starts now.
你的时间从现在开始。
-Aah! -No, no, no, no, no.
啊!-不，不，不，不。
-No, grab, don't look. -Whoo!
-不，抓住，别看。-哇!
I got peanut butter and jelly sandwich!
我有花生酱和果冻三明治!
I have burrito.
我有墨西哥卷饼。
I got fried chicken.
我有炸鸡。
My ticket says fried chicken. I look at it.
我的车票上写着炸鸡。我看着它。
And I'm like, "Fried chicken. Oh.
我说:“炸鸡。哦。
Oh.
哦。
Okay. I'll see what I can do.
好吧。我看看我能做些什么。
Huh.
嗯。
I'm just gonna do cake."
我要做蛋糕。”
So, for my fried chicken,
我的炸鸡，
I will be making a lemon cake
我要做柠檬蛋糕
with a gum paste bone.
用口香糖糊骨头。
I sift flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt.
我筛面粉、糖、发酵粉和盐。
Beating the egg whites helps to make your cake nice and airy.
打蛋白可以让蛋糕更漂亮，更松软。
And I'm gonna make bones out of gum paste.
我要用口香糖做骨头。
Gum paste is white.
口香糖膏是白色的。
So I'm gonna roll it out
所以我要把它推出来
into a nice, long log shape
做成漂亮的长圆木形状
to make it look like the joint of the bone.
让它看起来像骨头的关节。
I made a sort of accidental Dessert Imposter once.
我曾经做过一个意外的甜点冒充者。
It was a cheesecake.
那是一块芝士蛋糕。
But it looked more like a pizza.
但它看起来更像披萨。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I'm making a "meatball sub"
我在做"肉丸三明治"
with pâte à choux bread.
配上泡芙面包。
All right. I'm gonna get started on my pâte à choux.
好吧。我要开始做我的馅饼了。
I'm going to start by boiling water and butter
我要先烧开水和黄油
and then mix in flour really quickly.
然后迅速加入面粉。
Are you kidding me? Aidan is making pâte à choux.
你在开玩笑吗?艾丹在做炸土豆条。
It's got to be for his roll for his meatball sub.
肯定是给他的肉丸子三明治准备的。
That is good thinkin'.
这主意不错。
It's gonna look like bread, 'cause it kind of is bread.
看起来会像面包，因为它就是面包。
Then I mix that in the mixer.
然后在搅拌器里搅拌。
Then I begin to add my eggs.
然后我开始加鸡蛋。
Pipe it out and bake it off.
用管子把它弄出来，烤制一下。
What's a meatball sub without a nice, big slice of bread?
没有美味的大片面包，肉丸三明治算什么?
* I like big buns, and I cannot lie *
我喜欢大面包，我不能撒谎
I'm just publicly embarrassing myself on TV.
我只是在电视上当众出丑。
[ Grunting, straining ]
[咕噜，用力]
I am making a grilled-cheese sandwich out of almond cake
我正在用杏仁蛋糕做烤奶酪三明治
and almond paste for cheese.
还有杏仁酱做奶酪。
Pretty excited to try this out.
很高兴能尝试一下。
Can't wait to grill a cake.
等不及要烤蛋糕了。
I would love to try a Dessert Imposter
我想尝尝冒牌甜点
as a trick on my dad.
作为对我爸的一个玩笑。
My daddy would try to eat the sandwich,
我爸爸试着吃三明治，
and he'd be like this.
他会是这样的。
"I did not know this was cake."
“我不知道这是蛋糕。”
**
**
I'm choosing a loaf pan because I really want my cake
我要选一个烤盘，因为我真的很想吃蛋糕
to look like whole-wheat bread.
看起来像全麦面包。
You already got yours into the pan?
你已经把你的放进锅里了吗?
-Yeah. -Wow.
-是的。-哇。
I have to work on somethin' else.
我有别的事要做。
The tomato soup.
西红柿汤。
MAYA: I don't even know what a roast-beef sandwich looks like.
玛雅:我甚至不知道烤牛肉三明治长什么样。
Because of my religion, I don't eat beef at all.
因为我的宗教信仰，我根本不吃牛肉。
So I'm a little worried.
所以我有点担心。
So far, I'm making, like, the bread,
目前为止，我在做面包，
which is gonna be a yellow cake.
那将是一个黄色的蛋糕。
And then the brownie is gonna be the meat.
然后布朗尼就是肉了。
That's all I know so far.
到目前为止我只知道这些。
Last week, the judges thought that my cake was dense.
上周，评委们认为我的蛋糕太稠了。
To make the cake moist, I'm adding a little more butter.
为了使蛋糕湿润，我要再加一点黄油。
And I really hope it doesn't ruin the recipe.
我真的希望它不会破坏食谱。
Oh, yay. It's smooth.
哦,耶。它是光滑的。
I thought it would be clumpy. But it's actually really smooth.
我以为它会是块状的。但是它真的很光滑。
I can't serve the judges another dense cake
我不能再给评委们上厚厚的蛋糕了
'cause, like, I've already done that.
因为，我已经做过了。
I can check that off.
我可以核对一下。
How are you doing, Audra?
你还好吗，奥德拉?
I'm making a pie dough right now.
我现在正在做馅饼。
-Really? -I have mac and cheese.
-真的?-我有芝士通心粉。
I make mac and cheese for me and my brothers
我给我和我的兄弟们做奶酪通心粉
because I love mac and cheese
因为我喜欢芝士通心粉
even though I make it from a box.
尽管我是用盒子做的
Come on, coarse crumbs.
来吧，粗面包屑。
I am doing a deconstructed lemon pie,
我在做一个解构柠檬派，
because the lemon curd that I'm going to make
因为我要做的柠檬凝乳
should look like cheese.
看起来应该像奶酪。
Stay.
留下来。
For my pie crust, I combine my flour and salt
我把面粉和盐混合在一起做派皮
with a pastry blender.
用面点搅拌机。
And then I add my butter and shortening.
然后加入黄油和起酥油。
Seems strong enough to hold together.
看起来足够坚强，可以团结在一起。
I wrap it in plastic wrap
我用保鲜膜把它包起来
and chill it in the blast chiller.
然后用冷风机冷却。
90 minutes, bakers.
90分钟，面包师们。
90 minutes.
90分钟。
Oh, don't close that. Don't close that.
哦，别关。不要关闭它。
Comfort Food Dessert Imposters.
安慰食品甜点骗子。
They have to be deceiving but delicious.
它们必须具有欺骗性，但又很美味。
Hope this works.
希望这有用。
I'm making a chili made out of chocolate ganache,
我在用巧克力甘纳许做辣椒，
pistachio and almonds, and cake "chicken."
开心果和杏仁，还有鸡肉蛋糕。
Almonds and pistachios
杏仁和开心果
are gonna be my beans in my chili.
我要把豆子放进辣椒里。
When I eat chili, I usually have tortilla strips in my chili.
当我吃辣椒的时候，我通常会在辣椒里放玉米饼条。
For my tortilla strips,
做玉米饼条的时候，
I will be using phyllo dough.
我要用菲罗面团。
Of all the things to make today,
今天要做的事，
I had to make a hot dog out of cake.
我不得不用蛋糕做热狗。
-Oh, wow. -For my diner comfort food,
-哦,哇。-我的晚餐安慰食物
I am making a vanilla cake hot dog bun
我在做香草蛋糕热狗面包
with a buttercream hot dog.
还有奶油热狗。
I'm making a vanilla cake for my hot dog bun
我在为我的热狗面包做香草蛋糕
'cause it's kind of a stiff batter,
因为它是一种硬面糊，
and it doesn't crumble too much.
而且不会太碎。
DUFF: All right. How's it goin', Dylin?
达夫:好吧。怎么样，迪林?
Going way better than it normally has.
比平时好多了。
Okay. That's good. That's good.
好吧。这很好。这很好。
So, uh, what is your Dessert Imposter?
你的甜点冒名顶替者是什么?
-Mine is hot dogs. -All right.
-我的是热狗。-好的。
So how do you eat your hot dogs?
你是怎么吃热狗的?
I eat my hot dog with my hands and with, like, two bites.
我用手吃热狗，大概两口就吃完。
[ Laughing ]
[笑]
I meant, like, what do you -- What do you put on top of 'em?
我是说，你会在上面放什么?
Oh. I put on top ketchup and mustard.
哦。我在上面放上番茄酱和芥末。
-Wait. Did you say ketchup? -Yes.
等。你是说番茄酱吗?-是的。
I really feel that ketchup on a hot dog
我真的感觉到了热狗上的番茄酱
is just un-American.
就是不美国。
-Why? -I just -- Ugh.
-为什么?-我只是…
Ketchup on fries. Mustard on hot dogs.
薯条上放番茄酱。热狗上有芥末。
But ketchup's awesome on hot dogs.
但是番茄酱加在热狗上太棒了。
Is it? Ugh.
是吗?啊。
Hey, who in here puts ketchup on their hot dog?
嘿，谁会在热狗上涂番茄酱啊?
-Me! -Me.
加!加。
-Ketchup! -You're all wrong.
番茄酱!-你们都错了。
-No, we're not. -Dude, that's totally gross.
-不，我们没有。-老兄，这太恶心了。
Awesome. [ Both laugh ]
太棒了。[两人笑]
-All right, man. Good luck. -Thank you.
-好吧，伙计。祝你好运。-谢谢。
-You're making a chocolate cake? -I am.
-你在做巧克力蛋糕?我是。
Looks good.
看起来不错。
On my diner ticket, I got meatloaf.
我的餐券上有肉卷。
I have made Dessert Imposters before.
我以前做过甜点冒名顶替者。
I am gonna win this challenge.
我要赢得这场挑战。
I'm gonna make a easy chocolate cake
我要做一个简单的巧克力蛋糕
with a strawberry coulis.
配上草莓酱。
But I don't want it to be boring.
但我不想太无聊。
So I'm gonna infuse it with coffee.
所以我要往里面倒咖啡。
-Coffee.
咖啡。咖啡。
Coffee really brings out the flavor of cocoa,
咖啡真的能带出可可的味道，
like, in the best way possible.
用最好的方式。
And I'm pouring the batter in my pan.
我把面糊倒进锅里。
But I feel like I can add
但我觉得我可以补充
a little more texture on the top.
上面要多一点质感。
So I chop up some pecans and sprinkle them right on top.
所以我切碎一些山核桃，洒在上面。
One hour left, bakers!
还有一个小时，面包师们!
I don't know if I have enough time.
我不知道我是否有足够的时间。
Hmm.
嗯。
That's not good.
这可不太好。
The cake is oozing out of the side
蛋糕从侧面渗出来了
and dropping to the bottom and burning.
然后掉到底部燃烧。
Ai-yai-yai.
Ai-yai-yai。
COLE: This is not good.
科尔:这可不妙。
The cake is oozing out of the side.
蛋糕从侧面渗出来了。
I don't know what I'm gonna do right now.
我不知道我现在该怎么办。
But I know I have to fix it.
但我知道我必须解决它。
Ai-yai-yai.
Ai-yai-yai。
So I decided to put a layer of aluminum foil over the cake.
所以我决定在蛋糕上盖一层铝箔。
It's gonna keep the batter from continuing to spill out.
这样可以防止面糊继续溢出来。
I hope this helps.
我希望这对你有帮助。
Okay. This could work.
好吧。这是可行的。
I grab a sheet pan, unwrap my dough,
我拿起烤盘，打开面团，
and start to cut it to look like noodles.
开始把它切成面条的样子。
It's gonna take forever to roll them all out.
要把它们全部推出去要花很长时间。
**
**
VALERIE: I love watchin' the kids bake.
瓦莱丽:我喜欢看孩子们烤面包。
I love tasting all of their desserts.
我喜欢品尝他们所有的甜点。
But, you know, sometimes I just want somethin' salty.
但是，你知道，有时候我只是想吃点咸的。
Yeah. Me, too.
是的。我也是。
I think they're just snacking. I hope they're just snacking.
我想他们只是在吃零食。我希望他们只是在吃零食。
Bakers, can we have your attention, please?
面包师们，请注意了?
-Uh-oh. -No.
啊哦。-不。
We have decided to spice up the big bake.
我们决定给大烤面包加点调料。
We want Dessert Imposter chips and salsa.
我们要甜点冒名顶替薯片和莎莎酱。
-Chips and salsa? -You guys get it?
-薯条和萨尔萨?你们明白了吗?
You got to make chips and salsa.
你得做薯片和辣酱。
But you can't use chips or salsa.
但你不能用薯片或莎莎酱。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Another Dessert Imposter.
又一个甜点骗子。
Actually, that's gonna go perfect with my burrito.
事实上，这和我的墨西哥卷饼很搭。
JASON: Duff and Valerie want chips and salsa.
杰森:达夫和瓦莱丽要薯条和萨尔萨酱。
I got this.
我来吧。
I'm making a burrito
我在做墨西哥卷饼
with pound-cake chicken
用磅饼鸡肉
and buttercream sour cream,
还有奶油酸奶油，
using crepes for my tortilla.
用可丽饼做玉米饼。
Crepe time.
绉。
I want to be the kids baking champion
我想成为儿童烘焙冠军
because I want to start my own crepe business.
因为我想开创自己的可丽饼生意。
I am amazing at crepes.
我很擅长做可丽饼。
I'm using eggs, salt, sugar, butter, and flour.
我要用鸡蛋、盐、糖、黄油和面粉。
Ah, that's some nice crepe batter.
这可丽饼面糊真不错。
So I wait for the crepe to start bubbling,
等可丽饼开始冒泡，
little small bubbles at the top,
上面有小气泡，
kind of like when you're cooking a pancake.
就像你在做煎饼一样。
That's how you know when to flip it.
这样你就知道什么时候该出手了。
Wait 30 seconds.
等30秒。
And then my crepe is done.
然后我的可丽饼就做好了。
For my chips and salsa,
为了我的薯片和萨尔萨酱，
I'm gonna make my chips out of crepes.
我要用可丽饼做薯片。
I'm gonna cut it into triangles,
把它切成三角形，
fry them until they're crispy.
把它们煎到酥脆。
This is crispy. And for my salsa,
这个很脆。我的萨尔萨舞，
I'm gonna be using two different colors
我要用两种不同的颜色
of milk chocolate
牛奶巧克力
and some leftover buttercream from my burritos.
还有墨西哥卷饼剩下的奶油。
I'm doin' okay.
我还好。
I'm crying on the inside.
我的内心在哭泣。
I have to stop what I'm doing and make chips and salsa.
我得停下手头的事，去做薯片和辣酱。
Right now is not the right time,
现在不是时候，
when I'm still mixing this batter.
当我还在搅拌面糊的时候
Then I'm making a white cake sandwich bread,
然后我要做一个白蛋糕三明治面包，
a peanut butter chip buttercream,
花生酱片奶油，
and a grape buttercream filling.
还有葡萄奶油馅。
Gonna make the white cake
要做白蛋糕了
because most peanut butter and jelly bread is white.
因为大多数花生酱和果冻面包都是白色的。
I need to get these in right now
我得马上把这些拿进去
so I can get started on my chips and salsa.
这样我就可以开始吃薯片和萨尔萨了。
For my chips, I have leftover cake batter.
我用剩下的蛋糕面糊做薯片。
I'm gonna make it thin. I'm gonna bake it for a bit.
我要把它做薄一点。我要烤一会儿。
Then I'm gonna throw it in the fryer and fry it,
然后把它扔进油炸锅里煎，
then toss it in cinnamon and sugar.
然后加入肉桂和糖。
I guess, for my salsa, I'm just gonna throw together
我想，做萨尔萨的时候，我要把它们放在一起
chocolate malt coconut flakes
巧克力麦芽椰子片
and sprinkles for the cilantro.
撒上香菜屑。
Aidan: I don't know what I should use as my salsa.
艾丹:我不知道我应该用什么来做萨尔萨舞。
I already have a side.
我已经有立场了。
I'm not gonna worry about that right now
我现在不担心这个
'cause I've got other things to do.
因为我还有别的事要做。
I'm making my meatballs.
我在做肉丸子。
Delicious butter and chocolate.
美味的黄油和巧克力。
My trick to making really fudgy brownies
我做巧克力蛋糕的小窍门
is adding more butter and chocolate to them.
就是加更多的黄油和巧克力。
[ Laughing ] I'm getting emotional about these brownies.
(笑)这些巧克力蛋糕让我很激动。
They're gonna live happily ever after in the oven
他们会在烤箱里幸福地生活下去
until I take them out.
直到我把他们干掉。
For my chips, I'm going to make sugar-cookie chips...
至于我的薯片，我要做糖饼干薯片……
That's just gonna cream together.
会变成奶油的。
...with triangle shapes.
…三角形。
And for my salsa, I'm thinking
我在想我的萨尔萨舞
of just pureeing some fruit.
只是把一些水果弄成泥。
REESE: I'm pretty lucky that I already have chips done.
里斯:我很幸运，我已经做好了薯条。
All I have to do is just make a raspberry compote.
我要做的就是做覆盆子果盘。
About a teaspoon.
大约一茶匙。
I'm using corn starch so I can get a thicker consistency.
我用的是玉米淀粉，这样粘稠度会更高。
**
**
Delicious.
美味。
DUFF: 45 minutes, bakers! 45 minutes.
达夫:45分钟，面包师们!45分钟。
Okay. Thanks.
好吧。谢谢。
What do you usually order at a diner?
你在餐厅通常点什么?
Um, you know, like, mac and cheese, uh, meatloaf.
比如芝士通心粉，肉卷之类的。
Open-faced turkey sandwich with gravy.
带肉汁的火鸡三明治。
-Open-faced turkey sandwich. -Open-faced turkey
-敞口火鸡三明治。阔脸土耳其
with the gravy and the mashed potatoes on the side.
配上肉汁和土豆泥。
Oh!
哦!
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
-Reese. -Yeah?
瑞茜。-是吗?
-What are you doing for chips? -Phyllo chips.
-你要吃薯片吗?蛋糕芯片。
Phyllo it is.
是菲洛。
I've never worked with phyllo dough before.
我从来没做过油酥皮。
But I think I might be able to use it.
但我想我可以用它。
I cut the raw phyllo dough into triangles
我把生油酥皮切成三角形
and get those in the oven.
然后把它们放进烤箱。
And my salsa is diced apples, cherries,
我的萨尔萨酱是苹果丁，樱桃丁，
mixed together with some green sprinkles.
和一些绿色的碎屑混合在一起。
I add a bit of red
我加了一点红色
so that it looks just like chipotle salsa.
这样看起来就像墨西哥辣酱。
It is hot in here.
这里很热。
I'm already making grilled cheese,
我已经在做烤奶酪了
tomato soup, french fries. There.
西红柿汤，炸薯条。在那里。
Now I have to make chips and salsa?
现在我还得做薯片和辣酱?
For my chips, I'm going to use phyllo dough
我要用菲罗面团做薯片
and put it in the oven for a little bit.
然后把它放进烤箱烤一会儿。
And for my salsa, I'm using blood-orange puree
做萨尔萨，我用的是血橙泥
and coconut.
和椰子。
And I'm using chocolate-candy melts.
我用的是巧克力糖融化物。
And it's turning brown. I don't know about that.
它正在变成棕色。我不知道。
I hope it tastes good.
我希望它尝起来不错。
Justice, can you open this for me?
法官，你能帮我打开这个吗?
-Yeah. -Thanks.
-是的。-谢谢。
To make this roast beef sandwich
做这个烤牛肉三明治
look like a real sandwich
看起来像个真正的三明治
I am dyeing coconut flakes green
我正在把椰子片染成绿色
to make it look like lettuce.
让它看起来像生菜。
And I use raspberries as tomatoes.
我用覆盆子做番茄。
To make my chips and salsas,
来做我的薯片和辣酱，
for the chips, I'm doing crepes deep fried
至于薯条，我要做油炸薄饼
with sprinkled cinnamon sugar.
撒上肉桂糖。
For my salsa, I'm also using my leftover coconut flakes
我还用剩下的椰子片做萨尔萨酱
that look like lettuce and frozen cherries mashed up.
看起来像是生菜和冻樱桃捣碎的。
I'm just gonna go with that.
我就这么办了。
Ooh, you're makin' phyllo-dough chips?
哦，你在做油酥片?
-Yeah. -That's a good idea.
-是的。-好主意。
I hope that it works.
我希望它能起作用。
JUSTICE: To stand out, I can make watermelon salsa.
JUSTICE:为了脱颖而出，我会做西瓜辣酱。
I get some green-apple puree, and I put that in there as well.
我准备了一些青苹果泥，也放进去了。
And I start to stir that up.
我开始搅动它。
It looks a lot like salsa.
看起来很像萨尔萨舞。
I'm really proud of myself.
我真的为自己感到骄傲。
Justice is takin' a really cool approach to the salsa.
正义对萨尔萨舞的态度很酷。
He's chopping a bunch of fresh fruit.
他正在切一串新鲜水果。
It certainly does look a lot more like salsa
它看起来确实更像萨尔萨舞
than a lot of the other salsas I'm seeing.
比我见过的很多其他莎莎舞都好
When I was younger, you know,
我小的时候，你知道，
chips and salsa was, like, a thing.
炸薯片和莎莎舞是很流行的。
-Is it somethin' different now? -I-I don't know.
-现在有什么不同了吗?-我不知道。
Some sort of Pokemon snack or somethin' they eat?
是口袋妖怪的零食还是他们吃的东西?
I don't know.
我不知道。
Kids these days.
现在的孩子们。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
For my chips and salsa,
为了我的薯片和萨尔萨酱，
I'm going to deep-fry puff pastry dough
我要油炸酥皮面团
and toss it in cinnamon sugar
然后加入肉桂糖
and make a mango-pineapple salsa.
做一个芒果菠萝沙司。
I've never made this before.
我以前从没做过这个。
And I don't think I ever would if it weren't for Duff.
如果不是因为达夫，我也不会这么做。
**
**
-40 minutes, bakers. -40?
-40分钟，面包师们。-40年?
-Oh, no.
-40年?-哦,不。
My hands are so full
我忙得不可开交
that I'm not even going to be able to start my chips and salsa
我都没法开始吃薯片和萨尔萨了
until I'm done with my mac-and-cheese Dessert Imposter.
直到我吃完奶酪通心粉甜点冒名顶替者
It is such a long process,
这是一个漫长的过程，
because I have to do them all individually.
因为我要逐个做。
This is taking a lot longer than I expected.
这比我预期的要长得多。
Audra's been spending way too much time on that pie dough.
奥德拉在那批派上花了太多时间。
And she hasn't made anything else.
除此之外，她什么也没做。
-What's she got, mac and cheese? -She's got mac and cheese.
-她有奶酪通心粉吗?她有芝士通心粉。
Mm.
毫米。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I think I have to scratch my lemon curd.
我想我得刮一下我的柠檬凝乳。
I don't know if I have enough time to make it.
我不知道我是否有足够的时间去。
30 minutes left, bakers.
还有30分钟，面包师们。
-Oh, my God. -30?
-我的天啊。-30年?
VALERIE: Comfort Food Desert Imposters
瓦莱丽:安慰食品沙漠骗子
with a little side of chips and salsa.
再加一点薯片和莎莎酱。
Do they have a juicer here?
这里有榨汁机吗?
Lemon curd takes a while.
柠檬凝乳需要一段时间。
And I still have to make my chips and salsa.
我还得做薯片和辣酱。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝。
To make my lemon curd,
做柠檬凝乳，
I separate out some egg yolks...
我挑出一些蛋黄…
Egg yolk.
蛋黄。
...measure out some butter,
…量出一些黄油，
juice and zest some lemons...
给柠檬榨汁并去皮……
It was not a good idea
这不是一个好主意
to juice my lemons before I zest them.
在削皮前榨柠檬汁。
...and measure out some sugar.
…量出一些糖。
With your lemon curd, you have to heat it up slowly,
做柠檬凝乳时，要慢慢加热，
because you don't want to scramble the eggs.
因为你不想炒鸡蛋。
This twist sucks.
这种扭曲很糟糕。
I'm not sure I like the service at this diner.
我不太喜欢这家餐厅的服务。
We've been waiting here for almost 2 hours now.
我们已经在这里等了快两个小时了。
Almost 2 hours. Yeah.
差不多2个小时。是的。
Not even a cup of coffee. You know what I mean?
连一杯咖啡都没有。你懂我的意思吗?
Nothin'.
一文不值。
I remember, Duff, he likes chocolate.
我记得，达夫他喜欢巧克力。
But he doesn't like chocolate -- chocolate explosion.
但他不喜欢巧克力，巧克力爆炸。
-I know. -Now I have to figure out
-我知道。-现在我得想办法了
how to make beans for my burrito.
如何为我的墨西哥卷饼做豆子。
Hmm. I'm going to go with milk chocolate...
嗯。我要选牛奶巧克力……
It kind of looks like beans.
它看起来有点像豆子。
...because I don't want to have a big chocolate bomb again.
…因为我不想再吃巧克力炸弹了。
Hello, Jason.
你好,杰森。
-[ Giggling ] -Hello.
-[咯咯笑]-你好。
-So you're makin' a burrito. -Mm-hmm.
-所以你在做墨西哥卷饼。-嗯。
-And how you doin' that? -So, I have some refried beans
-你是怎么做到的?-那么，我有一些炒豆
made out of some milk chocolate chips.
用牛奶巧克力片做的。
Uh-huh.
啊哈。
-Are these the refried beans? -Yeah.
-这些是炒豆吗?-是的。
Well, you really refried those multiple times, huh?
你还真是炸了好几次啊?
[ Laughs ] That looks more like chocolate sauce to me.
(笑)我觉得那更像巧克力酱。
But how are you gonna make that chocolate sauce
但你要怎么做巧克力酱
-look like refried beans? -My chocolate's really smooth.
-看起来像油炸豆?-我的巧克力很滑。
So I add some chocolate chips
所以我加了一些巧克力片
while it's still a little warm
趁现在还有点热
so it kind of looks like the refried beans
看起来有点像油炸豆
have a little bit of whole beans in there.
放一点全豆进去。
I hope that kid was listening last week.
我希望那孩子上周有在听。
I think he did. But we'll see.
我想是的。但我们会看到的。
JUSTICE: I pull out my cakes.
正义:我拿出我的蛋糕。
I cut the top of it. I take my "chicken."
我剪掉了它的顶部。我带着我的“鸡”。
And I make my cake balls.
我做我的蛋糕球。
And I cover them in blackberry jam, like "barbecue sauce."
然后涂上黑莓酱，就像烧烤酱一样
And then I cover it in graham cracker crumbs
然后在上面撒上全麦饼干屑
so it'll stick and look like fried chicken.
所以它会粘起来，看起来像炸鸡。
I like it.
我喜欢它。
Maya, what'd you get? What do you got?
玛雅，你得到了什么?你有什么发现?
Um, beef sandwich?
牛肉三明治?
Roast beef sandwich or just a beef sandwich?
烤牛肉三明治还是只吃牛肉三明治?
-Oh, no. A roast beef sandwich. -Okay. [ Chuckles ]
-哦,不。烤牛肉三明治。-好的。[笑]
I'm going to be adding extra moisture to my cake,
我要给蛋糕加点水分，
adding buttercream as mayonnaise.
加入奶油作为蛋黄酱。
Okay. I get started
好吧。我开始了
on creaming my butter and my powdered sugar.
搅拌黄油和糖粉。
Then I add my milk and then my vanilla.
然后加入牛奶和香草。
I know my buttercream is done when it's, like, really fluffy.
当奶油变得非常蓬松的时候，我就知道它做好了。
And, like, if it would fly up in the air,
如果它能飞到空中，
it would, like, probably be like clouds soaring.
可能就像云在飞翔。
[ Birds singing ]
[鸟儿歌唱]
20 minutes, guys!
20分钟，伙计们!
-20? -Yes. 20.
-20年?-是的。20.
Whoa, that's not a lot of time.
这时间可真不多啊。
For my grape jelly buttercream,
我的葡萄果冻奶油，
I'm gonna use grape jelly inside
我要在里面放些葡萄果冻
so that it gives it that grape jelly flavor.
这样就有了葡萄果冻的味道。
And hopefully it'll give it that color.
希望它能变成那种颜色。
But I'm not so sure if it will.
但我不确定它是否会。
So I add in purple food coloring.
所以我加入了紫色食用色素。
Perfect.
完美的。
**
**
I cut rectangles out of my cake.
我从蛋糕上切出长方形。
And I carefully put them on the plate.
我小心翼翼地把它们放在盘子里。
I put them in the freezer so they'll cool.
我把它们放在冰箱里，让它们冷却。
And I start working on my buttercream.
然后我开始做奶油。
One of them, I dye red.
其中一个，我染成红色。
One of them, I dye green.
其中一个，我染成绿色。
And one of them, I dye yellow --
其中一个，我染成黄色
yellow for the mustard,
黄色是芥末酱，
red for the hot dog and the ketchup,
红色代表热狗和番茄酱，
and the green for the relish.
绿色的用来调味。
The many uses of buttercream.
奶油的多种用途。
KANIYAH: I have cheese.
我有奶酪。
For my grilled cheese, I am using almond paste
烤奶酪用的是杏仁酱
and mixing it with yellow food dye
和黄色食用染料混合
to make it look like the cheese.
让它看起来像奶酪。
Lookin' like cheese, lookin' like cheese,
看起来像奶酪，看起来像奶酪
lookin' like cheese.
看起来像奶酪。
And I start assembling my sandwiches.
然后我开始组装三明治。
I want to slice it so that it looks the same size.
我想把它切成一样大小。
It looks like Texas toast.
看起来像德州吐司。
I flip my bread over, and...
我把面包翻过来，然后…
Ah.
啊。
...what do I see?
…我看到了什么?
I see golden brownness.
我看到了金黄色。
Yay.
耶。
Okay. It's not burnt.
好吧。没有烧焦。
15 minutes, bakers. You got 15 minutes.
15分钟，面包师们。给你15分钟。
Order up!
订单!
Oh, my God. I need to make my salsa.
我的天啊。我要做萨尔萨。
Audra is just now starting on her chips and salsa?
奥德拉现在才开始吃薯片和萨尔萨?
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
AUDRA: To make my chips,
为了做薯片，
I fry up some pie dough.
我煎了一些派皮。
And for my salsa,
我的萨尔萨舞，
I take some passion-fruit puree
我拿一些西番莲果泥
and add some red food dye to it.
再加一些红色食用染料进去。
Super red. Nice.
超级红。好了。
Then I add some mini marshmallows
然后我加一些迷你棉花糖
to act as kind of, like, onions.
就像洋葱一样。
As my water's boiling with my beans inside,
当我的水和豆子一起沸腾时，
I'm going to start on my chocolate ganache.
我要开始做巧克力甘纳许了。
I heat up my heavy cream
我加热我的浓奶油
and then pour it right over the chocolate
然后把它倒在巧克力上
and start to stir.
然后开始搅拌。
I think my chili's gonna taste awesome.
我觉得我的辣椒会很好吃。
COLE: It's okay.
科尔:没关系。
I want to make this Dessert Imposter extra special.
我想让这个甜点冒名顶替者特别一点。
So I decided to put a side dish.
所以我决定放一道配菜。
For my mashed potatoes, I make a buttercream
我做土豆泥的时候，会放奶油
with seeds from a vanilla bean and a half a banana.
用香草豆和半根香蕉的种子。
I'm adding sea-salt flakes to this
我在里面加入海盐片
because it's a really sweet frosting.
因为它的糖霜真的很甜。
So it'll give a nice sweet-and-salty taste.
所以它会有一种甜咸的味道。
I'm also gonna add some green beans.
我还要加一些四季豆。
Okay. I grab green candy melts
好吧。我抓起绿色的糖果融化物
and glucose syrup.
还有葡萄糖浆。
And I put 'em in a food processor
我把它们放在食品加工机里
until it forms a dough.
直到它变成面团。
I made fresh modeling chocolate. Very proud of myself.
我做了新鲜的模型巧克力。我为自己感到骄傲。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I'm such a nerd.
我真是个书呆子。
Did you say saucy?
你是说俏皮吗?
Yes, something that we always joke around
是的，我们经常开玩笑的事
in our house.
在我们家。
To assemble my subs,
组装潜艇，
I roll out some brownie into the shape of meatballs,
我把布朗尼擀成肉丸状，
sprinkle on some raspberry sauce
撒上一些覆盆子酱
as my marinara,
作为我的调味汁，
and spoon on white chocolate for mozzarella.
用勺子舀上白巧克力做马苏里拉奶酪。
All right. That's my last one.
好吧。这是我最后一个。
5 little, ol' minutes. Uh, hey.
就5分钟。哦,嘿。
Have you guys plated? Are you plating now?
你们准备好盘子了吗?你现在在电镀吗?
You got 5 minutes.
给你5分钟。
All right. Now to throw together a salsa.
好吧。现在来做萨尔萨。
I remembered that I still need to make salsa.
我记得我还需要做萨尔萨。
I think I can pull it off if I try.
我想只要我努力，我就能成功。
It doesn't look the prettiest.
它看起来不太漂亮。
But it's fine.
但没关系。
JASON: I sprinkle my cake just like little pieces of chicken
杰森:我把蛋糕撒得像鸡块一样
on top of the chocolate refried beans in my burrito.
在我的墨西哥卷饼里的巧克力炒豆上面。
And then I start layering over the other ingredients.
然后我开始在其他食材上分层。
Sour cream. I wrap them up in some tin foil.
酸奶油。我用锡纸把它们包起来。
And there you go.
好了。
Burritos!
墨西哥玉米煎饼!
3 1/2 minutes.
3分半钟。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。我的天啊。
We've been waiting. We want food.
我们一直在等。我们需要食物。
REESE: To fill my bowl, I put my ganache in,
里斯:为了填满碗，我把巧克力酱放进去，
put some almonds and pistachios,
放一些杏仁和开心果，
put a little more of ganache on top
在上面再放一点巧克力酱
and then sprinkle chicken in it.
然后把鸡肉撒进去。
AUDRA: Oh, God. These are gonna have to be done.
哦，天哪。这些都是必须要做的。
Audra, you really have to get plated.
奥德拉，你真的得去镀银了。
90 seconds left.
还剩90秒。
And I finally start pouring my lemon curd over my noodles.
我终于开始把柠檬凝乳倒在面条上。
-Audra, do you need any help? -Yes, yes, yes.
-Audra，你需要帮忙吗?-是的，是的，是的。
What do you need us to do? Jason and Keili come to help me.
你需要我们做什么?杰森和凯丽来帮我。
Can you dust my things with sugar, please?
你能在我的东西上撒点糖吗?
I'm adding green sugar to my chips
我在薯片里加绿糖
to kind of add a little spice.
为了增加一点情趣。
And Keili's just spooning sugar onto my mac and cheese.
凯莉正在往我的芝士通心粉上撒糖。
Hopefully that'll make it more sweet.
希望这会让它更甜。
-10. -9.
-10年。9。
Glitter finishes off anything you're making.
闪光剂可以完成你制作的任何东西。
-5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
-5 4 3 2 1。-5 4 3 2 1。
Hands up!
举起手来!
All right. Let's eat! I'm hungry.
好吧。让我们吃!我饿了。
VALERIE: Jason!
瓦莱丽:杰森!
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Oh, my God. You're such a character.
我的天啊。你真是个怪人。
I really hope they like my burrito.
我真希望他们喜欢我做的墨西哥卷饼。
And I really hope I didn't go overboard on chocolate again.
我真的希望我没有再次过度食用巧克力。
Well, it is a burrito.
嗯，这是墨西哥卷饼。
I made refried beans as chocolate.
我做了油炸豆做巧克力。
Then I have chicken as pound cake.
然后我要鸡肉磅蛋糕。
And then I have some buttercream like sour cream.
然后是酸奶油之类的奶油。
And then my wrap is made out of a crepe.
然后我的披肩是用可丽饼做的。
And then the chips that you see are a crepe
然后你看到的薯片是可丽饼
cut into triangles and then deep fried.
切成三角形，然后油炸。
-Uh, Jason, I have a question. -Yeah.
-杰森，我有个问题。-是的。
Last week, you made us boulders that were pure chocolate.
上周，你给我们做了纯巧克力巨石。
And so it looks like you gave us
看起来你给了我们
some mostly pure chocolate salsa.
有些是纯巧克力萨尔萨。
It doesn't really taste like chocolate chocolate
它尝起来不像巧克力巧克力
because it's milk chocolate.
因为这是牛奶巧克力。
-[ Laughs ] -Let's find out.
-[笑]-我们来看看。
Is it good, or is it bad?
是好是坏?
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary breakfast eggs sweeten up
解说员:普通早餐鸡蛋加糖
into a well-balanced dessert right after this.
变成了均衡的甜点。
ANNOUNCER: How to make fried-egg imposter cookies.
解说员:如何做假煎蛋饼干。
Gather together flour, sugar-cookie dough,
把面粉，糖饼干面团，
a rolling pin, an oval cookie cutter,
擀面杖，椭圆形饼干切刀，
white frosting, and canned apricot halves.
白糖霜，半杏罐头。
Flour your board.
在你的盘子上撒面粉。
Roll out the dough.
把面团擀开。
Cut out egg-shaped cookies and bake.
切出鸡蛋形状的饼干并烘烤。
Once cool, ice the whole cookie
冷却后，把整个饼干冰起来
with white frosting
白色的糖霜
and top with the apricots.
上面放上杏子。
Makes an egg-cellent dessert.
做一道很棒的甜点。
For more fun treats like this,
想要获得更多这样的乐趣，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
DUFF: Jason, it looks like you gave us
达夫:杰森，看起来你给了我们
a mostly pure chocolate salsa.
基本上是纯巧克力萨尔萨。
**
**
Is it good, or is it bad?
是好是坏?
That's delicious. I like it.
这是美味的。我喜欢它。
[ Laughter ] Yes! Yes!
(笑声)是的!是的!
-A lot of flavor. Yeah. -Oh, that's really good.
-很有味道。是的。-哦，那真的很好。
More flavor than you were hinting at.
比你说的更有味道。
Did you make your crepes, or did you --
你做的可丽饼，还是。
Uh, yeah. I made the crepes.
嗯,是的。我做了可丽饼。
You made the crepe batter, and you made the crepes?
你做了可丽饼面糊，还做了可丽饼?
-Yeah. -You tellin' stories?
-是的。-你在讲故事?
No.
不。
This is so good!
这太好吃了!
Oh, my gosh. It even looks like a burrito.
哦，我的天啊。它甚至看起来像墨西哥卷饼。
How fun is that?
多有趣啊?
For a crepe, this is very thick.
对于可丽饼来说，这太厚了。
-Mm-hmm.
-嗯。-嗯。
You know what? Thick or not thick,
你知道吗?厚或不厚，
-it's really tasty. -Thank you.
-真的很好吃。-谢谢。
Jason, I think that you just redeemed yourself
杰森，我觉得你刚刚救赎了自己
-from last week. -Yes.
-上周的。-是的。
I love the chocolate in here.
我喜欢这里的巧克力。
It's the right amount of chocolate this time.
这次是适量的巧克力。
I'm a fan of this burrito.
我很喜欢这个墨西哥卷饼。
-Thank you. -Good job, man.
-谢谢。-干得好，伙计。
Yes.
是的。
Aidan.
艾丹。
I made a meatball sub
我做了一个肉丸三明治
with pâte à choux for the bread
用面粉做面包
and brownies as the meatballs
布朗尼是肉丸子
and a chunky salsa
还有一大块萨尔萨酱
with watermelons, peaches, and mangos.
还有西瓜、桃子和芒果。
I love the shape of your tortillas.
我喜欢你做的玉米饼的形状。
-That's perfect. -Thanks.
这是完美的。-谢谢。
That fruit, on the other hand,
另一方面，这种水果
you want to season a little bit --
你想给它加点调料
little bit of lemon juice, little bit of sugar.
一点柠檬汁，一点糖。
-Yeah. -Tiny pinch of salt.
-是的。-一小撮盐。
I wish I did a better job on the salsa.
我真希望萨尔萨舞跳得更好。
**
**
This is amazing.
这太神奇了。
I mean, that looks like a meatball sandwich.
我是说，这看起来像肉丸三明治。
-Seriously. -That's a meatball sandwich.
认真对待。-这是肉丸三明治。
-Wow. Thank you. -You even eat it like a sub.
-哇。谢谢你！-你甚至像吃潜水艇一样吃。
I mean, look at that. You can pick it up.
我的意思是，看看那个。你可以把它捡起来。
-You can eat it, like -- -Yeah.
-你可以吃，就像-是啊
Duff ate it just like a meatball sub.
达夫把它当肉丸子潜水艇吃了。
And I'm really hoping that he likes it.
我真心希望他会喜欢。
That's a wicked-good brownie.
这是一个又坏又好的布朗尼。
Are you tryin' to get brownie points?
你是想要得到印象分吗?
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Boy, it's really good. It's not too sweet.
天啊，真的很好吃。不太甜。
-Yeah. -It just really looks
-是的。-看起来真的很像
like a meatball sub.
就像肉丸子潜水艇。
And it tastes really good, too.
而且味道也很好。
-Yeah. -Thank you, Aidan. Good job.
-是的。-谢谢你，艾登。好工作。
-Bye. -Great job.
再见。——工作。
Dude, that looks like a sandwich.
伙计，那看起来像个三明治。
Best looking so far.
目前为止最好看的。
Hi, Reese!
嗨,瑞茜!
My chili is made out of a chocolate ganache
我的辣椒酱是用巧克力甘纳许做的
with boiled almonds and cake.
还有煮杏仁和蛋糕。
The salsa is a raspberry compote
萨尔萨是一种覆盆子拼盘
with phyllo chips.
配肉片。
Your raspberry salsa,
你的覆盆子辣酱，
it's tangy in the right places, sweet in the right places.
恰到好处，恰到好处，恰到好处。
-Well done. -Thank you.
-嗯。-谢谢。
But you would have made a much more convincing chip
但你做的芯片会更有说服力
if the phyllo dough was thicker. Okay.
如果酥皮面团更厚。好吧。
-You know what I love? -What do you love, Duff?
-你知道我喜欢什么吗?-你喜欢什么，达夫?
I love that as soon as I saw this plate,
我喜欢这一点，我一看到这个盘子，
I was just like, "I don't know who made that.
我就说，“我不知道这是谁做的。
But whoever it was, they got chili."
但不管是谁，他们都吃了辣椒。”
Good job.
好工作。
Not a big fan of the nuts being boiled.
我不太喜欢煮坚果。
-Okay. -I think using the nuts
-好的。-我想用坚果
was a really good idea visually. Okay.
在视觉上真是个好主意。好吧。
I don't know if it was a good idea taste-wise.
我不知道这是不是个好主意。
All right, Reese. Thank you so much.
好吧，里斯。非常感谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Keili.
Keili。
So, it's a peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
这是花生酱和果冻三明治。
The bread is white cake.
面包是白蛋糕。
The jelly is purple buttercream.
果冻是紫色的奶油。
The salsa is chocolate melt.
萨尔萨酱是巧克力融化的。
And the chips are cake coated in cinnamon and sugar.
薯片是裹着肉桂和糖的蛋糕。
Keili, uh, you basically made a doughnut.
凯莉，你做了个甜甜圈。
There's, like, the cinnamon, the sugar.
有肉桂，还有糖。
It's fried. It's greasy.
它是油炸的。它是油腻。
-Okay. -It's delicious.
-好的。——它的美味。
I would have hoped that you did a little bit more with the salsa
我真希望你能多跳点萨尔萨舞
'cause when I think of salsa,
因为我一想到萨尔萨舞
I think it's got some liquid in there
我觉得里面有一些液体
to put your tortilla chip in there and soften it.
把玉米片放进去，让它变软。
Okay. I got some issues. I mean, you never make
好吧。我遇到了一些问题。我是说，你从来没有
a peanut butter and jelly sandwich with the heel.
花生酱果冻三明治加鞋跟。
Here's the deal.
事情是这样的。
The weird thing about this is it doesn't really look like
奇怪的是，它看起来并不像
a peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
花生酱和果冻三明治。
-But it tastes like one. -Is that good or bad?
但尝起来像。-这是好事还是坏事?
It's always good to confuse people.
迷惑别人总是好的。
Yeah. But I'm really easily confused.
是的。但是我真的很容易混淆。
-[ Laughs ] -Thank you.
-[笑]-谢谢。
Hey, Cole.
嘿,科尔。
I'm really hoping that this meatloaf imposter
我真希望这个肉饼骗子
will bring me to the top, if not win.
就算赢不了，也会把我带到巅峰。
So, for the meatloaf part,
那么，在做肉饼的时候，
it's chocolate cake infused with coffee
这是巧克力蛋糕加了咖啡
with a pecan topping for, like, meat texture.
上面放上山核桃，有肉的质感。
And the mashed potatoes are a banana buttercream
土豆泥是香蕉奶油
with a candy melt butter square.
用糖果融化黄油方块。
Tell me about your chips and salsa.
跟我说说你的薯片和莎莎。
For the chips, it's deep-fried puff pastry
炸薯片用的是油炸酥皮
tossed in cinnamon sugar.
加入肉桂糖。
And the salsa is mango and pineapple and lime.
莎莎酱是用芒果，菠萝和酸橙做的。
I got to tell you, that's --
我得告诉你，那真是
It's incredibly impressive looking.
它看起来令人印象深刻。
Thank you. Like, really impressive looking.
谢谢你！看起来真的令人印象深刻。
I have one little question, though.
不过我有一个小问题。
-Mm-hmm. -Why is it sparkling?
-嗯。-为什么是闪闪发光的?
Glitter makes everything better.
闪光能让一切变得更好。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Really well done.
做得很好。
But the glitter kind of takes me away from it.
但闪光让我有点心不在焉。
-Okay. -But, like,
-好的。但是,
your meatloaf is amazing looking.
你的肉饼真好看。
-Thank you. -This is amazing.
-谢谢。-太神奇了。
-It really looks like meatloaf. -Your mashed potatoes
-看起来真像肉饼。-你的土豆泥
with the pat of butter looks so good.
这一小块黄油看起来真不错。
Nice green beans.
不错的青豆。
-Mmm. -The cake's real nice.
-嗯。-蛋糕真好吃。
I mean, it's getting a good, deep chocolate flavor.
我是说，巧克力的味道越来越浓了。
I think you used the coffee right.
我觉得你的咖啡用对了。
Now, this is interesting. It is like a fruit salad.
这很有趣。它就像水果沙拉。
But, yet, this looks a little bit more like salsa...
但是，这看起来更像萨尔萨舞……
-Mm-hmm. -...except for the glitter.
-嗯。-…除了闪光。
Except for the pound of glitter in there.
除了里面那一磅亮片。
Really well, well done.
非常好，做得很好。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Hey, Kaniyah.
嘿,Kaniyah。
For my Dessert Imposter,
我的甜点冒名顶替者，
I have made a grilled cheese sandwich.
我做了一个烤奶酪三明治。
The bread is a almond cake.
面包是杏仁蛋糕。
The cheese is a almond paste dyed yellow.
奶酪是染成黄色的杏仁糊。
The salsa, I have blood-orange puree with coconut
莎莎酱，我有椰汁橙泥
and a little bit of cake crumbs on top.
再在上面放一点蛋糕屑。
-And what are the chips? -Phyllo dough...
-什么是筹码?蛋糕面团…
-Phyllo dough. -...dusted in sugar.
蛋糕的面团。-…撒上糖。
Okay.
好吧。
I don't think it looks like salsa.
我觉得它不像萨尔萨舞。
It looks like a big, globby mess.
它看起来像一个巨大的，全球性的混乱。
**
**
-Actually... -Yeah. It tastes pretty good.
其实是……-是的。味道不错。
It tastes really good.
味道真的很好。
Having said that, that looks just like a grilled cheese.
话虽如此，这看起来就像烤奶酪。
And it's a good, thick one, too.
而且还很好，很厚。
It's like Texas toast.
就像德州吐司。
That's what I said.
我就是这么说的。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
I love that you actually grilled your grilled cheese.
我喜欢你烤奶酪的样子。
I'm looking at Duff. And he's like this.
我在看达夫。他是这样的。
And this is gonna take forever.
这要花很长时间。
You eat it, you swallow it, and you like it.
你吃了它，吞了它，你喜欢它。
**
**
Wow.
哇。
You eat it, you swallow it, and you like it.
你吃了它，吞了它，你喜欢它。
**
**
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
He starts laughing at me.
他开始嘲笑我。
I'm wondering how many times
我在想有多少次
you've heard that in your lifetime.
这句话你肯定听过。
It's my parents' fault.
这是我父母的错。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
All right. This grilled cheese
好吧。这个烤奶酪
is delicious cake,
是美味的蛋糕，
-really, really good. -I love this.
-真的，真的很好。-我喜欢这个。
Got that great almond flavor to it.
有很棒的杏仁味。
-Yeah. -Yes.
-是的。-是的。
-This -- -This weirdness, however --
-这个-这个奇怪，然而
I don't know what's goin' on there.
我不知道这是怎么回事。
-Uh, yeah. -Thank you, Kaniyah.
-嗯,是的。-谢谢你，Kaniyah。
Thank y'all.
谢谢你们。
She said, "You eat it. You swallow it."
她说:“你吃吧。你把它吞下去。”
-"You like it."
-“你喜欢。”-“你喜欢。”
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Wow.
哇。
Audra!
Audra !
Well, I made deconstructed lemon pie,
我做了解构柠檬派，
which is my mac and cheese,
这是我的MAC和奶酪，
and a passion-fruit candy salsa
还有一份西番莲糖辣酱
with pie dough chips.
配上薄饼。
This salsa, it looks like tomato soup
这个莎莎酱，看起来像西红柿汤
with crackers in it.
里面有饼干。
Hey, wait a minute.
嘿，等一下。
-What's up? -They're good.
什么啦?他们很好。
It's tart. I like it.
这是馅饼。我喜欢它。
So, this is your mac and cheese?
这就是你的芝士通心粉吗?
Yeah.
是的。
It doesn't look delicious.
看起来不好吃。
I know.
我知道。
It says sort of mac and cheese to me.
对我来说好像是芝士通心粉。
I'm gonna taste it.
我要尝尝。
Whoa!
哇!
-It's really sweet. -Um...
-真贴心。-恩……
-The pie dough tasted good. -Yeah?
-馅饼皮尝起来很好吃。-是吗?
But you had the super, super, sweet, sweet,
但你有超级，超级，甜蜜，甜蜜，
sweet, sweet lemon curd.
甜甜的，甜甜的柠檬凝乳。
-And then it goes, mm, bitter. -Mm.
-然后，嗯，苦。毫米。
You know, zesting the lemon, think you probably had
你知道，给柠檬调味，我想你可能已经
too much pith in there and too much sugar.
里面的髓和糖都太多了。
I would say keep this recipe.
我会说保留这个食谱。
And then, next time you make it, take some of the sugar out.
下次做的时候，把糖拿出来。
-Okay. Thank you. -Thank you, Audra.
-好的。谢谢你！-谢谢你，奥德拉。
Justice!
正义!
Dude, this chicken looks amazing.
伙计，这鸡看起来棒极了。
I made a lemon cake,
我做了一个柠檬蛋糕，
and then I made a gum paste bone.
然后我做了一个口香糖糊骨头。
And I have some barbecue sauce,
我还有一些烧烤酱，
which is also blackberry jam.
这也是黑莓果酱。
All right. How'd you make this salsa?
好吧。你是怎么做这个萨尔萨的?
I did watermelon and green apple puree.
我做了西瓜青苹果泥。
And I chopped some mint on top.
我还在上面切了些薄荷。
Yeah. I mean, lookin' like salsa.
是的。我是说，看起来像萨尔萨。
I would have liked to have had the chips seasoned.
我本想把薯条调味的。
But it's the best-looking salsa of the day.
但这是今天最好看的萨尔萨舞。
I don't know if it's the best tasting.
我不知道这是不是最好的味道。
Dude, this chicken looks amazing.
伙计，这鸡看起来棒极了。
It is. It looks like a chicken leg.
它是。它看起来像鸡腿。
Let's slice into this.
我们来切一下。
[ Laughing ] What are you doing?
(笑)你在干什么?
Got a chicken leg.
我有一条鸡腿。
I'm excited about it.
我对此很兴奋。
-Mmm! -Mmm.
-嗯!-嗯。
This cake is so moist.
这蛋糕太湿了。
The lemon is not overpowering.
柠檬的味道并不浓烈。
It's a very subtle lemon flavor.
这是一种非常微妙的柠檬味。
With the jam on top
上面有果酱
and then the graham crackers,
然后是全麦饼干，
it all kind of goes together and looks like a chicken leg.
这些都放在一起，看起来像鸡腿。
-Spot on, man. -Thank you.
-没错，老兄。-谢谢。
Hey, Dylin.
嘿,Dylin。
My Dessert Imposter was a hot dog.
我的甜点冒名顶替者是热狗。
I made a classic vanilla cake.
我做了一个经典的香草蛋糕。
And I made that into the hot dog bun.
我把它放进了热狗面包里。
And for my hot dog, I put pink buttercream.
至于我的热狗，我放了粉色的奶油。
And I know Duff hates it,
我知道达夫不喜欢
but ketchup is red buttercream.
但是番茄酱是红色的奶油。
I like ketchup on my hot dog, ketchup and mustard.
我喜欢在热狗上涂番茄酱，番茄酱和芥末。
-Ketchup and mustard. -We used to be friends.
-番茄酱和芥末。-我们以前是朋友。
-[ Laughs ] -Tell me about your salsa.
-[笑]-跟我说说你的萨尔萨舞。
My salsa is diced sweet cherries, apples,
我的辣酱是甜樱桃丁，苹果丁，
and then I added a little bit of red dye
然后我加了一点红色染料
so it would be a dark red.
所以应该是深红色。
And that is my chipotle sauce.
这就是我的墨西哥辣椒酱。
And then for my chips,
至于我的薯片，
they are triangular-shaped phyllo dough.
它们是三角形的酥皮面团。
Huh. Okay.
嗯。好吧。
Mmm. I like the cherries.
嗯。我喜欢樱桃。
I think we could've backed off
我想我们本可以放手的
on the red dye just a little bit.
在红色染料上涂一点。
I think if this color would have been
我想如果这个颜色是
a little bit different and the chips a little firmer,
有点不同，薯片也更结实，
you would've knocked it out of the park.
你一定会很出色的。
All right. Well, let's get into your hot dog.
好吧。我们来吃你的热狗吧。
I've been watching you bake for a couple of weeks now.
我已经看你烤面包好几周了。
And I think that you're a lot more creative than this.
我觉得你比这更有创意。
I think that you could've done a little bit more,
我觉得你可以再多做一点，
because, right now, I got cake and buttercream.
因为我现在有蛋糕和奶油。
And that's it.
就是这样。
Your bun kind of looks like
你的发髻看起来像
you just sort of tore it off the cake
你把它从蛋糕上扯下来了
and relatively quickly kind of mashed it into shape.
相对较快地把它弄成形状。
I'm wondering how long you left your cake in the oven.
我想知道你的蛋糕在烤箱里烤了多久。
It could've used a good extra 10 minutes.
本来可以多花十分钟的。
Yeah. It's a little under-baked.
是的。有点不熟。
Although...that's some tasty buttercream.
尽管……那是一些美味的奶油。
-Thank you. -Thank you, Dylin.
-谢谢。-谢谢你，迪林。
-Thank you so much, man. -Thank you.
-太谢谢你了，伙计。-谢谢。
I just wanted a little more.
我只是想要更多一点。
Hmm, roast-beef sandwich. Want to bring in Maya?
嗯，烤牛肉三明治。想把玛雅带来吗?
-Yes, please. -Hey, Maya.
是的,请。-嘿,玛雅。
MAYA: Walking into judging, I'm, like, shivering.
玛雅:开始评判的时候，我浑身发抖。
I have butterflies in my stomach,
我忐忑不安，
a lot of things wrong with me.
我有很多问题。
**
**
-Hi, Maya. -Hi.
-你好,玛雅。-你好。
All right. So, Maya, you got roast beef sandwich?
好吧。玛雅，你有烤牛肉三明治吗?
-Yes. -Tell me about it.
-是的。-跟我说说。
The bread is white cake.
面包是白蛋糕。
The beef is brownies.
牛肉是布朗尼蛋糕。
And the lettuce is coconut flakes dyed green.
生菜是染成绿色的椰子片。
And then the tomatoes are raspberries.
西红柿是覆盆子。
And then for my salsa and chips,
然后我的莎莎酱和薯条，
you have crepes
你有可丽饼
sprinkled in cinnamon sugar, deep fried.
撒上肉桂糖，油炸。
And then for the salsa you have, um,
做萨尔萨舞的时候，
coconut flakes dyed green with cherries.
用樱桃染成绿色的椰子片。
-The chips are good. -I think the chips are good.
-薯片很好。-我觉得薯条不错。
But they do look like ridged potato chips, though.
但它们看起来确实像脊状薯片。
Okay. So this is your salsa?
好吧。这就是你的萨尔萨舞?
-Yeah. -Now, your salsa
-是的。-现在，你的萨尔萨舞
looks suspiciously like the lettuce...
看起来很像生菜……
-Mm-hmm. -...on your sandwich.
-嗯。-…在你的三明治上。
Did you use the same stuff?
你们用的是同样的东西吗?
-Yes. -Why?
-是的。-为什么?
I didn't really have enough time.
我真的没有足够的时间。
I'm not real crazy about the salsa.
我不是很喜欢萨尔萨舞。
Yeah. I think this might be the weakest part of your plate.
是的。我觉得这可能是你盘子里最薄弱的部分。
Yeah.
是的。
This looks roast beef sandwich-ish.
这看起来像烤牛肉三明治。
But it looks more like
但它看起来更像
a piece of cake cut into a pie shape.
切成馅饼状的一块蛋糕。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
This cake is so moist,
这蛋糕太湿了
so yummy, cooked perfectly.
太好吃了，煮得很完美。
I'm wondering why you didn't put more brownie in
我在想你为什么不多放点巧克力饼进去
so you see the roast beef.
你看到烤牛肉了。
If I get a roast beef sandwich like this at the deli,
如果我在熟食店买到这样的烤牛肉三明治，
I'm -- I'm givin' it back,
我要把它还给你
'cause, like, there's not enough roast beef on here, you know?
因为这里的烤牛肉不够，你知道吗?
Yeah. When you get a roast beef, it's like 2/3 roast beef,
是的。烤牛肉差不多有2/3的烤牛肉，
-1/3 bread. -Mm-hmm.
1/3的面包。-嗯。
Thanks, Maya.
谢谢你,玛雅。
**
**
Bakers, today we asked you
面包师们，今天我们问你们
to create Dessert Imposters
制作甜点骗子
that looked like comfort foods
那看起来像是安慰食物
but tasted like dessert.
但尝起来像甜点。
And there were three imposters
有三个骗子
that were really, really great.
那真是太棒了。
Aidan, you made an incredible meatball sub.
艾登，你做的肉丸潜水艇棒极了。
Not only did it look good,
不仅看起来不错，
you filled it with wicked-good brownies.
你用邪恶的巧克力蛋糕填满了它。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
-Cole. -Yes!
科尔。-是的!
Your meatloaf and mashed potatoes were amazing.
你的肉卷和土豆泥太好吃了。
You hit every detail.
你做到了每一个细节。
-Excellent work. -Thank you.
优秀的工作。-谢谢。
Jason, you served your burrito in aluminum foil
杰森，你的卷饼是用铝箔包起来的
just like a real burrito.
就像一个真正的墨西哥卷饼。
You actually balanced the chocolate very well.
你的巧克力搭配得很好。
-Chocolate. -[ Laughs ]
巧克力。——(笑)
And your crepe was a really smart tortilla imposter.
你的可丽饼是个很聪明的墨西哥薄饼骗子。
**
**
Now, one baker's dish earned a five-star review.
现在，一个面包师的菜获得了五星好评。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
Please be me.
请做我吧。
-...Jason. -Yay!
-…杰森。耶!
Good job, Jason.
干得好，杰森。
-You did it. -Good job, Jason.
-你做到了。-干得好，杰森。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
Monster comeback, my man.
怪物回来了，伙计。
That is a big leap from bottom three
这是从倒数第三名的飞跃
to the winner of the challenge.
敬挑战的赢家。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Now, there were some bakers
这里有一些面包师
whose Dessert Imposters had a few flaws
谁的甜点冒名顶替者有一些缺点
but were good enough to fool us at first glance.
但它们很好，第一眼就能骗过我们。
Those bakers are Justice,
那些面包师是正义，
-Kaniyah... -Yes.
-Kaniyah……-是的。
Keili, and...
Keili,…
Reese.
瑞茜。
Unfortunately, that leaves Audra, Dylin, and Maya.
不幸的是，只剩下奥德拉，迪林和玛雅。
Please step forward.
请往前走。
AUDRA: No. Not Maya.
AUDRA:没有。不是玛雅。
Audra, your deconstructed lemon pie
Audra，你的解构柠檬派
macaroni and cheese was overly sweet
通心粉和奶酪太甜了
and bitter at the same time.
同时也很苦。
Made it a little hard to eat.
吃起来有点难。
Dylin, your hot dog approach
迪林，你的热狗方法
wasn't super creative.
不是很有创意。
You used buttercream for the hot dog
你用奶油做热狗
and all the condiments.
还有所有的调味品。
And your cake bun was really under-baked.
你的小圆面包烤得太烂了。
Maya, your roast-beef sandwich
玛雅，你的烤牛肉三明治
didn't really fool anyone,
骗不了任何人，
especially since it hardly had any brownie roast beef.
尤其是店里几乎没有烤牛肉布朗尼。
The baker that will be going home is...
要回家的面包师是……
**
**
...Dylin.
……Dylin。
Sorry, man.
对不起,男人。
You were awesome to watch.
你太棒了。
-Great job. -We're really gonna miss you.
——工作。-我们会很想你的。
Sorry, Dylin.
对不起,Dylin。
DYLIN: There's one thing I've learned in the kitchen.
我在厨房里学到了一件事。
And that's I'm not just any kid.
我不是一个普通的孩子。
I'm also a talented and amazing baker.
我还是个才华横溢的面包师。
Bye, guys.
再见,各位。
ANNOUNCER: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
“儿童烘焙锦标赛”前情提要……
Here are the comfort-food classics
以下是经典的安慰食物
that you are gonna be turning into...
你会变成…
ALL: Dessert and pasta!
全体:甜点和意大利面!
WOMAN: With a little side of chips and salsa.
还有一点薯片和莎莎酱。
But I already have a side.
但我已经有立场了。
WOMAN: Oh, my gosh.
女:哦，我的天哪。
Jason, I think that you just redeemed yourself.
杰森，我觉得你刚刚救赎了自己。
Yes!
是的!
I'm a fan of this burrito.
我很喜欢这个墨西哥卷饼。
Now, one baker earned a five-star review --
现在，一个面包师获得了五星好评
Jason.
杰森。
Yeah!
是啊!
MAN: Dylan, I think that you're a lot more creative than this.
男:迪伦，我认为你比这更有创造力。
The baker that will be going home is Dylan.
要回家的面包师是迪伦。
Wow.
哇。
Oh.
哦。
Oh, my gosh!
哦，天哪!
KANIYAH: We are walking into the kitchen.
我们正走进厨房。
And we see this '80s stuff.
我们看到了80年代的东西。
I'm 10 years old. I was born in 2006.
我10岁了。我出生于2006年。
What is the '80s to me?
80年代对我来说是什么?
Oh! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
哦!我的天啊!我的天啊!
'60s clothes!
60年代的衣服!
Hi, bakers.
嗨,面包师。
ALL: Hi!
:嗨!
You're lookin' groovy.
你看起来棒极了。
Groovy.
Groovy。
Bakers, you're probably wondering
你可能在想面包师们
why we're wearing tie-dye.
为什么我们要扎染。
Pretty much.
差不多。
Fact is, colorful cakes are incredible popular...
事实上，五颜六色的蛋糕非常受欢迎……
Oh, yeah.
哦,是的。
Especially tie-dye cakes.
尤其是扎染蛋糕。
ALL: Yay!
:耶!
I've made tie-dye cakes before.
我以前做过扎染蛋糕。
And they look pretty swagger.
他们看起来很神气。
For your big bake, bakers,
烘焙师们，
you have two hours to make a tie-dye cake
你有两个小时做扎染蛋糕
bursting with color and...
五彩缤纷……
-Flavor! -...flavor.
味道!-…味道。
-Flavor.
味道!味道。
All right. And your baking time starts...
好吧。你的烘焙时间开始了…
-now! -Now!
-现在!-现在!
Glitter, rainbow glitter.
闪闪发光，彩虹闪闪发光。
4 ounces is one stick. 6 ounces of butter.
4盎司是一根。6盎司黄油。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
I was one of the last ones here.
我是最后一批来的。
I know the '60s were all about peace and love.
我知道60年代是和平与爱的年代。
But right now, all I'm feeling
但现在，我的感觉是
is the pressure to get this cake done perfectly.
就是要把蛋糕做好的压力。
Orange.
橙色。
I'm making an orange-flavored tie-dye cake
我在做橙味扎染蛋糕
with an orange buttercream.
配上橙色奶油。
Audra's got a big bottle of orange extract over there.
奥德拉那边有一大瓶橙汁。
Extract is intense, only to be used sparingly.
提取物是强烈的，只能谨慎使用。
First, I cream together my butter and shortening.
首先，我把黄油和起酥油搅在一起。
Then I add in my sugar, eggs, buttermilk, and my whole milk
然后加入糖、鸡蛋、酪乳和全脂牛奶
and combine it with my orange extract.
把它和橙汁混合。
Orange extract.
橙色的提取。
-Wow. -Eeh!
-哇。-Eeh !
Perfect.
完美的。
Then I add my flour...
然后加入面粉…
A little flour mixture
一点面粉混合物
...and my milk mixture to my other wet ingredients.
…还有牛奶混合物和其他湿食材。
Audra, how are you doing?
奥德拉，你好吗?
Um, fine.
嗯,很好。
For today's bake,
今天的烘焙，
I'm gonna make an apple-cinnamon cake.
我要做一个苹果肉桂蛋糕。
There we go.
好了。
I had never added apples into my cake before.
我以前从来没有在蛋糕里加过苹果。
I'm not sure if that's gonna affect the baking time.
我不确定这是否会影响烘焙时间。
But I'm pretty sure it'll turn out fine
但我很确定结果会很好
because it'll give it that flavor that I need.
因为这样会有我想要的味道。
-Jason. -Yeah?
杰森。-是吗?
What type of cake are you gonna make?
你要做什么样的蛋糕?
I'm just making, like, a vanilla cake recipe.
我在做香草蛋糕的食谱。
And then for the flavor, I'm probably gonna make,
至于味道，我可能会做，
like, um, puree or something.
就像，呃，果汁之类的。
Oh, cool!
哦,太酷了!
JASON: Last week built my confidence quite a bit
杰森:上周我的信心大增
because I got first place! Yeah!
因为我得了第一名!是啊!
Now it's nice and smooth.
现在它又好又顺滑。
Duff and Valerie said
达夫和瓦莱丽说
that we have to have both color and flavor.
颜色和味道都要兼顾。
I have a good plan for that.
我有个好计划。
I'm gonna make a strawberry puree
我要做草莓泥
and add that into my batter.
把它加到面糊里。
Mmm. This is gonna be delicious.
嗯。这一定很好吃。
Baking a tie-dyed cake
烤扎染蛋糕
is pretty much the same thing as baking a regular cake.
和烤普通蛋糕差不多。
I divide the batter into three bowls.
我把面糊分成三碗。
I dye the first one red with the strawberry puree,
我用草莓泥把第一个染成红色，
the middle one blue, and the last one green
中间的是蓝色的，最后的是绿色的
and layer the different colors on top of each other.
然后把不同的颜色叠加在一起。
I get a toothpick and start spreading
我拿起牙签开始撒
out the colors just a little bit
稍微调一下颜色
and just bake it like a normal cake.
就像普通蛋糕一样烤。
-Hi, Kaniyah! -Hello.
-你好,Kaniyah !-你好。
I see you're separating your batters already. Yeah.
我看你已经把击球手分开了。是的。
What flavor of cake are you making?
你在做什么口味的蛋糕?
I am making a vanilla cake.
我正在做香草蛋糕。
Have you made a tie-dyed cake before?
你以前做过扎染蛋糕吗?
I have not. But I know what they look like.
我没有。但我知道他们长什么样。
I have seen many people
我见过很多人
make tie-dye cakes on the Internet.
在网上做扎染蛋糕。
So let's see how this turns out.
我们来看看结果如何。
Have at it. Have fun.
试试吧。玩得开心。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
I like me cake. And I like me colors.
我喜欢我的蛋糕。我喜欢我的颜色。
Roy G. Biv, which means red, orange, yellow,
Roy G. Biv，意思是红色，橙色，黄色，
green, blue, indigo, and violet.
绿色，蓝色，靛蓝和紫色。
VALERIE: We're looking for a tie-dye cake
瓦莱丽:我们在找扎染蛋糕
bursting with color
色彩缤纷
sort of like Duff's shirt, lots of color.
有点像达夫的衬衫，颜色很丰富。
That it is.
没错。
I do like Duff's shirt. It's really, really neon.
我确实喜欢达夫的衬衫。它真的是氖气。
I don't know what happened to all the hippies.
我不知道那些嬉皮士怎么了。
But I'm pretty sure it just, like, it got outta style.
但我很确定，它有点过时了。
Does anybody have the cake flour?
有人有蛋糕粉吗?
AIDAN: I have cake flour. I just got it.
艾丹:我有蛋糕粉。我刚拿到。
Can I use it?
我可以用它吗?
Yes. Yeah. Take it.
是的。是的。把它。
REESE: I am making a tie-dye yellow-and-white cake
里斯:我在做一个扎染的黄白蛋糕
with an American buttercream.
加上美式奶油。
My inspiration comes from a tie-dye shirt
我的灵感来自一件扎染衬衫
that I made for my fourth-grade graduation.
那是我为四年级毕业做的
Reese, what you making?
里斯，你在做什么?
I'm making a white cake right now.
我现在正在做一个白蛋糕。
You haven't made your cake batter yet?
你还没做好蛋糕面糊吗?
I have. I made a yellow cake.
我有。我做了一个黄色的蛋糕。
Oh, okay. So you're making two different kinds of batter? Yeah.
哦,好的。所以你在做两种不同的面糊?是的。
Okay. All right. All right.
好吧。好吧。好吧。
I'm making two different batters
我在做两种不同的击球手
because I think that'll impress the judges.
因为我觉得这会给评委留下深刻印象。
Is anything in the oven yet?
烤箱里有东西了吗?
Not yet.
还没有。
Okay. Are you worried about that?
好吧。你担心这个吗?
No.
不。
No? I am.
没有?我是。
Good luck, man. [ Chuckles ]
祝你好运，伙计。[笑]
Thank you.
谢谢你！
This looks really good. I'm, like, so excited.
看起来真不错。我太兴奋了。
I am making a vanilla tie-dye cake
我在做香草扎染蛋糕
with a vanilla buttercream.
加香草奶油。
In the first challenge,
在第一个挑战中，
the judges loved my tie-dye cakes.
评委们很喜欢我的扎染蛋糕。
So I'm just gonna stick with the same recipe.
所以我还是沿用原来的做法。
Love this color.
我喜欢这个颜色。
When the judges eat this cake,
当评委们吃这个蛋糕时，
I want them to feel like they're on a unicorn
我想让他们觉得自己骑在独角兽上
jumping over a rainbow.
跳过彩虹。
I'm using one cake pan instead of two
我用的是一个烤盘而不是两个
because I don't have enough.
因为我的钱不够。
I'm a little nervous.
我有点紧张。
But I'm just gonna go with it.
但我还是要顺其自然。
Please bake.
请烤。
Does anybody have food coloring I can use?
谁有我可以用的食用色素?
Oh, food coloring? Yeah.
哦，食用色素?是的。
I'm about to get to the coloring stage.
我要开始上色了。
I like to bake with a lot of colors at home,
我喜欢在家里用不同的颜色烘烤，
just, like, with my signature "crayon-melt cake."
就配上我的招牌"蜡笔融化蛋糕"
I took a fondant cake
我拿了一块软糖蛋糕
and dripped food coloring down the sides.
然后往边上滴食用色素。
That's good.
这很好。
I'm making a tie-dye cake
我在做扎染蛋糕
Mm, delicious.
嗯,很好吃。
...with strawberry, orange, lemon, and lime.
…加草莓、橘子、柠檬和酸橙。
When they take a bite, with each flavor,
当他们咬一口，每种味道，
I think it's gonna really pop.
我觉得会很流行的。
Gosh, I need to get these in the oven stat.
天啊，我得马上把这些放进烤箱。
Blue.
蓝色的。
Today, I'm making tie-dye white cakes
今天，我要做扎染白糕
with some airbrush fondant.
加上一些喷枪软糖。
This is the perfect challenge for me
这对我来说是个完美的挑战
because I love making cakes.
因为我喜欢做蛋糕。
Groovy, man.
Groovy中,男人。
I'm making a vanilla-strawberry cake
我在做香草草莓蛋糕
because I think those flavors go really good with tie-dye.
因为我觉得这些味道和扎染很搭。
I've never used strawberry powder in a cake.
我从没在蛋糕里放过草莓粉。
And I've never used it at all in baking.
我从来没有在烘焙中使用过它。
But I hope that this will work.
但我希望这能奏效。
I'm looking around,
我环顾四周，
and everyone else has their cakes in the oven.
每个人的蛋糕都在烤箱里。
I'm thinking, "Why am I so slow?"
我在想，“为什么我这么慢?”
Can we have your attention, bakers?
请注意了，面包师们?
Oh, no.
哦,不。
What is going on?
发生了什么事?
You guys in the mood for a little twist?
你们想不想来个小转折?
-No. -No!
-不。-不!
Tie-dye is so colorful and cool.
扎染是如此的多彩和凉爽。
So we thought, "What would go with a tie-dye cake?
所以我们想，“扎染蛋糕配什么?”
Something with a swirl maybe?"
也许是带漩涡的东西?”
Oh, no.
哦,不。
Why?
为什么?
Bakers, you must make swirled ice cream...
面包师们，你们一定要做漩涡冰淇淋……
Uh!
哦!
...to go with your tie-dye cake.
…来配你的扎染蛋糕。
Swirly, twirly.
纠结的,急速旋转。
* Ice cream, cake and cake *
冰淇淋、蛋糕和蛋糕
Everything is the worst twist ever.
一切都是最糟糕的转折。
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo !
KANIYAH: We have to make swirl ice cream.
我们要做漩涡冰淇淋。
No!
不!
[ Sobs ]
[啜泣]
What did we do to them?
我们对他们做了什么?
Peace out, bakers.
别闹了，面包师们。
VALERIE: 90 minutes left, bakers!
瓦莱丽:还有90分钟，面包师们!
30 minutes have gone bye-bye.
30分钟过去了，再见。
Ugh. Worst twist ever.
啊。史上最糟糕的转折。
First, we had to make a tie-dye cake,
首先，我们要做一个扎染蛋糕，
which is already hard enough.
这已经够难的了。
Ah, hot pink.
啊，粉红的。
Now, we have to make an ice cream
现在，我们要做一个冰淇淋
with a swirl in it?
里面有漩涡吗?
What did we do to them?
我们对他们做了什么?
I know, right?
我知道，对吧?
Even cakes.
即使是蛋糕。
Hi, Justice.
嗨,正义。
Are you done with the food coloring?
食用色素用完了吗?
Um, not yet.
嗯，还没有。
-Can I borrow it? -Um, soon.
-我能借用一下吗?-恩,很快。
Before I start working on my ice cream,
在我开始做冰淇淋之前，
I need to start getting my batter dyed
我得开始给面糊染色了
and into my pans.
放进我的锅里。
For the, um, swirl, I use a toothpick.
我用牙签来做漩涡。
And I just swirl around so, like, the colors are a tie-dye.
我只是旋转，就像扎染一样。
In the '60s, everyone was a hippie.
在60年代，每个人都是嬉皮士。
And they hugged trees.
他们拥抱树木。
And they ran wild through the forests and went
他们狂奔着穿过森林，走了
like, "I love nature."
比如，“我爱大自然。”
I bet it was, like, so cool.
我猜一定很酷吧。
KEILI: When I think of a tie-dye cake,
凯丽:当我想到扎染蛋糕时，
I think of a lot of colors and a lot of flavors.
我想到了很多颜色和很多味道。
So for my red, I'm gonna add in raspberry coulis.
所以我要加入覆盆子酱。
For my yellow, I'm gonna add in lemon juice
做黄色的，我要加柠檬汁
and yellow food dye.
黄色食用染料。
That is done.
这就完成了。
All right, so Keili's putting
好了，凯里在推杆
a lot of extra stuff in her batter.
她的面糊里有很多多余的东西。
I don't know how that's gonna work out.
我不知道这能有什么结果。
Here we go.
开始吧。
COLE: To make my ice cream base, in a sauce pan,
科尔:为了做我的冰淇淋底，在平底锅里，
I mix my cream and my milk.
我把奶油和牛奶混合在一起。
In a separate bowl,
在另一个碗里，
I whisk together my egg yolks and sugar
我把蛋黄和糖搅拌在一起
until it's pale in color and really smooth
直到颜色变淡，非常光滑
when you, like, lift up the whisk.
当你举起打蛋器的时候。
My milk-and-cream mixture is now to a simmer.
我的牛奶和奶油混合物现在要小火煮了。
So I can ladle a quarter of it into the egg-yolk mixture
所以我可以舀四分之一到蛋黄混合物里
and whisk it to temper the eggs.
然后搅拌，使鸡蛋回火。
It means to get your egg yolks to a certain temperature
意思是让蛋黄达到一定的温度
that the cream mixture's in
奶油混合物进去了
so that you don't scramble your eggs.
这样你就不会炒鸡蛋了。
And heat it until it coats the back of a wooden spoon.
然后加热，直到它覆盖在木勺的背面。
And you can go...
你可以去……
I don't wanna make a boring swirl.
我不想做无聊的漩涡。
So I'm gonna make a strawberry- mango-and-passion-fruit swirl.
所以我要做一个草莓芒果百香果漩涡。
It's gonna be, like, a Hawaiian breeze on a sunny day
就像阳光灿烂的日子里，夏威夷的微风
in my ice cream.
在我的冰淇淋里。
Cole is my biggest competition.
科尔是我最大的竞争对手。
He already has his fruit swirl going and his ice cream base.
他已经开始做水果漩涡和冰淇淋底了。
So I'm rushing to get everything working.
所以我急着让一切正常运转。
Milk, cream, sugar.
牛奶，奶油，糖。
For my ice cream,
为了我的冰淇淋，
I'm going to make a simple vanilla base.
我要做一个简单的香草底。
And I'm going to swirl in some raspberry,
我要加入一些覆盆子，
maybe some passion fruit.
也许来点百香果。
I'm really worried about just, like, I'm kind of behind.
我真的很担心，我有点落后了。
And you're, like, so ahead.
而你，遥遥领先。
I still need to finish my ice cream, make my frosting,
我还得吃完冰淇淋，做糖霜，
decorate my cake and glaze my cake.
装饰我的蛋糕，给蛋糕上釉。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
One hour left, bakers.
还有一个小时，面包师们。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
Blast chiller time.
冷却时间。
VALERIE: We're looking for a tie-dye cake
瓦莱丽:我们在找扎染蛋糕
bursting with color.
色彩缤纷。
It's ice cream time.
冰淇淋时间到了。
I've made ice cream before.
我以前做过冰淇淋。
I've never made ice cream with an ice cream swirl.
我从来没做过冰淇淋漩涡。
That might be my downfall.
这可能是我的缺点。
Perfect!
完美!
I'm gonna make a raspberry jelly.
我要做覆盆子果冻。
So I grab some raspberries
所以我拿了一些覆盆子
and put them in pot with a little bit water
把它们放进锅里，加一点水
and a little bit of sugar.
再加一点糖。
I wait for it to boil down.
我等着它煮沸。
And then I put some cornstarch and water.
然后我放一些玉米淀粉和水。
So Jason's doing something really interesting.
杰森在做一件很有趣的事。
He's mixing cornstarch and water
他正把玉米淀粉和水混合在一起
with either a jam or a jelly.
用果酱或果冻。
And then he's gonna freeze it. It's gonna be like...
然后他会把它冻起来。就像…
Hmm.
嗯。
...jam-flavored gum.
…jam-flavored口香糖。
What color did I not use? Purple, purple, purple.
我没有用什么颜色?紫色，紫色，紫色。
One hour left and I'm still scooping
只剩一个小时了，我还在挖
my cake batter into the pans.
把蛋糕糊倒进锅里。
At this point, I wish I only made one cake batter.
在这一点上，我希望我只做了一个蛋糕面糊。
This took way too much time.
这花了太多时间。
MAYA: No scrambled eggs, no scrambled eggs.
玛雅:不要炒蛋，不要炒蛋。
For my ice cream twist,
为了制作我的冰淇淋，
I am making a vanilla ice cream
我在做香草冰淇淋
with a raspberry syrup.
加覆盆子糖浆。
I don't really love Duff and Valerie's twist.
我不太喜欢达夫和瓦莱丽的把戏。
I don't really like ice cream at all.
我一点也不喜欢冰淇淋。
I know kids normally like ice cream and candy
我知道孩子们通常喜欢冰淇淋和糖果
and all that happiness and sugar.
还有所有的快乐和糖。
I don't.
我不喜欢。
It comes out, and it's like soft-serve ice cream.
它出来了，就像软冰淇淋一样。
I feel, like, so relieved.
我感到如释重负。
[ Vocalizes ]
[发声]
Finally, I have a good ice cream.
最后，我有一个好的冰淇淋。
KANIYAH: My cake looks ready.
我的蛋糕看起来好了。
So I take it out, and I flip it over.
我把它拿出来，把它翻过来。
I level the top.
我把顶部弄平了。
And it's not done.
但这并没有完成。
What is happening with Kaniyah's cake?
Kaniyah的蛋糕怎么了?
She looks like she is freaking out.
她看起来吓坏了。
[ Sniffles ]
[流鼻涕]
I have to pull myself together
我必须振作起来
and get this cake back in the oven
把蛋糕放回烤箱里
for it to bake all the way through.
让它烤透。
Stupid cake!
愚蠢的蛋糕!
Now that my cakes are in the oven,
现在蛋糕已经在烤箱里了，
I need to start my ice cream.
我要开始吃冰淇淋了。
I cut my vanilla bean and scrape the seeds out.
我把香草豆切开，把籽刮掉。
The inside is the best part.
里面是最好的部分。
And put that into my pot with my heavy cream and my milk.
把它和浓奶油和牛奶一起放进锅里。
And then I add my eggs and sugar.
然后加入鸡蛋和糖。
As I stir, it comes back to a simmer.
当我搅拌的时候，它又变成了小火。
So now I'm gonna strain it.
现在我要把它滤一下。
It's, like, really curdled.
它真的凝结了。
This is gonna be disgusting.
这会很恶心的。
I cannot serve this to the judges.
我不能把这个呈给评委。
REESE: I'm inspecting my ice cream base.
里斯:我在检查我的冰淇淋底。
And I see that all of my ice cream is curdled.
我看到我所有的冰淇淋都凝固了。
I cannot serve this to the judges.
我不能把这个呈给评委。
I'm already behind on time.
我已经迟到了。
And now, I have to make a whole nother ice cream.
现在，我得再做一个冰激凌。
Heavy cream.
奶油。
AUDRA: Have to make my ice cream base.
我要做冰淇淋底。
I did try to make ice cream once.
我曾经试过做冰淇淋。
But it just turned out liquid.
但是它变成了液体。
For my swirl, I get some white chocolate,
要做旋流，我要一些白巧克力，
melt that in a bowl.
把它放在碗里融化。
And then I add some orange extract.
然后加入一些橙汁。
This has to taste like orange.
这个要尝起来像橘子。
I'm not really satisfied with the color.
我对这个颜色不太满意。
So I add some orange food dye.
所以我加了一些橙色的食用染料。
I like it.
我喜欢它。
I go back to check on my ice cream.
我回去检查我的冰淇淋。
And it's time to get it out of the machine.
是时候把它从机器里拿出来了。
Ah, that's so awesome. To add the swirl,
啊，太棒了。为了加入漩涡，
I put some of my white chocolate onto the ice cream.
我把一些白巧克力放在冰淇淋上。
And I take a toothpick and kind of swirl it in.
我用牙签把它旋进去。
My ice cream looks unreal when it's coming out.
我的冰淇淋出来的时候看起来不真实。
I sort of wish that I could just stop and eat some.
我真希望我能停下来吃点。
But I can't.
但是我不能。
And I go back to my station. And I add in my cinnamon.
然后我回到我的工作岗位。然后加入肉桂粉。
When you're making ice cream
当你做冰淇淋的时候
that has this really good flavor, like cinnamon,
味道很好，像肉桂，
you don't wanna overpower it.
你不想压制它。
But you also don't wanna make it weak.
但你也不想让它变弱。
Nice.
好了。
Whoa. What are you doing?
哇。你在干什么?
-Fondant. -Oh, fondant.
方旦糖。-哦,方旦糖。
I'm using fondant because
我用软糖是因为
I wanna airbrush on a smooth, clean surface.
我要在光滑干净的表面上喷枪。
When you're working with fondant,
当你处理软糖时，
you have to brush it with powdered sugar,
你要用糖粉刷它，
otherwise it'll stick to your surface.
否则它会粘在你的表面。
Now, I'm gonna roll it up on a French rolling pin
现在，我要用擀面杖把它卷起来
and drape it over the cake.
把它盖在蛋糕上。
I've never airbrushed a tie-dye design before,
我从来没有给扎染图案喷过油，
so I'm gonna take a toothpick
所以我要拿根牙签
and indent the spiral design
并采用螺旋缩进设计
and go beside those lines with the airbrush.
然后用喷枪在这些线的旁边画。
That looks spectacular.
看起来很壮观。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
All right. Time to check.
好吧。是时候检查了。
I take my cakes out, and I can really smell the lime
我把蛋糕拿出来，就能闻到酸橙的味道
and the strawberry and orange and the lemon,
还有草莓，橘子和柠檬，
which is great because I know Duff
这很好，因为我认识达夫
and Valerie will love it.
瓦莱丽会喜欢的
I get it on a turntable.
我把它放在唱机转盘上。
And I apply a frosting.
然后涂上糖霜。
All right. Making a ganache.
好吧。做巧克力酱。
I separate the ganache into individual deli cups,
我把甘纳许分成单独的熟食杯，
so I can dye them.
这样我就可以给它们染色了。
That's good.
这很好。
I start pouring it on my cake.
我把它倒在蛋糕上。
It doesn't completely cover the whole thing.
它并没有完全覆盖整个区域。
But it's still fun and messy, just like real tie-dye.
但它仍然是有趣和凌乱的，就像真正的扎染。
AIDAN: How's everyone doing?
艾丹:大家都好吗?
Pretty good! How are you doing, Aidan?
很好!你好吗，艾登?
Okay. I just hope, like,
好吧。我只是希望，
the clock doesn't get me this time.
这一次闹钟不听我的了。
Yeah.
是的。
To decorate my cake,
为了装饰我的蛋糕，
I'm gonna put a layer of fondant.
我要放一层软糖。
And then I'm gonna use the airbrush
然后我要用喷枪
and put some colors on there.
在这里涂上一些颜色。
You need to be super colorful for this challenge.
你需要在这个挑战中表现得非常丰富多彩。
I put my fondant in the sheeter,
我把软糖放在纸上，
which will basically flatten it out in even layer.
这样就能把它平铺成均匀的一层。
So there won't be any inconsistencies
所以不会有任何矛盾
with my cake.
用我的蛋糕。
DUFF: Oh, nice.
达夫:哦，不错。
Look, Jason's using the sheeter for his fondant.
看，杰森在用这张纸做软糖。
I think he's the first one so far. Mm-hmm.
我想他是目前为止第一个。嗯哼。
Can I use that to make giant lasagna noodles?
我能用它来做千层面吗?
No?
没有?
I mean, technically, yes.
我是说，严格来说，是的。
-Ooh. -Yeah.
-哦。-是的。
Mm, that looks pretty good.
嗯，看起来很不错。
10 minutes left, bakers. You got 10 minutes.
还有10分钟，面包师们。给你10分钟。
KANIYAH: I check on my cake in the oven.
凯妮雅:我检查一下烤箱里的蛋糕。
It's looking, like, um, 90 percent cooked.
看起来，已经煮了九成了。
But I need to get my cake out of the oven now
但我现在得把蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来
so I can ice this thing!
这样我就可以把它冰起来了!
It looks a mess.
看起来很乱。
I hope that this buttercream saves my cake.
我希望这奶油能拯救我的蛋糕。
Please save my cake.
请保存我的蛋糕。
I paint the inside of my pastry bag
我在我的糕点袋里面画画
red, blue, and purple.
红色，蓝色和紫色。
When it comes out, it'll look like a rainbow.
当它出来的时候，看起来就像彩虹一样。
JUSTICE: For my buttercream,
法官:为了我的奶油，
I start by mixing together powdered sugar,
我先把糖粉混合在一起，
softened butter, milk, and vanilla.
软化黄油、牛奶和香草。
I whip it until it's nice and creamy
我把它搅成奶油状
to make the cake have an extra pop
让蛋糕更有冲击力
of nice tie-dye color.
扎染的颜色不错。
So I color part of the buttercream yellow
所以我把奶油的一部分涂成黄色
and the other part pink.
另一部分是粉红色的。
It's ugly right now, but it'll look better soon.
现在很难看，但很快就会好起来的。
I put the pink buttercream on,
我放上粉色的奶油，
and I put the yellow buttercream on.
然后放上黄色的奶油。
They're mixing together.
它们混合在一起。
And I'm just thinking like, "Mm, that looks amazing."
我就在想"这看起来太棒了"
KEILI: I need to get my cakes out of the oven.
凯莉:我要把蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来。
But I'm not so sure if they're done.
但我不确定他们是否完成了。
[ Gasps ]
[喘息]
Oh, no. Keili's cake, it's just oozing.
哦,不。凯丽的蛋糕，都要渗出来了。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
It's rank!
它的排名!
There's liquid just coming out all over the place.
到处都是液体。
I'm done.
我完成了。
She just doesn't even have time to do -- No.
她甚至都没时间做不。
It's just -- Oh, Keili!
只是——哦，凯丽!
Pbht!
Pbht !
Looks like Godzilla stomped on it.
看起来像是哥斯拉踩到它了。
7 minutes, guys.
7分钟，伙计们。
VALERIE: Tie-dye cake.
瓦莱丽:扎染蛋糕。
And swirled ice cream.
还有漩涡冰淇淋。
I am so mad at my cake.
我对我的蛋糕很生气。
Pbht!
Pbht !
It's not done.
它还没有完成。
There's nothing else I can do.
我没有别的办法了。
Okay, I'm just gonna call it a lava cake.
好吧，我就叫它熔岩蛋糕吧。
That's what lava cakes are. Right?
这就是熔岩蛋糕。对吧?
This is a horrible mess.
这是一个可怕的混乱。
I got my second batch of ice cream done
我做了第二批冰淇淋
and no curdling.
不要凝固。
But I still have to ice my cake.
但我还得给蛋糕加冰。
Four minutes, guys.
还有四分钟，伙计们。
Oh. Four minutes.
哦。四分钟。
Get your cakes frosted.
给你的蛋糕撒上糖霜。给你的蛋糕撒上糖霜。
We heard you, Duff.
我们听到了，达夫。
I don't have time to make it all fancy.
我没时间把它弄得很花哨。
So I'm just slapping icing all over my cake.
所以我只是在蛋糕上涂糖霜。
30 seconds, guys, 30 seconds.
30秒，伙计们，30秒。
Uh...
嗯…
This is so stressful.
压力太大了。
I wonder if I'm gonna have enough time.
我不知道我是否有足够的时间。
Can't do anything more.
不能再做什么了。
BOTH: 10, 9, 8, 7, 6,
都是10,9,8,7,6，
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
5、4、3、2、1。
Hands up!
举起手来!
We're done!
我们完成了!
All right!
好吧!
REESE: There's tie-dye inside.
里斯:里面有扎染。
But on the outside, what the heck is this?
但在外面，这到底是什么?
All right, Val, we asked to see tie-dye cakes
好吧，瓦尔，我们要求看扎染蛋糕
and swirled ice cream.
还有漩涡冰淇淋。
You ready to see the results?
准备好看结果了吗?
Let's do it. Aidan, come on in.
我们开始吧。艾登，请进。
Someone's proud.
某人的骄傲。
I love that.
我喜欢这样。
All right, so, Aidan, tell me about your cake.
好吧，艾登，跟我说说你的蛋糕。
I've made a tie-dye cake with orange, lime,
我用橙子，青柠，
strawberry, and lemon
草莓和柠檬
with a white-chocolate-ganache drizzle.
淋上白巧克力甘纳许。
I love that you made a smaller cake
我喜欢你做的小蛋糕
with a lot more layers.
有更多的层次。
Now, the cake is looking a tiny bit
现在，蛋糕看起来有点
like the Leaning Tower of Colorful Pisa.
比如彩色比萨斜塔。
[ Chuckles ]
[笑]
Eh.
嗯。
It's supposed to be deconstructed
它应该被解构
and wild and fun.
狂野而有趣。
Just like Duff.
就像达夫一样。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Let's cut into that gorgeous cake
我们来切蛋糕吧
and try a bite, shall we?
尝一口，好吗?
-Okay. -Let's eat.
-好的。小的吃了。
Enjoy.
享受。
-Thank you, Aidan. -Wow.
-谢谢你，艾登。-哇。
Oh, that's so fun!
哦，那太有趣了!
Does it pass the shirt test?
它通过衬衫测试了吗?
It absolutely does. Absolutely does.
确实如此。绝对。
Mm. Mm! Very moist cake.
毫米毫米!非常湿润的蛋糕。
You cooked it perfectly. Not underdone, not overbaked.
你做得很好。不要生熟，也不要烤过头。
I really like that you can taste
我很喜欢你的味觉
the different flavors in each color.
每种颜色都有不同的味道。
-That's really fun. -You really can.
-真的很有趣。-你真的可以。
Mm, delicious.
嗯,很好吃。
I had orange taste just like orange.
我吃起来就像橘子一样。
That's so inventive, Aidan!
你真有创意，艾登!
Thanks!
谢谢!
All right, Aidan, tell me about your ice cream.
好吧，艾登，跟我说说你的冰淇淋。
It is a vanilla ice cream base.
这是一种香草冰淇淋基底。
And then I swirled in some raspberry puree
然后我加入了一些覆盆子泥
and a little bit of passion-fruit puree.
再来一点西番莲果泥。
Delicious. It's really creamy.
美味。真的很柔滑。
What I love about this -- It's not too sweet.
我喜欢它的一点是，它不太甜。
Way to go, man. I'm impressed.
干得好，伙计。给我留下了深刻的印象。
-Well done. -Good job, Aidan.
-嗯。-干得好，艾登。
-Thanks. -Thank you, Aidan.
-谢谢。-谢谢你，艾登。
-See you, man. -All right. Bye.
-再见，伙计。-好的。再见。
-Bye. -Thank you.
再见。-谢谢。
-Wow. -I'm so impressed with him.
-哇。-我对他印象深刻。
Yeah.
是的。
How you doing, Cole?
你好吗，科尔?
Great.
太好了。
There's glitter on your forehead.
你的额头上有闪光。
I know.
我知道。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
I have glitter on me every single day -- every day.
我每天身上都有亮片，每天都有。
All over my hands.
沾满了我的手。
People ask me what I do. I say I'm a unicorn wrangler.
人们问我是做什么的。我说我是独角兽牧马人。
Can you please tell us what you made for us today?
你能告诉我们你今天为我们做了什么吗?
It's a white cake dyed rainbow for tie-dye,
这是一个白色的蛋糕，染成彩虹，用于扎染，
covered in fondant,
裹着软糖，
and airbrushed to look like Duff's shirt.
然后把它喷得像达夫的衬衫
-And it does! -And it does.
-确实如此!确实如此。
I think it's an absolutely beautiful cake.
我认为这是一个非常漂亮的蛋糕。
Thank you. Now, I know we gave you a hard time
谢谢你！我知道我们让你很难过
about the glitter last week
关于上周的闪粉
-because it was on meatloaf. -Mm-hmm.
-因为是在肉饼上。-嗯。
This is the perfectly appropriate time to use glitter.
这是使用亮片的最佳时机。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Glitter makes everything perfect.
闪光让一切变得完美。
I can't wait to taste it.
我等不及要尝尝了。
I don't wanna talk about it anymore. Let's taste it.
我不想再谈这个了。让我们尝一尝。
Let's taste it.
让我们尝一尝。
I can feel the glitter.
我能感觉到闪光。
Thank you, Cole.
谢谢你，科尔。
All right. Nice-lookin' cake.
好吧。Nice-lookin”蛋糕。
-Beautiful. -Yeah.
来。-是的。
Vivid colors there, you know?
色彩鲜艳，你知道吗?
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Cole, did you soak it with anything?
科尔，你用什么东西泡过吗?
Did you soak it in a syrup or...
你是把它泡在糖浆里还是…
Mnh-mnh.
Mnh-mnh。
Nothin'. That is a moist cake.
一文不值。那是一块湿蛋糕。
Super moist. Mm, wow!
超级滋润。嗯,哇!
Moist and not -- not raw moist.
湿润而不是，不是生的湿润。
I think you iced it. It was still warm
我想你把它冻住了。天气依然温暖
like putting butter on warm toast.
就像在烤面包上涂黄油一样。
You know? And it soaks it all up.
你知道吗?它把水都吸收了。
Really good cake.
蛋糕真的很好吃。
Duff is, like, the cake master.
达夫就像是蛋糕大师。
So I feel really good about myself
所以我对自己感觉很好
because I guess I'm the cake master 2.0.
因为我想我是蛋糕大师2.0版。
Let's dive into your ice cream.
让我们开始吃你的冰淇淋吧。
It's a vanilla ice cream
这是香草冰淇淋
with a passion-fruit- mango-strawberry swirl.
搭配百香果-芒果-草莓的漩涡。
The flavor's great.
味道很好。
-Flavor is terrific. -Texture's really nice.
-味道好极了。-质地很好。
Not too sweet.
不太甜。
This tastes exactly like my mom's ice cream.
这和我妈妈做的冰激凌一模一样。
[ Chuckles ]
[笑]
Cole, you are formidable. Good baker, man.
科尔，你真厉害。不错的面包师，伙计。
-Thank you. -Thanks a lot.
-谢谢。-非常感谢。
Thanks, Cole.
谢谢,科尔。
Audra, tell me about the cake you made.
奥德拉，跟我说说你做的蛋糕。
I made a orange cake.
我做了一个橘子蛋糕。
And it has a orange frosting.
它有橙色的糖霜。
You know orange is my favorite color?
你知道我最喜欢的颜色是橙色吗?
No, I didn't. I did not.
不，我没有。我没有。
-Mine is blue. -Yours is blue?
-我的是蓝色的。-你的是蓝色的?
-I think we should taste this. -Let's taste it.
-我想我们应该尝尝这个。-让我们尝尝。
-Here we go. -Thank you, Audra.
-开始了。-谢谢你，奥德拉。
Look at these colors.
看看这些颜色。
Beautiful colors.
美丽的颜色。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
It's a little "Miami Vice." Very '80s.
有点像《迈阿密风云》。"80年代非常。
Yes.
是的。
"Miami Vice"? What's that?
“迈阿密风云”?那是什么?
Oh, no. Is it --
哦,不。是——
Is the orange flavor really strong?
桔子味真的很浓吗?
-It's pretty strong. -Mm-hmm.
-味道很浓。-嗯。
Orange extract.
橙色的提取。
You first taste the orange.
你先尝一下橘子。
You're like, "Oh, that's kind of pleasant."
你会说:“哦，这还挺不错的。”
And then it kind of kicks in to high gear
然后就进入了高速档
and starts to get a little bitter.
然后开始变得有点苦。
Audra, if I were you, what I would've done
奥德拉，如果我是你，我会做的
is maybe cut the amount of extract you used in half,
也许是把提取物的用量减半，
then use some of the zest.
然后用一些果皮。
But here's the deal -- It is a super-moist cake.
但事实是，这是一个超级湿润的蛋糕。
You cooked it perfectly.
你做得很好。
-Thank you. -It's nice and moist.
-谢谢。-很好，很湿润。
Tell us about your ice cream.
跟我们说说你的冰淇淋吧。
It is a plain vanilla with a white-chocolate-orange flavor.
这是一种纯香草口味的白巧克力橙味。
How did you make the orange-white-chocolate stuff?
你是怎么做橙白巧克力的?
I melted some white chocolate.
我融化了一些白巧克力。
I put some orange extract in that.
我在里面放了一些橙汁。
-How much? -A tablespoon.
——多?一汤匙。
[ Laughing ] Really?
(笑)真的吗?
Maybe two.
也许两个。
It's a lot. You used a lot of extract in there.
很多。你在里面用了很多提取物。
Like, extract is not juice. Big difference.
比如，提取物不是果汁。很大的差别。
Yeah! It's really strong!
是啊!它真的很强壮!
-Thank you, Audra. -Thanks, Audra.
-谢谢你，奥德拉。Audra, -谢谢。
-Bye. -Bye, honey.
再见。再见,亲爱的。
My tongue.
我的舌头。
Yeah.
是的。
Too much extract, too much.
太多的萃取，太多。
Keili.
Keili。
Yes?
是吗?
This is not my best work.
这不是我最好的作品。
This is actually one of my worst things
这是我做过的最糟糕的事情之一
I have ever made.
做过的最好的事。
I see you've met my cake.
看来你见过我的蛋糕了。
We have met your cake.
我们已经见过你的蛋糕了。
You wanna tell us about it?
你想跟我们说说吗?
My cake is a cinnamon-apple cake.
我的蛋糕是肉桂苹果蛋糕。
What happened?
发生了什么事?
I honestly don't know.
我真的不知道。
How much shredded apples did you put?
你放了多少苹果丝?
Like, an apple.
比如苹果。
-There's a lot of moisture. -Yeah.
-有很多湿气。-是的。
I'm gonna bet what happened was there was so much moisture
我敢打赌当时的情况是太潮湿了
that it changed the chemistry of your cake.
它改变了你蛋糕的化学成分。
Uh-oh.
哦。
I didn't think about it that way.
我不是这么想的。
All right, well, I think we should give it a whirl.
好吧，我觉得我们应该试一试。
-Let's cut into it. -Okay.
-我们切开吧。-好的。
Just be careful.
小心点。
It might be a little gooey.
可能有点粘稠。
It's a little gooey.
有点粘稠。
That's a little -- Okay. Yeah.
这有点——好的。是的。
I didn't want it to turn out like this.
我不希望事情变成这样。
I know.
我知道。
The little corner that is baked is really good.
烤好的小角真的很好吃。
It's not that you underbaked it.
并不是你没做好。
You got too much liquid, way too much liquid.
你的液体太多了，太多了。
You can even taste it in there.
你甚至可以在里面尝到它的味道。
It's really a shame, though, because it --
但这真的很遗憾，因为
it does taste really good.
味道真的很好。
But I just didn't execute it well.
但我没有很好地执行。
Now, tell us about your ice cream.
现在，跟我们说说你的冰淇淋吧。
My ice cream is a cinnamon ice cream
我的冰淇淋是肉桂味的
with a raspberry coulis on top.
上面还有覆盆子酱。
-You got a nice swirl. -Well, thank you.
-你有一个漂亮的漩涡。-好吧，谢谢。
I love -- love the taste of the cinnamon.
我喜欢肉桂的味道。
Good ice cream. Really good.
好吃的冰淇淋。真的很好。
-Oh, thank you. -Yeah, it's nice.
-哦，谢谢。-是啊，很不错。
Got a weird cake, but got some good ice cream.
蛋糕很怪，但冰淇淋很好吃。
-Thanks, Keili. -Thank you.
-谢谢,Keili。-谢谢。
You're welcome.
不客气
My emotions are racing.
我的情绪失控了。
Most of them are sadness and nervousness.
大多数是悲伤和紧张。
I don't wanna go home.
我不想回家。
ANNOUNCER: Sugar cookies get their groove on
解说员:甜饼干来了
as tie-dyed treats, right after this.
作为扎染的款待，就在这之后。
ANNOUNCER: How to make groovy tie-dye cookies.
播音员:如何制作绝妙的扎染饼干。
Gather together store-bought frosting, food coloring,
把商店里买的糖霜，食用色素，
pastry bags,
糕点袋,
sugar cookies, and wooden skewers.
糖饼干，还有木头串。
Dye your frosting with bright colors.
用鲜艳的颜色染你的糖霜。
Fill each of your piping bags.
填满每个裱花袋。
Pipe frosting in concentric circles,
同心圆管结霜;
completely covering your cookies.
完全盖住你的饼干。
Drag skewer through the frosting and rotate the cookies.
拖着烤串穿过糖霜，旋转饼干。
Makes a hip and colorful dessert.
做一道时髦又色彩斑斓的甜点。
For more fun treats like this,
想要获得更多这样的乐趣，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
Man, tie-dye cakes and swirled ice cream.
伙计，扎染蛋糕和漩涡冰淇淋。
-This is some fun. -I'm lovin' it.
-这很有趣。-我很喜欢。
Yeah, me too. Kaniyah.
是啊，我也是。Kaniyah。
What does that look mean?
那表情是什么意思?
Yeah.
是的。
What'd you make today?
你今天做了什么?
KANIYAH: I made a vanilla tie-dye cake
我做了一个香草扎染蛋糕
with a vanilla tie-dye buttercream.
加上香草扎染奶油。
What'd you make for your ice cream?
你的冰淇淋是怎么做的?
I made a vanilla-blackberry swirl ice cream.
我做了香草黑莓漩涡冰淇淋。
Mm.
毫米。
You know, your cake's a little messy.
你的蛋糕有点乱。
Tell me what's goin' on.
告诉我发生什么事了。
I was tryin' to cut the top off.
我想把它的顶部剪掉。
And it started dripping cake batter.
蛋糕糊开始滴下来。
Bad sign. So then what did you do?
不好的预兆。然后你做了什么?
I put it back in the oven.
我把它放回烤箱。
And I took it out one more time, and it still wasn't done.
我又把它取出来了，但还是没做完。
Are you worried?
你担心吗?
Yeah.
是的。
[ Sniffles ]
[流鼻涕]
Hey, girl, hey.
嘿，姑娘，嘿。
It's okay.
没关系。没关系。
What if it tastes really, really good?
如果它真的非常非常好吃呢?
-I wanna taste it. -I do, too.
-我想尝尝。-我也是。
Let's taste it.
让我们尝一尝。
It's a little bit raw in the middle.
中间有点生。
The edges got a little dry.
边缘有点干了。
The flavors are really good.
味道真的很好。
It's not terrible at all.
一点也不可怕。
Mnh-mnh.
Mnh-mnh。
Beautiful colors.
美丽的颜色。
Gorgeous colors.
华丽的颜色。
I think you got a good ice cream.
我觉得你的冰淇淋很好吃。
It's delicious. There's a swirl on top.
它是美味的。上面有一个漩涡。
I can see it. I can't really taste it.
我能看到。我尝不出它的味道。
Overall, not a bad job.
总的来说，还不错。
-Thank you. -Thanks, Kaniyah.
-谢谢。-谢谢,Kaniyah。
Puppy-dog eyes. Don't send me home.
小狗般的眼睛。别送我回家。
Justice, tell me what you made.
法官，告诉我你做了什么。
I made a strawberry-vanilla tie-dye cake.
我做了一个草莓香草扎染蛋糕。
My ice cream is a vanilla ice cream
我的冰淇淋是香草冰淇淋
with a raspberry swirl.
还有覆盆子漩涡。
I really love the way you gave your cake a fade.
我很喜欢你让蛋糕变淡的样子。
It goes from pink, salmon-y to the orange.
它从粉红色的鲑鱼色变成了橙色。
Yeah, it's kind of ombre.
是的，这是一种阴影。
-Ombre, yeah, yeah.
-嗯，是的，是的。
-A fade is a haircut. -Oh, sorry.
-退色就是理发。-哦,抱歉。
'Cause I know so much about haircuts, obviously.
因为显然我对理发很了解。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Well, I wanna see the inside of it.
我想看看里面是什么样子。
-Let's cut her open. -Let's see it.
-把她剖开。-让我看看。
All right. Thanks, man.
好吧。谢谢你,小伙子。
Will you look at all those fabulous colors in there.
你看看这些漂亮的颜色。
Yeah.
是的。
Mm! Super moist!
毫米!超级滋润!
Definitely getting strawberry, like you said.
一定要吃草莓，就像你说的。
-That is so moist. -So yummy.
-太潮湿了。所以好吃。
-Perfect. -Thank you.
完美的。-谢谢。
I got -- That's a --
我有——那是——
I got some swirls!
我有一些漩涡!
You got a nice swirl. Look at yours.
你有一个漂亮的漩涡。看看你的。
The ice cream's really good, creamy...
冰淇淋真的很好吃，奶油味…
-Thank you. -...not overly spun.
-谢谢。-…不要过度旋转。
I don't get a lot of flavor in the swirl.
漩涡里的味道不太好。
It's delicious. It's really good.
它是美味的。真的很好吃。
But I'm not -- I'm not tasting that raspberry.
但我不想，我不想尝覆盆子味。
And I really want to. Thanks, man.
我真的很想。谢谢你,小伙子。
I think it's time to call in Maya.
我觉得是时候叫玛雅来了。
-What do you think? -Let's do it.
-你觉得呢?-我们开始吧。
Hey, Maya.
嘿,玛雅。
MAYA: I'm afraid that my cake is a little short.
玛雅:恐怕我的蛋糕少了点。
But I think it looks like Duff's shirt.
但我觉得它看起来像达夫的衬衫。
So hopefully, I get some points for that.
希望我能因此得几分。
-How's it goin', Maya? -Good.
-最近怎么样，玛雅?改善情况。
Right on. Tell me about your cake.
正确的。跟我说说你的蛋糕。
It is a vanilla cake with a vanilla buttercream.
这是香草蛋糕加上香草奶油。
And then for the ice cream,
至于冰淇淋，
it's vanilla ice cream with a raspberry puree.
这是香草冰淇淋加覆盆子泥。
Your cake is too short. We need a little more cake.
你的蛋糕太短了。我们还需要一点蛋糕。
You know what?
你知道吗?
It's short and cute, just like you.
它又矮又可爱，就像你一样。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
I love the sprinkles.
我喜欢这些糖屑。
I love how colorful it is.
我喜欢它的色彩。
Thank you, Maya.
谢谢你，玛雅。
I do see that there's some different colors in there.
我确实看到里面有一些不同的颜色。
But I'm loving the cake.
但我很喜欢这蛋糕。
It's really perfectly moist.
它真的非常湿润。
There's just not enough of it.
只是还不够。
Lots of crunching.
很多嘎吱嘎吱的声音。
I think I'm gonna be crunching on sprinkles
我想我要嚼碎糖屑了
for at least like six hours.
至少六个小时。
Because there's that many sprinkles on it,
因为上面有很多糖屑，
it's really sweet.
真的很甜。
It's like a sugar overload.
就像糖过量一样。
Okay.
好吧。
Your ice cream is really creamy,
你的冰淇淋真香，
not too sweet.
不太甜。
And its got this big bold burst of raspberry, man.
它有一股大胆的覆盆子味，伙计。
-Well done. -Really nice.
-嗯。-真的不错。
That's the best-tasting swirl so far.
这是目前为止最美味的漩涡。
Yep.
是的。
That's, like, a huge compliment.
这是一个巨大的赞美。
-Hello. -What's up, Reese?
-你好。-怎么了，里斯?
Nothing.
什么都没有。
I'm kind of nervous.
我有点紧张。
As I'm looking at my cake, I'm like, "Seriously?
当我看着我的蛋糕时，我想，“真的吗?
I could've done a way better job."
我本可以做得更好的。”
Yeah, looks like you had kind of a rough day today.
是啊，看来你今天过得不太顺利啊。
-Yeah. -Yeah?
-是的。-是吗?
Please tell me about your cake.
请给我讲讲你的蛋糕。
Well, my cake is a white-and-yellow cake
嗯，我的蛋糕是白色和黄色的蛋糕
dyed different colors.
染成不同的颜色。
How about your ice cream? What'd you make?
你的冰淇淋怎么样?你做了什么?
I did a vanilla ice cream with a blackberry swirl.
我做了一个香草冰淇淋加黑莓漩涡。
One thing I will say for your cake --
关于你的蛋糕，我要说一点
It's nice and straight.
又好又直。
Your cakes are stacked up really evenly.
你的蛋糕堆得很均匀。
And it's sitting flat.
它平躺着。
-Thank you. -Yeah.
-谢谢。-是的。
I kind of wanna taste it. What do you think? I really wanna taste it.
我有点想尝尝。你觉得呢?我真的很想尝尝。
I cut into the cake, and I see the inside.
我切开蛋糕，看到里面了。
It's a burst of colors, like a rainbow and Duff's shirt.
这是一种颜色的爆发，就像彩虹和达夫的衬衫。
Oh, Reese, this is beautiful.
里斯，这太美了。
Look at that cake.
看那个蛋糕。
-Thank you. -It's so bright and cheerful.
-谢谢。-它是如此明亮和令人愉快。
The cakes are really warm.
蛋糕真的很热。
So the frosting melted into the cake.
于是糖霜融入了蛋糕。
It's good. It's got a little dense.
很好。它有点浓。
You know what? It needed to be frosted too
你知道吗?它也需要磨砂
because the cake is almost too dry.
因为蛋糕太干了。
I love your buttercream.
我喜欢你的奶油。
Your buttercream is really tasty.
你的奶油真好吃。
It's not too, too sweet, real buttery.
不是太甜，是真正的黄油。
It's very good.
非常好。
Ice cream's very tasty, though.
不过冰淇淋很好吃。
Again, not overly sweet.
同样，不要太甜。
I wish I tasted more blackberry.
我希望我能多吃点黑莓。
If you're gonna put a swirl in there,
如果你要在里面弄个漩涡，
you wanna be able to taste the swirl
你想要尝出漩涡的味道
and then taste the ice cream along with it.
然后一起品尝冰淇淋。
Okay.
好吧。
My cake didn't turn out as I hoped it to be.
我的蛋糕做得不像我希望的那样。
But I hope I do not go home.
但我希望我不要回家。
Hey, Jason!
嗨,杰森!
Hello!
你好!
Hi, Jason.
嗨,杰森。
I see that you're still in your tie-dyed shirt.
我看到你还穿着扎染的衬衫。
I'm still in my tie-dye shirt.
我还穿着我的扎染衬衫。
Tell us what you made today.
告诉我们你今天做了什么。
I made a tie-dyed cake.
我做了一个扎染蛋糕。
The red part of it is strawberry.
红色的部分是草莓。
And for my ice cream,
至于我的冰淇淋，
the swirl part of it is a raspberry jelly.
它的漩涡部分是覆盆子果冻。
Looking at your cake,
看着你的蛋糕，
your fondant job is actually not that bad.
你的糖果工作其实没那么糟。
-Yeah. -Thank you.
-是的。-谢谢。
Thanks, Duff.
谢谢,达夫。
That's a real compliment from a cake expert.
这真是蛋糕专家的赞美。
I say we cut into it and let's taste that puppy.
我说我们切开，尝尝那只小狗的味道。
Let's eat that thing.
我们把那东西吃了吧。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Got some interesting flavors.
有一些有趣的味道。
It's a moist cake that is falling apart.
这是一块正在散架的湿蛋糕。
I don't know why it's falling apart.
我不知道为什么它会崩溃。
The cake is falling apart?
蛋糕要散了?
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
How did you cool your cakes?
你是怎么冷却你的蛋糕的?
In the blast chiller.
在风冷机里。
Did you take 'em out of the pan?
你把它们从锅里拿出来了吗?
I put the pan in the blast chiller.
我把锅放进了冷风机。
You got to let it cool a little bit.
你得让它冷却一下。
Don't take it straight from the hot oven
不要直接从热烤箱里拿出来
and put it straight into the blast chiller.
把它直接放进冷风机里。
I think that's why it's falling apart.
我想这就是它崩溃的原因。
Let's dive into your ice cream.
让我们开始吃你的冰淇淋吧。
Their faces go kind of sour.
他们的脸变得有点酸。
Oh, whoo!
哦,哇!
That's a really odd flavor.
这味道真奇怪。
Jason, what -- What is goin' on with you?
杰森，你到底怎么了?
I don't know.
我不知道。
But a starch-thickened jelly inside of an ice cream is weird.
但冰淇淋里的淀粉粘稠果冻很奇怪。
I thought it tasted fine.
我觉得味道不错。
Your ice cream is delicious.
你的冰淇淋很好吃。
But lumps of starch frozen in ice cream...
但是冰激淋里的淀粉块…
That makes sense, scientifically.
这在科学上是有道理的。
I never considered that.
我从没想过这个。
Feel like you know what you're doing.
感觉你知道自己在做什么。
You're just a little heavy-handed with stuff.
你只是做事有点狠。
-Thanks. -Okay.
-谢谢。-好的。
I didn't do too well on my cake.
我的蛋糕做得不太好。
I hate cake.
我讨厌蛋糕。
I'm really worried now.
我现在真的很担心。
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package...
将会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包…
-Yeah! -...that includes
-耶!-…包括
a feature story in "Food Network Magazine"
《美食网络杂志》的一篇专题报道
-Hallelujah! -And...
哈利路亚!——……
$25,000.
25000美元。
[ Cheering ]
[欢呼]
Winner is coming.
赢家来了。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Well, we had some amazing tie-dyed cake
我们吃了很棒的扎染蛋糕
and ice cream swirls today.
今天的冰淇淋是漩涡状的。
I tell you, I think Aidan really
我告诉你，我觉得艾登真的
knocked it out of the park, though.
不过还是很出色的。
When I cut into it, it'll be perfect.
当我切开它的时候，它就完美了。
He took the time to individually flavor
他花时间单独调味
each color of his cake batter.
他的蛋糕面糊的每种颜色。
He totally did an amazing job.
他做得太棒了。
But Cole...
但是科尔……
Yeah.
是的。
He's got some skill.
他有点本事。
He does.
他所做的。他所做的。
The bite I had of Cole's cake was super moist.
我咬了一口科尔的蛋糕，感觉超级湿润。
Finally, an appropriate place
最后，一个合适的地方
for all the glitter he likes to use.
因为他喜欢用闪光剂。
Absolutely. Put it on a tie-dye cake.
绝对的。把它放在扎染蛋糕上。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
All right, so I gotta tell you, Val,
好吧，我得告诉你，瓦尔，
there were a few tie-dye cakes that were a real buzzkill.
有几个扎染蛋糕真让人扫兴。
I did not expect this to be
我没想到会是这样
such a difficult challenge for some of them.
对他们中的一些人来说，这是一个艰巨的挑战。
Kaniyah, I think, had a really rough day today.
我想Kaniyah今天过得很不顺。
She gets very emotional.
她变得非常情绪化。
She does.
她做的。她做的。
But she had some raw cake.
但是她吃了一些生蛋糕。
Yeah. I liked the swirliness of it.
是的。我喜欢它的旋涡。
The buttercream tasted great.
奶油味道好极了。
But, yeah, the -- Parts of that cake were raw.
但是，没错，蛋糕的部分是生的。
And then you look at Reese.
然后你看看里斯。
You know, he had three cakes.
你知道，他吃了三个蛋糕。
Now, thankfully, they were baked all the way through.
现在，谢天谢地，它们被烤透了。
-Mm-hmm. -But it looks like he had
-嗯。-但看起来他有
15 seconds to get that buttercream on.
15秒后涂上奶油。
My main problem with Reese's cake is that it was overbaked.
我对里斯蛋糕的主要不满是烤过头了。
-It was dry. -Yeah.
-很干。-是的。
It's beyond fixing!
这是无法修复的!
Keili had a rough day.
凯丽度过了艰难的一天。
But she still had such a great attitude about it.
但她对这件事的态度仍然很好。
I know. But, I mean, that cake was liquid.
我知道。但是，我是说，蛋糕是液态的。
Aw, this part is never fun.
这部分一点都不好玩。
Hi!
嗨！
-Hey, guys. -Hi.
-嘿,伙计们。-你好。
Bakers, two of you created desserts
面包师，你们俩做了甜点
that were out of this world.
那是来自这个世界的。
-Cole. -Yes, yes, yes!
科尔。-是的，是的，是的!
Good job, Cole.
干得好，科尔。
Your airbrush tie-dye cake was gorgeous
你的喷枪扎染蛋糕太漂亮了
and glitter-appropriate.
和glitter-appropriate。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
And your ice cream reminded me of my mom's homemade.
你的冰淇淋让我想起了我妈妈自制的。
Aidan, you took the time to individually flavor
艾登，你花了很多时间来单独调味
most of the colors in your tie-dye cake.
扎染蛋糕的大部分颜色。
And that, my man, was impressive.
而这，我的兄弟，令人印象深刻。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
But one baker's tie-dye cake colored us wowza.
但一个面包师的扎染蛋糕把我们染成了哇扎。
That baker is...
那个面包师是……
Cole.
科尔。
That's groovy, man.
太棒了，伙计。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
And I'm so happy.
我很高兴。
I've been in the top three times.
我已经进过三次了。
And I've finally won.
我终于赢了。
The following bakers created colorful cakes,
下面的面包师制作了五颜六色的蛋糕，
but a few elements were a bit out there.
但还是有一些元素存在。
Justice.
正义。
-Great job. -Thank you.
——工作。-谢谢。
Maya.
玛雅。
Jason.
杰森。
Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢。
And...
和…
Audra.
Audra。
Yes!
是的!
Unfortunately, that leaves Kaniyah, Reese, and Keili.
不幸的是，剩下Kaniyah, Reese和Keili。
Please step forward, guys.
请往前走，伙计们。
Kaniyah, your cake was raw, and the shape was off.
卡尼亚，你的蛋糕是生的，形状也不对。
And we struggled to taste the swirls in your ice cream.
我们努力品尝你冰淇淋里的漩涡味。
[ Sniffles ]
[流鼻涕]
Oh, Reese, time was not your friend today.
里瑟，你今天没时间了。
You struggled to get your cake frosted.
你努力让你的蛋糕上糖霜。
And the cake itself was dry.
蛋糕本身是干的。
Keili.
Keili。
Oh, Keili, there's just no way around it.
凯莉，这是没办法的事。
Your cake, it was just raw.
你的蛋糕，只是生的。
So then we had to ask ourselves,
所以我们不得不问自己，
"Was your successful ice cream enough to keep you here?"
“你成功的冰淇淋足以让你留在这里吗?”
The baker that will be leaving us is...
要离开我们的面包师是…
Keili.
Keili。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
You have the most amazing positive attitude.
你有最积极的态度。
This was really difficult for us.
这对我们来说真的很难。
-We're gonna miss you. -Don't stop baking.
-我们会想你的。-不要停止烘焙。
Okay.
好吧。
I'm really disappointed
我真的很失望
because I know that I can do better.
因为我知道我可以做得更好。
But I learned that I can do anything
但我知道我可以做任何事
because I did this.
因为是我干的。
ANNOUNCER: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
“儿童烘焙锦标赛”前情提要……
VALERIE: You have 2 hours to make a tie-dye cake.
瓦莱丽:你有两个小时来做扎染蛋糕。
-That looks spectacular. -That is a moist cake.
-看起来很壮观。-这是一块湿蛋糕。
-Super moist. -Thank you.
超级湿润。-谢谢。
VALERIE: One baker's tie-dye cake colored us wowza.
瓦莱丽:一个面包师的扎染蛋糕把我们染成了哇扎。
Cole. -That's groovy, man.
科尔。-太棒了，伙计。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
[ Gasps ] Keili's cake...
[喘气]凯丽的蛋糕……
The baker that will be leaving us is...
要离开我们的面包师是…
...Keili. -Thank you.
……Keili。-谢谢。
**
**
Hi, bakers. Welcome to week 5 of "Kids Baking Championship."
嗨,面包师。欢迎来到第五周的"儿童烘焙大赛"
-Week 5! -Whoo!
星期5 !-哇!
Yay!
耶!
VALERIE: Now, to become a champion,
瓦莱丽:现在，要成为冠军，
you guys really should know some baking history.
你们真应该了解一下烘焙历史。
-Oh, no. -Oh, no. No.
-哦,不。-哦,不。不。
So Duff and I made an educational video
所以我和达夫制作了一个教育视频
about the baked goods we ate growing up.
关于我们小时候吃的烘焙食品。
Well, it is the 1970s, Valerie.
这是70年代，瓦莱丽。
A great time for fashion but not desserts.
这是时尚的好时机，但不是甜点。
-Wow! -He did have hair.
-哇!-他确实有头发。
How old are these people?
这些人多大了?
Grandma's apple pie. It's okay.
奶奶做的苹果派。没关系。
But a lot of them are just funky,
但很多都很时髦，
like Black Forest cake.
比如黑森林蛋糕。
And coconut cream pie and German chocolate cake.
还有椰子奶油派和德国巧克力蛋糕。
Interesting fact, Ms. Bertinelli,
有趣的是波提纳尔女士
it was named for an American baker
它是以一位美国面包师的名字命名的
whose last name was "German."
他姓“德国人”。
Boss.
的老板。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Pineapple upside-down cake,
菠萝倒立蛋糕，
predictable old standby,
老套的备用方案，
and chocolate pecan pie.
还有巧克力山核桃派。
And banana cream pie.
还有香蕉奶油派。
And then there's cherry cheesecake.
还有樱桃芝士蛋糕。
-Heavy, man.
重,男人。重,男人。
Maybe in the future,
也许在未来，
desserts will become more interesting.
甜点会变得更有趣。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
I cannot believe that we used to eat those desserts.
真不敢相信我们以前也吃那些甜点。
-Old-people desserts.
老人甜点。老人甜点。
-[ Laughter ] -Hey, hey, hey.
-(笑声)-嘿，嘿，嘿
Pump your party brakes, kid.
给派对踩刹车吧，孩子。
You have 2 hours
你有两个小时
to take three key elements from these desserts
从这些甜点中提取三个关键元素
and transform them into much more on-trend...
然后把它们变成更流行的东西……
...eclairs.
条状拿。
-Eclairs. -Aw.
条状拿。哦。
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
对，对，对，对，对，对!
I'm so excited.
我太兴奋了。
-Eclairs! I love eclairs! -I knew it!
条状拿!我喜欢泡芙!-我就知道!
Eclairs are one of my favorite things.
泡芙是我最喜欢的食物之一。
VALERIE: Everyone will pick a card
瓦莱丽:每个人选一张卡
to see which throwback dessert
看看是哪种复古甜点
you'll be transforming into eclairs.
你会变成泡芙。
Please don't give me a Black Forest cake.
请不要给我黑森林蛋糕。
JUSTICE: I'm hoping that I do not get that Black Forest cake.
JUSTICE:我希望我不会得到那个黑森林蛋糕。
I do not know what that is.
我不知道那是什么。
And your baking time starts...
你的烘焙时间开始了…
VALERIE AND DUFF: ...Now.
瓦莱丽和达夫:……现在。
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh. What did I get? What did I get?
哦，我的天啊。哦，我的天啊。我得到了什么?我得到了什么?
Banana cream pie, yes!
香蕉奶油派，是的!
I know exactly what I'm gonna do. Okay.
我很清楚我要做什么。好吧。
I have Grandma's apple pie.
我有奶奶做的苹果派。
And I have to use apples, cinnamon and nutmeg.
我要用苹果，肉桂和肉豆蔻。
-I got German chocolate cake! -Pineapple upside-down cake!
-我有德国巧克力蛋糕!菠萝倒立蛋糕!
I got cherry cheesecake!
我有樱桃芝士蛋糕!
I got chocolate pecan pie!
我有巧克力山核桃派!
Coconut cream pie!
椰子奶油派!
Black Forest cake!
黑森林蛋糕!
I get the Black Forest cake.
我得到了黑森林蛋糕。
Seriously?
严重吗?
This is the one I really, really,
这是我真的，真的，
really did not want.
真的不想要。
I might have had Black Forest cake once in my life.
我这辈子可能吃过一次黑森林蛋糕。
But I don't know.
但我不知道。
My ingredients are whipped cream,
我的原料是鲜奶油
chocolate and cherries.
巧克力和樱桃。
But I'm actually kind of glad I have that
但我其实很高兴我有这个
'cause I can make something out of that.
因为我可以从中得到一些东西。
But first, I start my pâte à choux.
但首先，我要开始做我的馅饼。
I quickly add my 2 cups of bread flour.
我迅速加入两杯面包粉。
And I stir that really hard,
我使劲搅拌，
really vigorously and really quick.
非常有力，非常迅速。
And the mass forms a ball.
质量形成一个球。
Then I transfer my pâte à choux to a mixing bowl
然后把面团转到搅拌碗里
because that helps to get all the steam out.
因为这样可以让所有的蒸汽都出来。
Put your eggs in when it's hot. And it cooks the eggs.
热的时候把鸡蛋放进去。它还能煮鸡蛋。
And you do not want scrambled pâte à choux.
你也不想要炒蛋饼。
I add each of my eight eggs one at a time.
我把8个鸡蛋一次一个地加进去。
I want my pâte à choux to be in-between runny and firm.
我想让我的炸土豆条介于中间，既松软又结实。
I first learned how to make eclairs
我第一次学会做泡芙
from a baking book
从一本烘焙书
that I've used since I was 2.
我从两岁就开始用了
When I make my eclairs at home,
我在家做泡芙的时候，
they normally always turn out perfectly.
他们通常都很完美。
And I want them to turn out like that.
我想让他们变成那样。
I'm baking to stay in the competition.
我正在努力留在比赛中。
And there's a ton of pressure riding on my eclairs.
我的泡芙饼干承受着巨大的压力。
Pâte à choux. Pâte à choux, choux.
你为什么要这么做?泡芙，泡芙。
I love pâte à choux.
我喜欢土豆条。
I'm super excited because we have 2 hours
我超级兴奋，因为我们还有两个小时
to take three key components from old desserts
从传统甜点中提取三种关键成分
and make them into super new
把它们变成超级新的
and creative eclairs.
还有创意泡芙。
Mix, mix, mix, mix, mix.
混合，混合，混合，混合。
I'm making a banana cream pie eclair.
我在做香蕉奶油派泡芙。
And the three key components I'm required
我需要三个关键的组成部分
to have are bananas, vanilla custard
有香蕉，香草蛋奶冻
and graham-cracker crumbs.
还有全麦饼干屑。
All right, that will ensure my parchment paper
好了，这就保证了我的羊皮纸
doesn't try to fly anywhere.
它不会飞到任何地方。
I'm so excited that it's eclairs
我太兴奋了，这是泡芙
because I can do eclairs. They're easy.
因为我会做泡芙。他们很容易。
And I think it'll be a lot of fun
我觉得会很有趣的
to make 'em modernized.
让他们现代化。
-Wah! Sorry. -Sorry.
哇!对不起。对不起。
I get German chocolate cake.
我要德国巧克力蛋糕。
That's not my thing.
那不是我的菜。
Ugh. But I'll try my best.
啊。但是我会尽力的。
And the three ingredients I have to showcase is chocolate,
我要展示的三种原料是巧克力，
coconut and pecans.
椰子和山核桃。
I'm gonna add just one egg to my batter.
我要往面糊里加一个鸡蛋。
It starts, like, becoming really liquidy.
它开始变得非常流动。
I'm just gonna start over 'cause I don't have time to
我要重新开始，因为我没时间
doubt this one.
这一点值得怀疑。
This is not gonna bake up. And it's not gonna puff.
这不会烤烂的。它不会膨胀。
So I have to start again.
所以我得重新开始。
Maybe I put in too much butter.
也许我放了太多黄油。
The most important thing about pâte à choux
最重要的是关于  choux
is that your measurements are accurate.
你的测量是准确的。
-Correct. Have to be exact. -They have to be exact.
正确。必须精确。-它们必须精确。
Now, when you're adding the eggs...
现在，当你加入鸡蛋的时候…
Say you have a recipe that calls for eight eggs.
假设你有一个食谱需要8个鸡蛋。
Sometimes, it might take seven eggs.
有时，它可能需要七个鸡蛋。
Because you don't know the size of the eggs.
因为你不知道鸡蛋的大小。
Eggs are so many different sizes.
鸡蛋有很多不同的大小。
Eggs are different sizes.
鸡蛋大小不一。
But also just how much humidity is in the air.
还有空气中的湿度。
-What elevation you live at.
你住在什么高度?你住在什么高度?
Uh-oh.
哦。
We squashed an egg.
我们压扁了一个鸡蛋。
For my throwback dessert, I got cherry cheesecake.
我的复古甜点是樱桃芝士蛋糕。
My three elements are graham-cracker crumbs,
我的三个要素是全麦饼干屑，
cherries and cream cheese. I love cheesecake.
樱桃和奶油奶酪。我喜欢芝士蛋糕。
So I'm gonna make the best cheesecake eclair ever.
所以我要做史上最好吃的芝士蛋糕。
Last week, I was in the bottom.
上周，我排名垫底。
Never again.
我再也不会见你了。
KANIYAH: I am making a regular pâte à choux dough,
卡尼亚:我在做一个普通的土豆面团，
a cherry puree to put on top of it
在上面撒上樱桃泥
and a cherry cream-cheese filling
还有樱桃奶油芝士馅
with the graham-cracker crumbs on top.
上面放着全麦饼干屑。
For my cream-cheese filling,
我的奶油芝士馅，
I am using cream cheese, cherries and that's it.
我用的是奶油奶酪，樱桃，就这样。
I think the cherries gave it enough sweetness.
我觉得樱桃给了它足够的甜味。
I didn't add any powdered sugar.
我没有加糖粉。
VALERIE: 90 minutes left, bakers.
瓦莱丽:还有90分钟，面包师们。
90 minutes. -Gosh, no.
90分钟。天啊,没有。
DUFF: Throwback Dessert Eclairs.
达夫:复古甜点泡芙。
We want perfectly baked eclairs
我们想要完美烘焙的泡芙
if you want to be stayin' alive.
如果你想活下去。
This is gonna be my time to shine.
这将是我闪耀的时刻。
AUDRA: For my throwback dessert,
对于我的复古甜点，
I have chocolate pecan pie.
我有巧克力山核桃派。
And I am so happy.
我很高兴。
The three key ingredients
三个关键要素
I have to use are chocolate,
我必须用巧克力，
pecans and brown sugar.
山核桃和红糖。
I'm making a regular pâte à choux dough filled
我要做一个普通的泡芙面团
with a pecan chocolate mousse
加上核桃巧克力慕斯
and topped with a brown-sugar pecan glaze.
上面撒上一层红糖山核桃釉。
Egg wash. It's to make them shiny and pretty.
鸡蛋洗净。这是为了让它们闪亮漂亮。
I've been baking since I was 5.
我从五岁起就开始烘焙了。
And if I win, I'm gonna buy my cat a ton of cat toys.
如果我赢了，我就给我的猫买一大堆猫玩具。
That's in the oven.
在烤箱里。
How are your eclairs doing?
你的泡芙怎么样了?
AUDRA: Good.
AUDRA:很好。
I'm making a throwback apple-pie eclair
我在做复古苹果派泡芙
with cinnamon, apples and nutmeg.
加上肉桂，苹果和肉豆蔻。
I'm just making cinnamon filling
我只是在做肉桂馅
and maybe bake some apples and kind of lay those on top.
也许可以烤一些苹果，把它们放在上面。
Time to start working on my pastry cream.
是时候开始做糕点奶油了。
I put milk and heavy cream into the pan and warm it up.
我把牛奶和奶油放进锅里加热。
Just cinnamon alone won't add enough flavor.
仅仅用肉桂是不够的。
So I add some vanilla extract to my pastry cream.
所以我在糕点奶油里加了一些香草精。
Okay.
好吧。
That's nice and warm.
那很好，很暖和。
I grab my eggs and sugar,
我拿起鸡蛋和糖，
mix those up in a pan
在平底锅里搅拌
and pour the milk into the eggs.
把牛奶倒进鸡蛋里。
Come on.
来吧。
Get out of there. There you go.
离开那里。好了。
My throwback dessert is coconut cream pie.
我的复古甜点是椰子奶油派。
And the key ingredients are vanilla custard,
关键原料是香草蛋奶沙司，
coconut, and whipped cream.
椰子和鲜奶油。
Okay. Last week, I won.
好吧。上周，我赢了。
And I feel really great.
我感觉很好。
So coming into this week, I want to win again.
所以进入这个星期，我想再赢一次。
But I'm not really excited about this challenge
但我对这个挑战不是很感兴趣
because I don't like eclairs.
因为我不喜欢泡芙。
It's not working.
这行不通。
My batter is way too liquidy. I know it's not right.
我的面糊太稀了。我知道这不对。
And I have to start over. -What's going on with Cole?
我必须重新开始。-科尔怎么了?
-He just threw out his pâte à choux.
-他刚扔掉了他的p特·乔。
Hopefully, it'll work this time.
希望这次能成功。
I'm freaking out.
我吓坏了。
Most time, this thing's thickened up in a --
大多数时候，这东西都变厚了
in an instant. But...
就在一瞬间。但是…
JASON: I've been whisking for a long time.
杰森:我搅拌很久了。
But this pastry cream is not thickening up.
但是这个糕点奶油没有变稠。
How thick?
有多厚?
How thick? How thick?
有多厚?有多厚?有多厚?
I get my pastry cream into a glass bowl.
我把奶油糕点放进玻璃碗里。
Cinnamon pastry cream.
肉桂糕点奶油。
I throw that into the blast chiller.
我把它扔进冷冻机。
I really hope it'll be okay.
我真的希望一切都会好起来。
What were your favorite '70s shows?
你最喜欢的70年代的节目是什么?
Do not say, "One Day at a Time."
不要说“一天一天”。
Uh, I've -- I --
呃，我——我——
I'm telling -- I was a huge fan.
我告诉你，我是你的超级粉丝。
You know, it's weird.
你知道，这很奇怪。
We're leaning on a TV talking about TV on TV.
我们靠在电视机前在电视上谈论电视。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Kind of looks like there's a blizzard on the TV.
就像电视里有暴风雪一样。
What's that?
那是什么?
It's pretty cool how I got pineapple upside-down cake
我做菠萝倒立蛋糕的方式很酷
'cause my sister actually made a pineapple upside-down cake
因为我妹妹做了个菠萝倒立蛋糕
about a month ago.
大约一个月前。
I think I'm gonna use the cherries and the pineapple
我想我会用樱桃和菠萝
and probably the brown sugar in my pastry cream.
可能还有糕点奶油里的红糖。
I've never cut a pineapple before.
我从来没切过菠萝。
But I've seen my grandma cut many pineapples before.
但我以前见过我奶奶切过很多菠萝。
I'm chopping up my pineapple first,
我先切菠萝，
so I don't have to worry about it later.
这样我以后就不用担心了。
This is not working.
这行不通。
Maya, are yours in the oven yet?
玛雅，你的烤箱烤好了吗?
No.
不。
My second pâte à choux dough turns into,
我的第二个面团泡芙面团变成，
like, potato soup.
比如土豆汤。
What the heck?
搞什么鬼?
I'm really worried. This is terrible.
我真的很担心。这太可怕了。
I don't have time for this. [ Sighs ]
我没时间说这个。[叹气]
[ Crying ] I put my flour. And it -- it melted.
(哭)我把面粉放进去。然后就融化了。
VALERIE: What's up? What's up? What's up?
瓦莱丽:怎么了?有什么事吗?有什么事吗?
My pâte à choux is not working.
我的电子邮件坏了。
Look at me. Take a deep breath. Okay. You can do this.
看着我。深呼吸。好吧。你能做到的。
When you add your flour, turn the heat off.
加入面粉的时候，关火。
And look at those ingredients. And make sure they're exact.
看看那些配料。确保它们是准确的。
Okay.
好吧。
I need magical unicorn powers or something
我需要独角兽的魔力什么的
for this German chocolate cake eclair.
这款德国巧克力蛋糕泡芙
-Okay. -Hey, bakers.
-好的。-嘿,面包师。
Can we have your attention, please?
请大家注意了，好吗?
Oh. Hi.
哦。嗨。
Hi.
嗨。
What do you want me to do now?
你现在想让我做什么?
What do they have now?
他们现在有什么?
Back in the '70s, we didn't have as many
在70年代，我们没有这么多
healthy lunch snack options.
健康的午餐零食选择。
The only healthy treats in our lunch boxes
我们午餐盒里唯一健康的食物
was stuff like raisins, dried apricots.
是葡萄干，杏干之类的东西。
And if your grandma made your lunch, prunes.
如果你奶奶给你做午餐，那就吃西梅。
You guys are so mean.
你们太刻薄了。
Come on up. Grab a lunch box.
上来吧。拿个午餐盒。
And then incorporate the dried fruit inside
然后把干果放进去
into your eclairs.
放进你的泡芙里。
-What would my cat pick? -You guys are so nice.
-我的猫会选什么?-你们人真好。
Aren't we?
不是吗?
I've already gone through two pâte à chouxs.
我已经看了两个 周。
Don't need whatever's in that lunch box.
我不需要午餐盒里的东西。
One hour left, bakers.
还有一个小时，面包师们。
Throwback dessert eclairs with dried fruit.
带干果的复古甜点泡芙。
Come on. Please, be nice.
来吧。请对我好一点。
COLE: In my lunch box, I got dried cranberries.
科尔:我的午餐盒里有蔓越莓干。
Ew.
电子战。
-Oh, no. -Raisins. Dang it.
-哦,不。葡萄干。讨厌它。
Thank you for the apricots!
谢谢你的杏子!
-You're welcome! -Cranberry!
你是受欢迎的!蔓越莓!
Aidan. What'd you get in your lunch box?
艾丹。你午餐盒里装的是什么?
I got dates.
我有约会。
Aidan. I got dates too.
艾丹。我也有约会。
Aw. Aren't they so bad?
哦。他们不是很糟糕吗?
What'd you got? -I got raisins.
你有什么发现?-我有葡萄干。
-Aw. -So I might do raisin eclairs!
哦。-所以我可能会做葡萄干泡芙!
Since I haven't finished my batter,
既然我还没做完面糊，
I can add my twist to my batter
我可以在面糊里加入麻花
for my pineapple upside-down eclairs.
我的菠萝泡芙。
Perfect.
完美的。
I got dried apricots. I'm so happy.
我有杏干。我太高兴了。
I go-- I got dates. They're horrible.
我去，我有约会。他们是可怕的。
JUSTICE: Now that I have my apricots,
法官:现在我有杏子了，
I'm going to rehydrate 'em,
我要给他们补充水分
put 'em in a food processor
把它们放在食品加工机里
until they're like a paste
直到它们变成糊状
and then put that into my ganache.
然后把它放进巧克力酱里。
Do apricots go with Black Forest cake?
黑森林蛋糕配杏子吗?
I don't know.
我不知道。
Do they? -Mm.
他们吗?毫米。
Did you have a "One Day at a Time" lunch box?
你有"一天一天"的午餐盒吗?
I did not have a "One Day at a Time" lunch box.
我没有"一天一天"的午餐盒。
-That's just wrong. -That's -- that's just wrong.
-这是不对的。-那是——那是不对的。
If anybody out there has a "One Day at a Time" lunch box,
如果有人有"活在当下"的午餐盒，
please send... -Please send me one.
请将…-请寄给我一个。
Send it to Valerie Bertinelli care of Food Network.
寄给食品电视网的瓦莱丽·波提纳尔。
This is like the only way I can do dates.
这是我约会的唯一方式。
No.
不。
I decide to get something a bit tart
我决定吃点酸的
to help balance it out.
来平衡它。
Strawberry.
草莓。
Dates are equal combo of sweet
枣是甜的均等组合
and complete nastiness.
完全是肮脏的。
Just throw my bananas in there too.
把我的香蕉也扔进去。
If I didn't have to use these darn dates,
如果我不用这些该死的日期，
then I wouldn't have to use strawberry.
那我就不用用草莓酱了
And it would be a delicious, sweet banana-y vanilla custard.
还有美味的香蕉香草蛋奶冻。
But, no. We can't have that!
但是,没有。我们不能那样!
Oh, gross.
哦,恶心。
I got some dried apricots.
我有一些杏干。
And I'm turning them into a compote.
我要把它们做成一个果盘。
And this is gonna be kind of like a drizzle.
这就像一场毛毛雨。
To make my apricot compote
来做我的杏果盘
for my apple-pie throwback eclair,
我的苹果派复古泡芙，
I'm going to grind up my apricots...
我要把杏子磨碎……
1/3 cup.
1/3杯。
And then add a little bit of apple pectin.
然后加入一点苹果果胶。
The apple pectin will thicken it up.
苹果果胶会使它变稠。
So for when I put it on the eclair,
所以当我把它放在泡芙上的时候，
it won't just fall apart and fall off.
它不会就这么散架掉下来。
That is surprisingly good.
这是惊人的好。
How's everyone doing? -Good.
大家都好吗?改善情况。
A good eclair has to be golden brown, has to be risen.
一个好的泡芙必须是金黄的，必须是发起来的。
And it has to be hollow enough for you to fill it.
它必须足够空，让你填满它。
It's raw.
它是原始的。
So I put 'em back in the oven
所以我把它们放回烤箱
and hope they do not burn.
希望它们不会燃烧。
I got raisins.
我有葡萄干。
I'm going to put some inside of the filling.
我要在馅料里放一些。
And I'm going to put a little bit on top of the eclairs.
我要在泡芙上放一点。
I strained the cherries for the filling.
我把樱桃滤干做馅料。
Hmm. I'm going to use this juice.
嗯。我要用这个果汁。
And I add powdered sugar to thicken it up
我加入糖粉让它变稠
for like a sauce to go on the top
可以在上面撒酱汁
for my cherry cheesecake eclairs.
我的樱桃芝士蛋糕泡芙。
All planned out.
都计划好了。
AUDRA: No idea how I'm incorporating my cranberries.
我不知道怎么把蔓越莓混在一起。
Put it in the filling.
把它放进馅料里。
Actually, I think pecan pie would go with cranberries.
其实，我觉得山核桃派应该配蔓越莓。
To make my mousse,
要做慕斯，
I add my chocolate and my cocoa powder
加入巧克力和可可粉
and mix that together.
把它们混合在一起。
I add pecans to my mousse
我把山核桃加到慕斯里
and take all of my whipped cream
把我所有的鲜奶油都拿走
and fold my chocolate into that.
把我的巧克力拌进去。
You will not fail.
你不会失败的。
What's going on with Cole?
科尔怎么了?
COLE: I'm still making pâte à choux.
科尔:我还在做炸土豆条。
I need to hurry up.
我得快点了。
DUFF: Just waiting for that to boil?
达夫:就等着煮吗?
Uh, do you have all your other elements done, filling?
其他材料都准备好了吗，填充物?
Filling's trying to thicken.
馅料变稠了。
What are you making?
你在做什么?
Coconut vanilla filling, like a pie filling.
椰子香草馅，就像派馅一样。
Okay.
好吧。
There's a lot of pressure in this challenge
这个挑战有很大的压力
because if I don't make a good coconut cream pie eclair,
因为如果我做不好椰子奶油派泡芙，
$25,000 just, like, goes away.
两万五千美元就这么没了。
45 minutes, bakers.
45分钟，面包师们。
45 minutes.
45分钟。
Wow. Cole just gave us the stink eye.
哇。科尔刚刚对我们冷眼相待。
Mm-hmm. He is not a happy camper today.
嗯哼。他今天心情不太好。
Cole, how do you really feel?
科尔，你的真实感受是什么?
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Really liquidy.
真的像液体。
I'm really frustrated right now
我现在真的很沮丧
because my pâte à choux dough is not coming together.
因为我的泡芙面团没法揉成一团。
This is not good.
这可不太好。
Time is ticking down.
时间不多了。
And I'm on my third pâte à choux dough.
这是我做的第三个泡芙面团。
I just have to go with it 'cause I have no time.
我只能跟着它走，因为我没时间了。
Okay, Maya Jindal, you better get this together.
玛雅·金达尔，你最好振作起来。
Hopefully this works out.
希望这能解决。
Maya, are yours in the oven yet?
玛雅，你的烤箱烤好了吗?
-Yeah. -Nice. My egg wash.
-是的。-。我的蛋液。
VALERIE: Reese is having a little trouble
瓦莱丽:里斯有点小麻烦
with time management again.
还是时间管理。
He has time management problems every week.
他每周都有时间管理问题。
And every week, he pulls it out. -He does.
每周他都会把它取出来。他所做的事。
Okay. I'll give him that.
好吧。我同意他的观点。
REESE: I added raisins to my pâte à choux dough.
里斯:我把葡萄干加到我的泡芙面团里。
I am so lucky this worked.
我很幸运这招奏效了。
Now that my eclairs are in the oven,
现在我的泡芙已经在烤箱里了，
I'm going to start on my pastry cream.
我要开始做糕点奶油了。
-Reese, what you up to? -Pastry cream.
-里斯，你在做什么?糕点奶油。
Pastry cream.
蛋奶冻。
-Reese. -Yeah?
瑞茜。-是吗?
-Can I use your cherries? -Cherries, yes, yes.
我能用你的樱桃吗?-樱桃，对，对。
Don't take all of them -All right. Thank you.
别全拿走-好吧。谢谢你！
-You're welcome.
你是受欢迎的。
For my whipped cream, I have some cream,
做鲜奶油，我准备了一些奶油，
some chocolate and some powdered sugar
一些巧克力和一些糖粉
and some cherries that I combined all together
还有一些樱桃，我把它们混合在一起
to make a nice chocolate-cherry whipped cream.
来做美味的巧克力樱桃鲜奶油。
I pull my eclairs out.
我把泡芙拿出来。
And I poke each of them with a toothpick,
我用牙签戳他们每个人，
so the steam gets out of my eclairs.
这样泡芙里的蒸汽就出来了。
And it's not all gooey.
它并不全是粘稠的。
Your eclairs look so good.
你的泡芙看起来真不错。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
That's cool.
那很酷。
REESE: Three ingredients that I have to use
里斯:我要用三种食材
that represent a pineapple upside-down cake
那代表一个菠萝倒置蛋糕
is brown sugar, pineapple and cherries.
是红糖、菠萝和樱桃。
And this will be cooked with brown sugar.
用红糖煮。
JASON: Reese, your pastry cream?
杰森:里斯，你的糕点奶油?
Uh, thank you so much.
非常感谢你。
The pastry cream curdled.
糕点奶油凝结了。
I forgot about the pastry cream.
我忘了糕点奶油。
[ Groans ]
[呻吟]
[ Groans ] How do I forget my pastry cream?
(呻吟)我怎么会忘了我的糕点奶油呢?
No one wants to eat a curdled mess.
没人想吃凝固的东西。
I'm so far behind.
我落后太多了。
30 minutes, bakers. 30 minutes.
30分钟，面包师们。30分钟。
Those look really good.
看起来真不错。
DUFF: Throwback dessert eclairs with dried fruit.
带干果的复古甜点泡芙。
Getting harder, isn't it?
越来越难了，不是吗?
REESE: My pastry cream is curdled.
里斯:我的糕点奶油凝结了。
Are you kidding me right now?
你在开玩笑吗?
Oh... -Here I go.
哦……-我走了。
Pastry cream number two
第二款糕点奶油
for my pineapple upside-down eclairs.
我的菠萝泡芙。
Once my milk and sugar are up to a small boil,
牛奶和糖煮沸后，
then I add my egg mixture.
然后加入蛋液。
It's thickened.
增厚。
I'm happy because that's what it's supposed to be,
我很高兴，因为这是应该的，
kind of like a pudding.
有点像布丁。
Okay.
好吧。
I add my pineapple, cherry and brown sugar compote
加入菠萝，樱桃和红糖
to my pastry cream and mix it up.
加入我的糕点奶油，搅拌一下。
JUSTICE: For my Black Forest cake eclair,
法官:为了我的黑森林蛋糕泡芙，
I am putting my apricots in my chocolate ganache.
我把杏子放进巧克力甘纳许里。
I put the cream in the chocolate.
我把奶油放进巧克力里。
And I start to mix that up.
我开始把它们混在一起。
I add my apricot paste.
加入杏酱。
Now that I have my ganache made,
现在我已经做好了巧克力酱，
I need to pull out my eclairs
我得把泡芙拿出来
and start dipping them into the ganache.
然后把它们蘸到巧克力酱里。
I want to be the Kids Baking Champion
我想成为儿童烘焙冠军
because I want my own goat. 'Cause goats are really cool.
因为我想要我自己的山羊。因为山羊真的很酷。
So this has to be really good. Yes.
所以这一定很不错。是的。
Let's add a little more.
让我们再加一点。
My dad loves German chocolate cake.
我爸爸喜欢德国巧克力蛋糕。
I don't love
我不喜欢德国巧克力蛋糕。
If my dad was here,
如果我爸爸在这里
he would just amp it up and do great.
他只是把它放大，做得很好。
For my chocolate filling,
做巧克力馅，
I'm melting down chocolate chips and butter.
我在融化巧克力片和黄油。
And then I add some heavy cream and get that in the mixer.
然后我加入一些奶油，把它放进搅拌器里。
Okay. I think I'm just gonna throw some of these in.
好吧。我想我还是把这些扔进去吧。
I mean, dates and chocolate aren't the worst thing together.
我是说，大枣和巧克力在一起并不是最糟糕的。
But they're not the best.
但他们不是最好的。
It's gonna be really flavorful.
一定会很美味的。
Coconuts, no idea.
椰子，不知道。
Pecans.
山核桃。
I'm gonna highlight the ingredients in the eclair
我要强调一下泡芙里的配料
by putting a lot of pecans on top of the eclair.
在泡芙上放很多山核桃。
Does anyone have the pecans?
有人有山核桃吗?
Where are you? I'll bring them to you.
你在哪里?我给你拿来。
I'm so sorry. I had to grab it first.
我很抱歉。我得先抓住它。
Oh, no. Thank you. [ Pecans rattle ]
哦,不。谢谢你！[山核桃发出的响声]
Okay.
好吧。
For my base, I obviously need this.
作为我的基础，我显然需要这个。
For my glaze on top of my chocolate pecan pie eclairs,
为了在巧克力山核桃派泡芙上涂上釉料，
I'm kind of making up the recipe.
我在编菜谱。
So I combined brown sugar, crushed-up pecans
所以我把红糖，山核桃碎混合在一起
and heavy cream. I taste it.
还有浓奶油。我尝了尝。
And it is perfect, like, awesomely great.
这是完美的，简直棒极了。
That's delicious.
这是美味的。
Is something burning?
有什么东西烧着了吗?
I smell smoke. -I smoked coconut.
我闻到烟味了。-我烟熏椰子。
I want to smoke my coconut for my coconut cream pie
我想为我的椰子奶油派抽椰子
because my dad likes to smoke everything.
因为我爸爸什么都喜欢抽。
So why not smoke it?
那为什么不抽呢?
And hickory's my favorite flavor.
山核桃是我最喜欢的口味。
KANIYAH: For my cherry cheesecake eclairs,
我的樱桃芝士蛋糕泡芙，
I am mixing graham-cracker crumbs, sugar, and butter.
我在混合全麦饼干的碎料、糖和黄油。
Then I put it onto a small pan
然后我把它放在一个小锅里
and baked it in the oven for like five minutes.
然后在烤箱里烤了五分钟。
Please, be done.
拜托，就这样吧。
They're done.
他们做的。
It's looking good now.
现在看起来不错。
Now I have to get these eclairs assembled.
现在我要把这些泡芙组装起来。
I own my own business,
我有自己的生意
and it's called KC's Buttercream Sweet Shoppe.
它叫KC奶油甜店。
Winning the "Kids Baking Championship"
赢得“儿童烘焙锦标赛”
would be great for my business.
对我的生意有好处。
15 minutes left, bakers. 15 minutes.
还有15分钟，面包师们。15分钟。
Fill up those eclairs.
把那些泡芙加满。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I'm making caramel
我在做焦糖
because I think it'll complement the banana
因为我觉得它和香蕉很搭
in my banana cream pie eclair.
在我的香蕉奶油派泡芙里。
I just hope that it tastes nice
我只希望味道不错
with the strawberry and date.
还有草莓和枣。
Okay. It's done.
好吧。这是完成了。
Since this is a sauce, I want it to be lightly brown.
因为这是一种酱汁，我希望它是浅棕色的。
I add my dairy and my vanilla.
加入牛奶和香草。
Butter, which makes it taste good.
黄油，这让它的味道很好。
And this is my caramel sauce.
这是我的焦糖酱。
COLE: My eclairs are a little blonde,
科尔:我的泡芙是金黄色的，
but I know they're cooked on the inside
但我知道里面是熟的
because they're dry to the touch.
因为它们摸起来很干。
I'm adding more whipped cream
我要加更多的生奶油
because I don't think that the vanilla cream filling is enough.
因为我觉得香草奶油馅不够。
So I cut slits in the top and fill that with whipped cream
所以我在上面切了条缝，填上鲜奶油
and then dip 'em in the cranberry-chocolate ganache.
然后蘸上蔓越莓巧克力甘纳许。
Think that coconut cream pies have a graham cracker crust.
想想椰子奶油派有全麦饼干皮。
So I want to imitate that.
所以我想模仿一下。
I don't need too much nutmeg.
我不需要太多肉豆蔻。
It's quite a powerful, powerful taste.
它的味道非常强烈。
I want my apples to taste just like an apple pie.
我希望我的苹果吃起来像苹果派。
So I need the right blend of spices to get it right.
所以我需要正确的香料混合才能做出来。
All right, Jason. What do you got?
好吧，杰森。你有什么发现?
Your apples go in here?
你的苹果放在这里?
My apples are gonna basically just be coated on top.
我的苹果基本上只会被涂在上面。
-Uh-huh. -And this is gonna caramelize.
-嗯。-这个会焦糖化的。
-Nice. -Would you like a snack?
-。你想吃点点心吗?
I think I'll wait for your delicious-looking eclair.
我想我还是等着你的美味的泡芙吧。
Thank you!
谢谢你！
This eclair is
这个泡芙是
the most important eclair that I've ever made.
我做过的最重要的泡芙
Why must you be so...liquidy?
你为什么一定要这么…有流动性?
All right, bakers, you have eight minutes.
好了，面包师们，你们有八分钟。
Look at 'em go.
看看他们走了。看看他们走了。
Oh. I love these bakers so much.
哦。我太喜欢这些面包师了。
How you doing, bakers?
面包师们，你们好吗?
Good.
好。
-Could be better. -Bad.
-可以更好。太差了。
My eclairs, like, they're almost kind of doughy.
我的泡芙，有点像面团。
Oh, my gosh. I am seriously worried.
哦，我的天啊。我真的很担心。
My filling's splashing everywhere.
我的馅料溅得到处都是。
So I try to cut them open.
所以我试着把它们切开。
And I just kind of pour
然后我就倒了
a little bit of the filling in like a sandwich.
放一点馅进去，就像三明治一样。
Oh, my gosh. These are gross.
哦，我的天啊。这些太恶心了。
And this is a disaster.
这是一场灾难。
Trying to fall apart.
试图崩溃。
I'm just... [ Groans ]
我只是…[呻吟]
I'm not having a good day.
我今天过得不太好。
-Bakers, bakers! -Oh, my God.
面包师,面包师!-我的天啊。
Oh, my God. -Five minutes left.
我的天啊。-还剩五分钟。
Don't do that ever again, Duff.
别再这么做了，达夫。
Throwback Dessert Eclairs.
复古甜点泡芙。
Ugh, there's a date stuck in it.
有个日期卡在里面了。
I just want to get my bananas on it
我只是想把香蕉沾在上面
and brush on a little caramel.
再刷上一点焦糖。
REESE: Whoa. Oopsie.
里斯:哇。Oopsie。
My pineapple keeps getting stuck.
我的菠萝老是卡住。
I'm ditching the pastry bag 'cause I do not have time.
我要扔掉糕点袋，因为我没时间了。
There's no chocolate in a pineapple upside-down cake.
菠萝倒立蛋糕里可没有巧克力。
But what's an eclair without chocolate on top?
但是没有巧克力的泡芙是什么呢?
Two minutes, guys. You got two minutes.
两分钟，伙计们。给你两分钟。
-Go, go, go. -Okay, Duff.
-走，走，走。-好的,达夫。
Maya, how's it going? You gonna get it filled?
玛雅，最近怎么样?你要去填满吗?
-Hopefully. -Do you need any help?
希望是。你需要帮忙吗?
-Yes. -Okay.
-是的。-好的。
I'm coming over right now. -Ah!
我现在就过去。——啊!
JUSTICE: I'm putting the cherry, apricot, and chocolate on top
法官:我把樱桃、杏和巧克力放在上面
because I want the judges to see that I used all three
因为我想让评委们看到我用了这三个
of my ingredients in my eclair.
泡芙里的食材。
**
**
Time is ticking away.
时间在滴滴答答地流逝。
Uh, do you have any more of this?
这个你还有吗?
We're running out?
我们没货了?
Um, no.
嗯,没有。
Audra helped me, and, like, she's a real lifesaver,
奥德拉帮了我，她真是个救命恩人，
so if you see Audra in Colorado, say, "Thanks."
所以如果你在科罗拉多见到奥德拉，说声“谢谢”。
30 seconds, bakers.
30秒，面包师们。
Audra and Maya, you guys gonna finish in time?
奥德拉和玛雅，你们能按时完成吗?
BOTH: Yes!
两种:是的!
-Hurry up, guys. Hurry up. -Hurry up.
-快点，伙计们。快点。快点起来。
Perfectly.
完美。
Yay!
耶!
BOTH: 10...9...8...7...6...
两种:10 9……八……七……六……
5...4...3...2...1...
5 4 3…2…1…
Hands up!
举起手来!
-Ooh. -Yay!
-哦。耶!
-All right. -Well done, bakers.
-好的。-干得好，面包师们。
-Good job. -Ah!
改善工作。——啊!
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
Throwback Dessert Eclairs.
复古甜点泡芙。
All right. All right. All right.
好吧。好吧。好吧。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Why don't we bring in Justice?
我们为什么不伸张正义呢?
-Yes, please. -Justice.
是的,请。正义。
JUSTICE: I'm feeling pretty excited
JUSTICE:我感觉很兴奋
because my eclairs turned out really well.
因为我的泡芙做得很好。
But I want to see what the judges have to say.
但我想看看评委们会怎么说。
Confident walk. Feeling good?
自信的走。感觉好吗?
So, Justice, tell me about your eclair.
贾斯蒂斯，跟我说说你的泡芙吧。
I had the Black Forest cake
我吃了黑森林蛋糕
which had whipped cream, chocolate, and cherries.
里面有鲜奶油，巧克力和樱桃。
So I decided I was gonna do a chocolate-cherry whipped cream
所以我决定做巧克力樱桃生奶油
for my filling.
用来补牙的。
And I did a chocolate ganache.
我做了巧克力甘纳许。
But because I had to have dried apricots,
但因为我要吃杏干，
I blended them up.
我把它们混在一起。
And I put them in the ganache. -You put them into the ganache?
我把它们放在巧克力酱里。-你把它们放进巧克力酱里了?
-Yeah. -Hmm.
-是的。嗯。
Huh, cool. You ever had a Black Forest cake?
嗯,很酷。你吃过黑森林蛋糕吗?
No. When that little video popped up,
不。当那个小视频弹出时，
I'm like, "Oh, I definitely don't want that.
我想，“哦，我绝对不想那样。
There's no way I'm gonna get that one."
我不可能得到那个。”
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
I love how you put the flavors
我喜欢你放的味道
that we're gonna find inside our eclair on top.
我们会在泡芙里找到它。
-Mm.
毫米。毫米。
Oh, wow.
哦,哇。
That blew up all over me. That's a good sign.
我被炸飞了。这是个好迹象。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I love that it's not overly sweet.
我喜欢它不太甜。
I don't taste the apricot yet.
我还尝不出杏味。
Apricot is not a really big flavor.
杏味不是很重。
If you've ever seen a Black Forest cake,
如果你见过黑森林蛋糕，
you'll also see that there are maraschino cherries.
你还会看到这里有马拉斯奇诺樱桃。
It's actually pretty cool
这真的很酷
that you used fresh cherries instead of maraschinos.
你用的是新鲜樱桃而不是马拉斯奇诺。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Other thing I got to tell you,
还有一件事我要告诉你，
this dough is perfect --
这个面团很完美
crispy on the outside, eggy on the inside.
外面酥脆，里面有鸡蛋味。
-Well done. -Justice, I'm impressed, man.
-嗯。-正义，我很佩服，伙计。
Good job. -Thank you, Justice.
好工作。-谢谢你，法官。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
I'm so happy right now. Yes!
我现在很开心。是的!
-Audra. -I got chocolate pecan pie.
audra。-我有巧克力山核桃派。
The elements I had to include were chocolate,
我要加入的元素是巧克力，
pecans, and brown sugar.
山核桃和红糖。
And I made eclairs filled with chocolate-pecan mousse
我还做了巧克力核桃慕斯泡芙
topped with a brown-sugar pecan glaze.
上面撒上一层红糖核桃釉。
And for the twist, I just put some cranberries on top,
我在上面放了一些蔓越莓，
which I know is a little uncreative.
我知道这有点缺乏创意。
But just don't try to notice that too much.
但不要太在意这一点。
Don't try to notice it too much?
不要太注意它?
Yeah.
是的。
Your pâte à choux dough looks really beautifully done.
你的泡芙面团看起来很漂亮。
They're nice-looking eclairs.
它们是很好看的泡芙。
-Oh, no. -They're just not the same size.
-哦,不。-它们只是尺寸不同而已。
This is the Duff-size eclair.
这是达夫大小的泡芙。
And then this is the Audra-size eclair.
这是奥德拉大小的泡芙。
Your glaze -- so good.
你的釉色——太好了。
Totally taste the cranberry. -Thank you.
尝尝蔓越莓的味道。-谢谢。
So I got one little piece of chocolate in the middle there.
我在中间放了一小块巧克力。
It didn't go all the way to the edges.
它没有走到所有的边缘。
-Just eat the other half. -You call this mousse?
-只吃另一半。-你管这叫慕斯?
-I call it a ganache. -Mousse is light and fluffy.
-我叫它甘纳许。-慕斯又轻又蓬松。
Yeah.
是的。
And that's probably why you had trouble
这可能就是你遇到麻烦的原因
because it's so thick.
因为它太厚了。
Uh, but, man, your flavors are right on.
但是，伙计，你的口味太棒了。
I taste that -- that pecan pie.
我尝到了核桃派的味道。
-Thank you. -Good job.
-谢谢。改善工作。
Thanks, Audra. Toodle-oo.
谢谢,Audra。Toodle-oo。
Aidan.
艾丹。
AIDAN: I don't feel pretty good
艾丹:我感觉不太好
about my eclairs, walking in.
关于我的泡芙，走进来。
I just hope they taste good.
我只希望它们好吃。
I hope that you like them.
我希望你喜欢它们。
Do you like them?
你喜欢它们吗?
Um, I'm not too big on dates.
我不太喜欢约会。
I bet in like three or four years,
我打赌三四年后，
you're gonna be really into dates.
你会很喜欢约会的。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Maybe a bit longer than that.
也许比那要长一点。
What was your throwback dessert?
你的复古甜点是什么?
I got a banana cream pie.
我有一个香蕉奶油派。
What were the three elements of the banana cream pie?
香蕉奶油派的三种成分是什么?
Graham-cracker crumbs, vanilla pudding, and bananas.
全麦饼干屑，香草布丁和香蕉。
I have the vanilla custard in with a lot of fruit.
我把香草蛋奶沙司加了很多水果。
I have the bananas on top and inside the custard.
我把香蕉放在上面和蛋奶冻里面。
And there are graham-cracker crumbs
还有全麦饼干的碎屑
inside the eclair for a nice crunch
放入泡芙，嘎吱嘎吱
and dried dates.
还有干枣。
Could you say that with any more disgust?
你还能说得更恶心吗?
I'm gonna take a little taste. -What did I just taste?
我要尝一点。-我刚尝到什么了?
What is that? What's sticky?
那是什么?粘的是什么?
Uh, probably the caramel sauce.
可能是焦糖酱。
-The caramel? It's delicious. -It really is delicious.
——焦糖吗?它是美味的。-真的很好吃。
Yeah. Your caramel's really good.
是的。你的焦糖真好吃。
I'm not crazy about the strawberry.
我不喜欢草莓。
I wish you had just left it be dates...
我真希望你没去约会……
Okay.
好吧。
...because I think the strawberry takes away from it.
…因为我觉得草莓会让它失色。
And you don't need it.
你不需要它。
-I'm right there with you. -And I feel like the --
-我就在你身边。-我觉得
the challenge was to make
挑战在于
a banana cream pie into an eclair.
香蕉奶油派放进泡芙里。
And had you left out the strawberries,
如果你没拿草莓，
it would've screamed "banana cream pie."
它会尖叫"香蕉奶油派"
Okay.
好吧。
So it's not the dates that threw you for the loop.
所以让你迷惑的不是日期。
I think it's the strawberries.
我想是草莓的缘故。
-Okay. -Thank you, Aidan.
-好的。-谢谢你，艾登。
-Good job, Aidan. -You're welcome. Bye.
-干得好，艾登。你是受欢迎的。再见。
-See ya. -See ya later.
—看丫。-再见。
Really wish he hadn't added the strawberries.
真希望他没加草莓。
Strawberries, like, totally torpedoed this.
草莓完全毁了这一切。
Honestly, I'm really worried.
说实话，我真的很担心。
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary brownies
普通的布朗尼
ignite into quick-and-easy mini Baked Alaska,
点燃成快速简单的迷你烤阿拉斯加，
right after this.
就在这之后。
ANNOUNCER: How to make quick-and-easy mini Baked Alaska.
播音员:如何快速简便地制作迷你烤阿拉斯加。
Gather together baked brownies,
把烤好的布朗尼放在一起，
a mini cookie cutter, vanilla ice cream and scoop,
一个迷你饼干切割器，香草冰淇淋和勺子，
marshmallow cream, and a food torch.
棉花糖奶油，还有食物手电筒。
Cut out your mini brownies.
切出你的迷你布朗尼蛋糕。
Add a scoop of ice cream.
加一勺冰淇淋。
Cover with a mountain of marshmallow cream.
在上面撒上一层棉花糖奶油。
Carefully caramelize.
仔细焦化。
It's a delightful hot ice-cream dessert.
这是一道美味的热冰淇淋甜点。
For more treats like this,
想要更多这样的美食，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
Throwback desserts, man.
复古甜点，伙计。
Man. Groovy.
男人。Groovy。
-Want to talk to Jason? -Let's do it.
-想和杰森谈谈吗?-我们开始吧。
All right. Hey, Jason.
好吧。嗨,杰森。
Hello.
你好。
He's like the king of a parade.
他就像游行中的王者。
Hello. Hello.
你好。你好。
So, Jason, what was your throwback dessert?
杰森，你的复古甜点是什么?
For my throwback dessert,
我的复古甜点，
I got the grandma's apple pie.
我买了奶奶做的苹果派。
So I had to have apples, cinnamon, and nutmeg.
所以我必须吃苹果、肉桂和肉豆蔻。
And on the inside of my eclair,
在我的泡芙里面，
I have a cinnamon pastry cream.
我有一份肉桂酥皮奶油。
For the little tasty treat you put in my lunch,
感谢你在我的午餐里放的小点心，
I made a dried apricot compote.
我做了一个杏干果盘。
When I see an eclair, I usually like to see some kind of...
当我看到泡芙时，我通常喜欢看到一些……
-Glaze? -...glaze over it.
釉?-…上了一层釉。
Pie usually has a nice golden color, not a glaze on it.
馅饼通常呈金黄色，没有上釉。
-I almost buy that. -I ain't buying it.
-我差点就信了。-我才不信呢。
Almo-- I said, "I almost buy it."
我说:“我差点就买了。”
You got a nice amount of cream in there.
里面有很多奶油。
This is a pretty thin pastry cream.
这是很薄的糕点奶油。
You probably cooked the pastry cream a little too long
你可能把奶油酥皮煮得太久了
'cause it got a little scrambled.
因为有点乱了。
That's what happens with eggs.
鸡蛋就是这样。
I really taste the cinnamon in there.
我真的尝到了肉桂的味道。
I tasted nutmeg.
我尝了肉豆蔻的味道。
I would've liked a little bit more nutmeg
我还想再加点肉豆蔻
'cause I do love nutmeg.
因为我很喜欢肉豆蔻。
I am definitely getting the apricot.
我一定要杏味的。
Really good job with the twist.
扭得很好。
You incorporated it in a very natural way.
你以一种非常自然的方式融入其中。
You didn't force it, and it totally worked.
你没有强迫我，而且完全成功了。
-Bye. -See you later.
再见。-再见。
Thanks, Jason.
谢谢你,杰森。
Cole, tell me about your day today.
科尔，跟我说说你今天过得怎么样。
Well, I had to remake my pâte à choux.
我得重做我的炸土豆条。
[ Groans ] -Hmm.
[呻吟]-嗯。
COLE: So it's an eclair filled
科尔:所以这是一个泡芙填充
with coconut-cream pie filling
用椰子奶油做馅
and whipped cream dipped in ganache
还有蘸着甘纳许的鲜奶油
and graham crackers with hickory-smoked coconut.
还有山核桃烟熏椰子的全麦饼干。
And the key ingredients are vanilla custard,
关键原料是香草蛋奶沙司，
coconut, and whipped cream.
椰子和鲜奶油。
And in my lunch box, I got dried cranberries.
在我的午餐盒里，我有蔓越莓干。
So I chopped 'em up really tiny and put them in the ganache.
所以我把它们切得很小，放在巧克力酱里。
-Nice. -And they're on top, too.
-。-他们也在上面。
Your eclair is a little blonde.
你的泡芙是金黄色的。
Yeah. I was in a rush.
是的。我赶时间。
But they're cooked, like, enough.
但它们已经煮熟了。
It's not raw. It's not as crunchy, either.
它不是生的。它也不那么脆了。
But I like it. Love the chocolate.
但是我喜欢它。我喜欢巧克力。
I think the chocolate is the star.
我觉得巧克力是明星。
Yeah. The cranberry --
是的。蔓越莓——
Love it with the chocolate.
我喜欢和巧克力一起吃。
The coconut is very subtle.
椰子味很清淡。
I don't really taste the smoke on there.
我尝不出烟味。
But I don't mind that I don't taste it.
但我不介意我尝不到。
A lot of times, it just kind of tastes like a campfire.
很多时候，它尝起来就像篝火。
But great thinking.
但是很棒的想法。
I think that's awesome that you pulled that smoker out.
我觉得你把烟枪拔出来真是太棒了。
You did a really good job.
你做得很好。
-Thank you. -Thank you, Cole.
-谢谢。-谢谢你，科尔。
-Thanks, Cole. -Thank you.
-谢谢,科尔。-谢谢。
-Man, that kid. -He's so talented.
-天啊，那孩子。-他太有才华了。
Hey, Maya.
嘿,玛雅。
I know that it doesn't look good,
我知道这看起来不太好，
but I hope it tastes good. -Did you have fun today?
但我希望它尝起来不错。-你今天玩得开心吗?
-Yeah. -That doesn't --
-是的。-不——
-Wait. -She said, "Yeah."
等。-她说:“是的。”
But I didn't -- It sounded like no.
但我没有，听起来像是没有。
No. Nothing was really working today.
不。今天什么都不好使。
But at least I finished.
但至少我完成了。
-Absolutely. -You definitely finished.
-当然。-你绝对完成了。
What was your throwback dessert
你的复古甜点是什么
that you had to turn into an eclair?
你非得把它变成泡芙吗?
-A German chocolate cake. -Okay.
-德国巧克力蛋糕。-好的。
MAYA: Um, the three key elements were chocolate,
玛雅:嗯，三个关键要素是巧克力，
pecans, and coconut.
山核桃和椰子。
So I made a regular eclair
所以我做了一个普通的泡芙
with chocolate filling topped with coconuts and pecans.
里面有巧克力馅，上面有椰子和山核桃。
And my twist was dates.
我的转折是日期。
I'm looking at your pâte à choux.
我在看你的土豆条。
Uh, it's a little flat.
呃，有点瘪了。
Yeah.
是的。
I know what happened.
我知道发生了什么。
I think you put one too many eggs in your dough.
我想你在面团里多放了一个鸡蛋。
Mm. I can taste it.
嗯，我能尝出来。
Yeah, it's a little eggy.
是的，有点鸡蛋味。
I think the dates taste terrific on this.
我觉得枣子加在上面味道棒极了。
Your chocolate is quite delicious.
你的巧克力很好吃。
It's actually turned into some sort of,
它实际上变成了某种，
kind of fudge... -Mm-hmm.
有点胡言乱语……-嗯。
-...which is really delicious. -Delicious.
-…真的很好吃。美味的。
It's really nice.
真的很不错。
I'm not sure if it works as an eclair filling.
我不确定它能不能做泡芙的馅料。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
But whatever it is, is awesome and I want to eat more of it.
但不管它是什么，都很好吃，我想多吃点。
I have all the flavors in there
我把所有的味道都放进去了
that a German chocolate cake should have.
德国巧克力蛋糕应该有的
And for that, I'm happy. -And way to stick it out.
为此，我很高兴。-坚持到底的方法。
-Thank you. -Good job, Maya.
-谢谢。-干得好，玛雅。
Kaniyah, tell us what you made today.
Kaniyah，告诉我们你今天做了什么。
I made a cherry cheesecake eclair.
我做了一个樱桃芝士蛋糕。
I had to use cream cheese. I had to use cherries.
我不得不用奶油奶酪。我必须用樱桃。
I had to use graham-cracker crumbs.
我不得不用全麦饼干屑。
And then what was the dried fruit that you got?
然后你得到的干果是什么?
I got raisins. I put some inside the filling.
我有葡萄干。我在馅料里放了一些。
And I put some on top.
我在上面放了一些。
Hmm. What is the filling?
嗯。什么是填充物?
It's a cherry cream cheese filling.
这是樱桃奶油芝士馅。
I think you like it, don't you?
我觉得你喜欢它，不是吗?
It was good.
很好。
I used cream cheese and cherries.
我用的是奶油奶酪和樱桃。
Just cream cheese and cherries?
只有奶油奶酪和樱桃吗?
Yeah. -Sugar?
是的。四种不同食物吗?
No. It's enough sugar in the cherries.
不。樱桃里的糖足够了。
-Huh, okay. -What is the sticky stuff?
嗯,好吧。-这黏糊糊的东西是什么?
KANIYAH: It's cherry puree.
这是樱桃泥。
It's supposed to be the topping.
这应该是配料。
Whoa. That is nice and full.
哇。很好，很饱。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
So y-- you think that the cherries were sweet enough
所以，你觉得樱桃足够甜
to make that filling sweet enough for this eclair?
让夹心足够甜来做泡芙吗?
I don't think you think so.
我不认为你这么认为。
Well, I think so, too.
嗯，我也这么认为。
I think that filling is perfect.
我觉得馅料很完美。
-Yay! -[ Duff and Valerie laugh ]
耶!——[达夫和瓦莱丽笑]
-Got ya. [ Laughter ]
忘记你。[笑声]
Not tasting a lot of raisin. I'm tasting a lot of cherry.
尝不出葡萄干的味道。我尝到了很多樱桃味。
But I love that cream-cheese filling.
但我喜欢里面的奶油芝士馅。
Really makes me think of cheesecake.
真的让我想起了芝士蛋糕。
-Yay. -Ugh, that's just...
耶。-呃，那只是…
I lo-- Mmm. -Let me see that muscle.
我喜欢——嗯。让我看看你的肌肉。
[ Groans ] Ya!
(呻吟)耶!
[ Laughter ] -Thanks a lot, Kaniyah.
[笑声]-谢谢你，卡尼亚。
Good job. -Thank you.
好工作。-谢谢。
You're welcome.
不客气
Reese.
瑞茜。
My '70s throwback dessert
我的70年代复古甜点
was a pineapple upside-down cake.
是菠萝倒立蛋糕。
My elements were cherries,
我的元素是樱桃，
pineapple, and brown sugar. -All right.
菠萝和红糖。-好的。
And what was the twist that we threw at you?
我们给你出的圈套是什么?
Raisins.
葡萄干。
I used my raisins
我用了葡萄干
by putting them in my pâte à choux dough.
把它们放进我的炸土豆条面团里。
Huh, like raisin bread.
嗯，就像葡萄干面包。
That's amazing.
这是惊人的。
-Yeah. That's really cool. -I love that.
-是的。那真的很酷。-我喜欢。
Wow.
哇。
I'm looking at your presentation.
我正在看你的报告。
And, um, all the eclairs have their own little personality.
所有的泡芙都有自己的个性。
That's for sure.
那是肯定的。
A little crazy with the powdered sugar.
糖粉放得有点疯狂。
I'm -- I'm hoping it's powdered sugar and not flour.
我希望是糖粉而不是面粉。
That's flour.
这是面粉。
No. I'm just joking. That's powdered sugar.
不。我只是开个玩笑。那是糖粉。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
-You got me. -That was good.
-你说对了。-很好。
Yeah. They're a little -- they're a little rustic.
是的。它们有点，有点土气。
I think they're a little rustic, you know?
我觉得他们有点土气，你知道吗?
And what made you go with chocolate
你为什么要选巧克力
for pineapple upside-down cake?
菠萝倒立蛋糕?
It's not bad 'cause when you think
这并不坏，因为当你想
of an eclair, you think of chocolate.
说到泡芙，你会想到巧克力。
However, I don't have any cream in my eclair.
但是，我的泡芙里没有奶油。
-No! -A little disappointed.
-不!-有点失望。
I got pastry cream on this side, not on this side.
我这边有奶油，这边没有。
I think your eclairs are a little wonky,
我觉得你的泡芙有点不靠谱，
just a little bit more pastry cream.
再加一点糕点奶油。
Okay.
好吧。
But I definitely taste the pineapple.
但我绝对尝过菠萝的味道。
So great job, Reese. Thanks a lot, man.
干得好，里斯。非常感谢，伙计。
-Thank you. -Thank you, Reese.
-谢谢。-谢谢你，里斯。
REESE: Kind of nervous about the pastry cream
里斯:我对糕点奶油有点紧张
since I didn't put enough in my eclairs for the filling.
因为我没有在泡芙里放足够的馅料。
I don't know what to think.
我不知道该怎么想。
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package...
将会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包…
DUFF: Yeah!
达夫:是啊!
...that includes a feature story
…其中包括一个专题故事
in Food Network Magazine...
在美食网络杂志上…
-Hallelujah! -...and...
哈利路亚!-……
$25,000.
25000美元。
[ Cheering ]
[欢呼]
Winner is coming.
赢家来了。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
All right. Eclairs, the great equalizer.
好吧。泡芙，伟大的均衡器。
Who really stuck out?
谁真正脱颖而出?
-Kaniyah.
-Kaniyah。-Kaniyah。
That cream-cheese filling in her eclair...
她的泡芙里的奶油奶酪馅……
was -- Mwah! -- so tasty.
是——哇!——太好吃了。
It said cherry cheesecake right in there.
上面写着樱桃芝士蛋糕。
She was right about holding back on the sugar.
她说的少吃糖是对的。
Yeah. All right.
是的。好吧。
I got to bring up Justice and his Black Forest cake eclairs.
我得说说正义和他的黑森林蛋糕泡芙。
Justice really did well today.
正义今天表现不错。
Well-baked pâte à choux.
烤得很好的炸土豆条。
And I loved that the filling wasn't overly sweet.
我喜欢馅料不太甜的感觉。
But I loved there was so much of it.
但我喜欢那里有很多东西。
They were packed.
他们都打包好了。
They were packed full of filling.
他们装满了填充物。
Now, I struggled a little bit to get the apricot.
我费了好大劲才拿到杏。
But the way he used it was really creative.
但他使用的方式真的很有创意。
Mm-hmm. All right, Duff.
嗯哼。好吧，达夫。
Whose eclairs needed further eclair-ification today?
今天谁的泡芙需要进一步的泡芙化?
[ Laughs ] That's funny.
(笑)真有趣。
That was a good one.
这是个好主意。
Aidan really let me down today.
艾登今天真让我失望。
I know. I was disappointed, too.
我知道。我也很失望。
And he was disappointed in himself.
他对自己很失望。
He was. Aidan's a great baker.
他是。艾登是个很棒的面包师。
Today was just not his day.
今天他运气不太好。
He would've had the perfect-tasting banana cream pie
他会吃到味道绝佳的香蕉奶油派
had he not put strawberry in a banana cream pie.
要不是他在香蕉奶油派里放了草莓。
Where did strawberry come from? Why strawberry?
草莓是从哪里来的?为什么草莓?
He was trying to cover up those dates
他想掩盖那些日期
because he doesn't like dates.
因为他不喜欢约会。
Okay. We're gonna have to talk
好吧。我们得谈谈
about Maya's little train wreck today.
关于玛雅今天的小事故
Maya had German chocolate cake.
玛雅吃了德国巧克力蛋糕。
I was a little bummed that her filling
我有点郁闷她的补牙
was really just a topping.
其实只是点缀而已。
But it was delicious.
但是很好吃。
I feel like it just could've used a little more umph.
我觉得它应该再多加点味道。
Flat à choux.
平坦的土豆。
But Reese and his pineapple upside-down mess.
但是里瑟和他的菠萝倒过来了。
I thought that the raisins
我以为葡萄干
in the pâte à choux was really clever.
在美国，特·孔丘真的很聪明。
I was very impressed with that.
我对此印象深刻。
Chocolate on a pineapple upside-down cake --
菠萝蛋糕上的巧克力
Where -- Where's that coming from?
你这话是从哪来的?
I don't know.
我不知道。
'Cause you would think like a nice fruity glaze on top.
因为你会想在上面撒上一层水果汁。
Yeah.
是的。
And when I think of eclair also,
当我想到泡芙时，
I think of a stuffed-to-the-gills filling.
我想到的是填充物。
It's really disappointing when you get air.
当你呼吸新鲜空气时，真的很令人失望。
-You know? -Yeah.
-你知道吗?-是的。
So who made the most mistakes today?
那么今天谁犯的错误最多呢?
-Hi.
-你好。-你好。
Hi.
嗨。
AIDAN: I'm really scared about this elimination
艾丹:我真的很害怕被淘汰
just because of all the negative things about my eclair.
就因为那些关于我的泡芙的负面评论。
And I have so much more to show the judges.
我还有很多东西要给评委们看。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
Bakers, your Throwback Dessert Eclairs
面包师们，你们的复古甜点泡芙
offered a fresh take on old-school desserts.
为老式甜品提供了全新的诠释。
And there were two bakers today
今天有两个面包师
that were the most creative at bridging the gap
在弥合差距方面最有创意
between the old and the new.
在新旧之间。
Kaniyah... -Ah!
Kaniyah……——啊!
JASON: Good job, Kaniyah.
杰森:干得好，卡尼亚。
Your cherry cheesecake eclair was beautiful
你的樱桃芝士蛋糕棒极了
as was your reaction just now.
正如你刚才的反应。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Justice.
正义。
-Good job, Justice. -Thank you.
-干得好，法官。-谢谢。
You gave us a Black Forest eclair
你给了我们一个黑森林泡芙
that was packed with flavor
味道很好
and delicious chocolate-cherry cream filling.
还有美味的巧克力樱桃奶油馅。
Now, one of you in particular
现在，特别是你们中的一个
took a tired old throwback
带着疲惫的旧回忆
and turned into a fabulous eclair.
变成了美味的泡芙。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Justice.
…正义。
-Good job. -Congratulations, Justice.
改善工作。恭喜你,正义。
-Thank you. -You got a win.
-谢谢。-你赢了。
Good job, Justice.
干得好，法官。
Both of you will be safe, and we'll see you next week.
你们俩都会安全的，我们下周见。
Yeah.
是的。
I love your dance moves.
我喜欢你的舞步。
Best in town.
城里最好的。
Now, the following bakers' eclairs
下面是面包师的泡芙
were on-trend but slightly off-mark.
我们紧跟潮流，但略有偏离。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
Cole...
科尔……
-...Audra... -Yes! Phew!
——Audra…-是的!唷!
...and...
…和…
-...Jason. -Oh, good.
-…杰森。-哦,好的。
Unfortunately, that leaves Maya,
不幸的是，玛雅
Aidan, and Reese.
艾登和里斯。
Please, step forward.
请往前走。
Kind of expecting it.
有点期待。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
Maya, the pâte à choux on your chocolate eclairs
玛雅，你的巧克力泡芙上有巧克力泡芙
had serious problems.
有严重的问题。
And your filling was really more of a topping.
你的馅料更像是装饰。
Aidan, we question your decision to include strawberries
艾登，我们质疑你放草莓的决定
in your banana cream pie eclair.
在你的香蕉奶油派泡芙里。
Eclairs are one of my favorite things,
泡芙是我最喜欢的食物之一，
and I might go home because of one.
我可能会因为一个而回家。
Reese, your pineapple upside-down cake
里斯，你的菠萝倒立蛋糕
eclairs were inconsistent.
泡芙不稳定。
There was hardly any filling.
几乎没有什么填充物。
Please, Duff, keep me here.
求你了，达夫，把我留在这儿。
Bakers, the more we get to know you,
面包师，我们对你们了解得越多，
the harder this gets.
这就越难。
The baker that will be leaving us today is...
今天要离开我们的面包师是…
**
**
...Maya.
玛雅。
You've been so awesome. You've been fun to watch.
你太棒了。看你表演很有趣。
You're a really, really good baker.
你是一个非常非常好的面包师。
-Thank you. -Can say your goodbyes.
-谢谢。-可以说再见了。
We're gonna miss you, Maya. Oh.
我们会想你的，玛雅。哦。
Oh, you guys!
哦，你们这些家伙!
It's really sad,
这真的很可悲，
but you'll see me probably in the White House
但你可能会在白宫见到我
or probably in space or something big.
或者可能是在太空或其他大的地方。
So watch out for me.
所以要小心我。
VALERIE: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
瓦莱丽:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
DUFF: Throwback dessert, eclairs with dried fruit!
复古甜点，干果泡芙!
There's, like, no way I can do dates.
我根本没法跟人约会。
This dough is perfect, crispy on the outside,
这个面团很完美，表面酥脆，
eggy on the inside.
鸡蛋在里面。
Justice.
正义。
-Good job. -Congratulations.
改善工作。祝贺你。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
MAYA: What the heck?
玛雅:搞什么鬼?
What's up? What's up? What's up?
有什么事吗?有什么事吗?有什么事吗?
My pâte à choux, it's not working.
我的p，不工作了。
I'm seriously worried.
我真的很担心。
The baker leaving us today is Maya.
今天离开的面包师是玛雅。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
-What? -Whoa.
-什么?-啊。
[ Regal music plays ]
[皇家音乐演奏]
-A stack of pancakes. -Tasty.
-一堆煎饼。美味的。
REESE: Valerie's sitting on pancakes.
里斯:瓦莱丽正坐在煎饼上。
And Duff is on a waffle.
达夫在华夫饼上。
Welcome, welcome, welcome, bakers.
欢迎，欢迎，欢迎，面包师们。
Now, Duff and I are having a disagreement.
现在，达夫和我有了分歧。
Oh, boy.
哦,男孩。
It's not really a disagreement, Valerie.
这不是真正的分歧，瓦莱丽
It's a fact.
这是事实。
Waffles are better than pancakes.
华夫饼比煎饼好吃。
Pancakes are boring.
煎饼很无聊。
Pancakes are light and tender.
煎饼又轻又嫩。
And they even make great stacked cakes.
他们甚至会做很棒的叠饼。
-Oh, God. -Oh, boy.
-哦,上帝。-哦,男孩。
So I challenge you to a breakfast cake-off.
所以我向你挑战一场早餐蛋糕比赛。
You guys are weirdos.
你们真是怪胎。
Waffles versus pancakes.
华夫饼vs煎饼。
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no. -Oh, no, no, no.
-不，不，不，不，不。-不，不，不。
Oh, boy.
哦,男孩。
Let's see whose side makes the best dessert.
让我们看看谁做的甜点最好。
KANIYAH: I do not like breakfast for dessert.
我不喜欢把早餐当甜点。
Maybe I can make
也许我可以做早餐当甜点。
But I don't eat breakfast for dessert.
但我不把早餐当甜点吃。
You're on, pancake queen.
来吧，煎饼女王。
Prepare for defeat, king of waffles.
准备失败吧，华夫饼之王。
Bakers, inside this bag are the coins of our realm.
面包师们，这袋子里装的是我们王国的钱币。
The coin you choose will determine
你选择的硬币将决定一切
whether you're making a stacked waffle cake
不管你是在做华夫饼
or a stacked pancake cake.
或者一个堆叠的煎饼蛋糕。
Ladies first. -Me!
女士优先。加!
Go ahead. No peeking.
去做吧。没有偷看。
All right. Come on, boys.
好吧。加油，孩子们。
-Someone broke my hand. -Help.
-有人把我的手弄断了。-。
I got one.
我有一个。
Pancake! You're going down.
煎饼!你要完蛋了。
DUFF: All right, bakers.
达夫:好吧，面包师们。
You have 90 minutes to make a breakfast cake.
你有90分钟做早餐蛋糕。
And to make things more interesting...
为了让事情更有趣……
-Uh-oh. -...this week's winning side,
啊哦。-…本周获胜的一方，
waffles or pancakes... -Pancakes.
华夫饼或煎饼……煎饼。
...will be safe from elimination.
…将不会被淘汰。
[ All gasp ]
[喘气]
AUDRA: I'm so excited.
我太兴奋了。
All of my teammates have won at least one round.
我所有的队友都至少赢过一轮。
I definitely want to be safe this week.
这周我一定要保证安全。
May the best side win.
愿最好的一方获胜。
And your baking time starts...
你的烘焙时间开始了…
BOTH: ...now.
两种:…现在。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Pancakes.
煎饼。
I used to make pancakes a lot,
我以前经常做煎饼，
until I discovered the greatness that is the crepe.
直到我发现了可丽饼的伟大。
And if I win the "Kids Baking Championship,"
如果我赢了"儿童烘焙锦标赛"
I am hoping to open my crepe stand,
我想开个可丽饼摊，
called Jason's Crepes and Bakes.
叫杰森可丽饼店
I'm making a basic vanilla cake.
我在做香草蛋糕。
I'm probably gonna make, like, a buttercream
我可能会做个奶油蛋糕
or some other kind of filling
或者其他的填充物
that you'd usually have in a cake
你通常会把它放在蛋糕里
because we are making pancake cake stacks,
因为我们要做煎饼堆，
not pancake stacks.
不是煎饼堆。
I mix my white cake batter up in a stand mixer.
我把白蛋糕面糊放在立式搅拌机里搅拌。
So light and fluffy.
又轻又蓬松。
It's pancake time.
煎饼时间到了。
The way you're gonna cook your cakes
你做蛋糕的方式
is on a pancake griddle.
是在煎饼煎锅上。
And if you don't have one, you can always use a --
如果没有，你可以用——
a pan and a stove.
一个平底锅和一个炉子。
For me, these pancake cakes,
对我来说，这些煎饼蛋糕
it's definitely difficult
这肯定很难
because this cake breaks easily.
因为这种蛋糕容易碎。
* Ahh! *
*啊!＊
Nailed it!
钉!
Tastes delicious.
尝起来美味。
How are my pancake peeps doing?
我的煎饼嘴怎么样了?
-Good!
-好!-好!
I hate waffles.
我讨厌华夫饼。
[ Gasps ] How dare you?
你怎么敢这样?
Last week, I was in the bottom.
上周，我排名垫底。
And it was horrible.
这太可怕了。
So this week,
所以这周，
I just need to get back in the competition
我只是需要回到比赛中去
and do what I do best.
做我最擅长的事
And that is bake.
这就是bake。
I'm making a cinnamon roll stack of waffles
我要用华夫饼做肉桂卷
with a basic vanilla cake recipe.
一个基本的香草蛋糕食谱。
And then I'm gonna have cream cheese frosting on it.
然后我要在上面撒上奶油芝士糖霜。
It's gonna be delicious.
会很好吃的。
This idea comes from breakfast.
这个想法来自早餐。
I mean, cinnamon rolls,
我是说，肉桂卷
mm, waffles, yummy, yummy.
嗯，华夫饼，好吃，好吃。
My lovely waffle batter.
我可爱的华夫饼面糊。
In anticipation of my victory,
期待着我的胜利
I got some custom jewelry made.
我定制了一些首饰。
There it is. -Very impressive.
就是这个。-非常让人印象深刻。
What do you got?
你有什么发现?
A pat of butter, as every pancake
一块黄油，就像每个煎饼一样
should have a pat of butter.
应该有一块黄油。
Oh! So many strawberries.
哦!这么多草莓。
I like my waffles soft, not soggy, though.
我喜欢松软的华夫饼，不要太湿。
That's just gross.
这太恶心了。
I'm planning on making
我正在计划做什么
a strawberry cheesecake stacked waffle cake,
草莓芝士蛋糕堆叠华夫饼，
then putting cream cheese frosting
然后放入奶油芝士糖霜
in the middle of each layer.
在每层的中间。
I'm starting off with my white cake batter for my waffles.
我要先用白蛋糕糊做华夫饼。
Mm, smells like strawberries.
闻起来像草莓。
I love strawberries,
我喜欢草莓，
favorite fruit in the whole entire world.
全世界最受欢迎的水果。
Let's give this thing a taste.
让我们尝一尝。
Oh, that's really good.
哦，那真是太好了。
This first one is just to see how much time
第一个是看需要多少时间
to cook it for
为之烹饪
and how should I take it out.
我该怎样把它取出来呢?
Oh, my God. It's just ripping.
我的天啊。它在撕裂。
Figuring out how to cook these waffles
想想怎么做这些华夫饼
made of cake batter.
蛋糕糊做的。
It's really not the same.
这真的不一样。
No. It's crumbling.
不。这是摇摇欲坠。
And it's actually pretty soft.
它实际上很软。
This test is a fail.
这次测试失败了。
Guess I'll try another one.
我想我还是试试别的吧。
Pancake batter cake.
煎饼面糊蛋糕。煎饼面糊蛋糕。
I have been making pancakes since I was 7.
我从7岁起就开始做煎饼了。
So this should be pretty easy.
这应该很简单。
I'm gonna kind of do a rainbow effect on my pancake.
我要在我的煎饼上做一个彩虹的效果。
It's going to be a lemon cake.
这将是一个柠檬蛋糕。
Filling is going to be maybe raspberry or blueberry.
馅料可能是覆盆子或蓝莓。
I'm doing lemon and rainbow because I want it to stand out.
我要做柠檬和彩虹，因为我想让它脱颖而出。
I think that's enough.
我想这就够了。
I'm separating my batter
我把面糊分开
to make it three different colors.
让它有三种不同的颜色。
I like these colors.
我喜欢这些颜色。
Check out Kaniyah, man.
看看卡尼亚，伙计。
Those are some bright pancakes.
那些是鲜亮的煎饼。
Think I'll add more lemon juice.
我想我该再加点柠檬汁。
I'm adding more lemon juice
我在加点柠檬汁
because it wasn't lemon enough.
因为它不够柠檬。
I want to get this just right for the queen of pancakes
我想把它做得恰到好处，成为煎饼女王
that's sitting on a pile of butter and plastic syrup.
它就在一堆黄油和塑料糖浆上。
There's that lemon taste.
有柠檬的味道。
My dad gave me this tip.
我爸爸给了我这个建议。
When the pancake bubbles
当煎饼冒泡时
in the middle and around the edges,
在中间和边缘，
that means it's ready to be flipped.
这意味着可以翻转了。
Come on. Come on. I taste my test pancake.
来吧。来吧。我尝了试吃的煎饼。
And it tastes good.
而且味道很好。
It's lemon.
这是柠檬。
It's great.
太棒了。
Aidan, do you still have the cinnamon?
艾登，肉桂还在吗?
-Yeah. -Can I use it?
-是的。-我可以用吗?
-Yeah. I'm all done. -Thanks.
-是的。我都做完了。-谢谢。
Valerie, I'll be your loyal subject.
瓦莱丽，我会是你忠实的臣民。
I think pancakes are better because
我觉得煎饼更好，因为
that's what I cook for my family about every week.
这就是我每周为我的家人做的东西。
My cake that I'll be making to transform into a pancake
我的蛋糕，我要把它变成煎饼
will be a carrot cake.
将是一个胡萝卜蛋糕。
The filling will be a cream cheese buttercream.
馅料是奶油芝士奶油。
I grab cinnamon and carrots.
我拿了肉桂和胡萝卜。
And I start to make a classic white cake.
我开始做一个经典的白蛋糕。
Justice, look at this carrot.
正义，看看这根胡萝卜。
Duff, I'm shaving carrots.
达夫，我在刮胡萝卜。
If you ever need me to cut your hair, call me.
如果你需要我帮你剪头发，打电话给我。
I want a carrot in every bite.
我要每一口都像胡萝卜。
Cinnamon and nutmeg, I'm just measuring by look.
肉桂和肉豆蔻，我只是根据外表来衡量。
And I think using more spices
我想多用些香料
will bring a nice darker color to my pancake cake.
会给我的煎饼蛋糕带来漂亮的深色。
I want more nutmeg.
我想要更多的肉豆蔻。
I'm ready to start making my pancake.
我准备开始做煎饼了。
I have never used a cake batter to make pancakes.
我从来没用蛋糕糊做煎饼。
So they keep breaking.
所以它们一直在断裂。
And I hope that I can figure out a way so that it can work.
我希望我能想出一个办法，让它能起作用。
Gosh, my pancakes are not flipping.
天啊，我的煎饼不动了。
All my pancakes are breaking apart.
我所有的煎饼都裂开了。
It fell apart.
它崩溃了。
All right.
好吧。
Reese's batter is kind of thin.
里斯的面糊有点薄。
VALERIE: Oh, it really looks like he's struggling
瓦莱丽:哦，看起来他真的很挣扎
to flip his pancakes without breaking them.
翻转他的煎饼而不打碎它们。
I'm probably gonna have to build my cake
我可能得做我的蛋糕了
out of the broken pancake.
从破碎的煎饼里。
Oh.
哦。
I have a joke.
我有个笑话。
So the griddle says to the waffle iron,
所以烤盘对烤松饼机说，
"You're pretty cute."
“你很可爱。”
And the waffle iron says [Laughing]
华夫饼烤盘上写着[笑]
"Stop buttering me up."
“别拍我马屁了。”
I got the waffle coin.
我拿到了华夫饼硬币。
And I'm gonna make a chocolate hazelnut spread waffle
我要做一个巧克力榛子华夫饼
with chocolate-covered strawberry
巧克力草莓
cream cheese buttercream.
奶油芝士奶油。
And hopefully, if I have time,
希望，如果我有时间，
I'm gonna put some bacon strips in between each layer.
我要在每层之间放一些培根条。
I get to making my cake batter.
我开始做蛋糕面糊了。
I chose to use my favorite chocolate cake recipe
我选择用我最喜欢的巧克力蛋糕食谱
'cause it goes with strawberries,
因为它和草莓很搭
goes with hazelnut spread.
搭配榛子酱。
And I wanted it to taste like chocolate-dipped bacon.
我想让它尝起来像巧克力培根。
And I put it in the waffle iron.
我把它放进了华夫饼烤盘。
And it smells so good.
闻起来真香。
Is this a perfect waffle to you?
这华夫饼对你来说完美吗?
Is it a chocolate waffle?
是巧克力华夫饼吗?
Okay. 'Cause if it was not a chocolate waffle,
好吧。因为如果不是巧克力华夫饼
I'd say it's pretty burnt.
我得说它烧焦了。
You should get a waffle tattoo.
你应该纹个华夫饼纹身。
I should get
我应该纹个华夫饼纹身。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. We'll see who wins.
对，对，对，对。我们看看谁会赢。
All right. Hey. Here's the thing.
好吧。嘿。事情是这样的。
Team Waffles. -Yeah?
团队华夫饼干。-是吗?
If you guys bring home the gold,
如果你们能拿回金牌，
I will go out and get a waffle tattoo.
我要出去纹个华夫饼。
-Will you actually? -Yeah.
-你真的会吗?-是的。
That's extra motivation.
这是额外的动力。
And guess what, Team Pancakes?
你猜怎么着，煎饼队?
I won't. -Lame.
我不会的。站不住脚的。
I'm lame.
我是瘸腿的。
Butter, butter, butter, butter, butter,
黄油，黄油，黄油，黄油，黄油
butter, butter.
黄油，黄油，黄油，黄油。
I pledge of allegiance to the waffle
我宣誓效忠华夫饼
of the United Waffles of Wafflelandia.
华夫饼的联合华夫饼
I am going to make an orange cake.
我要做一个橘子蛋糕。
And I'll do, like, maybe an orange curd in the middle.
我可能会在中间放一点橘子凝乳。
And I might do a strawberry buttercream.
我可能会做草莓奶油。
And then I'll decorate it with, like,
然后我会装饰一下，比如，
orange slices and strawberries.
桔子片和草莓。
For my waffle cake batter,
做我的华夫饼面糊，
I add some vanilla and some orange extract.
我加入一些香草和橙汁。
I put the orange in there
我把橘子放进去了
'cause it's a complete balanced breakfast.
因为这是一份完全均衡的早餐。
I'm adding orange sprinkles because orange sprinkles
我要加橙屑，因为橙屑
will be like confetti orange cake.
会像橘色的彩纸蛋糕。
And I think that'll look cool in my waffles.
我觉得放在我的华夫饼里会很酷。
I'm not a breakfast guy. I really like to sleep.
我不喜欢吃早餐。我真的很喜欢睡觉。
When your waffle's done, you want a crispy outside shell
当你的华夫饼做好了，你想要一个脆的外壳
and a nice warm inside.
里面也很暖和。
Yes.
是的。
I'm surveying my kingdom.
我在调查我的王国。
Hot.
热。
Waffle time.
华夫饼干。
The thing that will make this waffle stack special
让华夫饼变得特别的东西
is my cinnamon brown sugar butter swirl mixture.
这是我的肉桂红糖黄油漩涡混合物。
It will be a nice, thick, almost kind of a sludge,
它会变成一种粘稠的污泥，
but the best possible sludge.
但是最好的污泥。
Okay. It's too chunky.
好吧。它太粗了。
My cinnamon mixture is a lot thicker
我的肉桂粉更浓
than I thought it would be.
比我想象的要多
There's, like, big chunks, and they get stuck.
有大块的，然后就卡住了。
By the time I get it all in,
等我都放进去的时候，
the bottoms of my waffles
我华夫饼的底部
are probably a lot more cooked than the top is gonna be.
可能比上面熟得多。
I'm just hoping that this turns out right.
我只是希望这事能顺利进行。
So I just close up the waffle iron and let it cook.
所以我把烤盘合上，让它烤熟。
But I definitely overfilled them.
但我确实填得太多了。
This isn't going as fun as I thought.
这可不像我想的那么有趣。
When I make waffles at home,
我在家做华夫饼的时候，
I just don't usually go over the top.
我只是不太会过分。
And this is more complicated.
这个更复杂。
Okay. Darn swirl.
好吧。该死的漩涡。
Um...It's stuck.
嗯…卡住了。
They're all sticking.
他们都黏在一起了。
And I try to get the tongs.
我试着拿钳子。
And by the time I get them out, they're just all mangled up.
等我把它们拿出来的时候，它们已经碎了。
And they're gross. It's just falling apart.
而且它们很恶心。它正在分崩离析。
I can't use this.
我不能用这个。
This is gonna have to be pitched.
这事得先定下来。
These are the worst waffles ever.
这是史上最难吃的华夫饼。
Duff, my waffles turned out horrible.
达夫，我的华夫饼太难吃了。
I cannot use these mangled-up waffles.
我不能用这些乱七八糟的华夫饼。
Come on, Aidan. Pull it together, man.
别这样，艾登。振作起来，伙计。
In the garbage.
在垃圾里。
I have to completely recook my waffles.
我得把我的华夫饼彻底换掉。
Thankfully, I have lots of batter left.
谢天谢地，我还有很多面糊。
I am not gonna overfill these again.
我不会再把这个放满了。
Bakers, may we have your attention?
面包师们，请注意了?
-Oh! -Uh-oh.
-哦!啊哦。
I just don't want to know.
我只是不想知道。
We are taking this challenge to the next level.
我们要把这个挑战提升到一个新的水平。
In order to make the ultimate breakfast desserts,
为了做出终极早餐甜点，
you also have to use one breakfast cereal
你还得吃一份早餐麦片
to decorate your cake.
来装饰你的蛋糕。
-Yes, yes, yes! -Whoa.
-是的，是的，是的!-啊。
-No. -What?
-不。-什么?
We are providing you with all kinds of cereal
我们为您提供各种谷物
to choose from.
从…中选择
Must choose wisely.
必须明智地选择。
AIDAN: All right. This is perfect.
艾丹:好吧。这是完美的。
I see a delicious cinnamon cereal
我看到了美味的肉桂麦片
that will pair perfectly with everything else.
和其他东西搭配起来会很完美。
Waffles!
华夫饼!
-Pancakes. -I will -- I will -- I will...
煎饼。-我会的——我会的——我会的……
What's it gonna be, Audra?
会是什么，奥德拉?
No idea because none of this stuff
不知道，因为这些东西都不是
goes with what I'm making.
和我做的很搭。
Wait. Wait. Okay.
等待。等待。好吧。
-Trust your instincts.
-相信你的直觉。-相信你的直觉。
But you better get moving.
但你最好马上行动。
AUDRA: I decide to choose corn cereal
我决定选玉米麦片
because it seems like kind of a vanilla flavor.
因为它看起来像是香草味的。
And I think it might go with my cake a little bit.
我觉得它和我的蛋糕很搭。
I'm only using it in the decoration
我只在装饰中使用它
and maybe in between some layers.
也许在两层之间。
Perfect. This time when I cook my waffles,
完美的。这次我做华夫饼的时候，
they come out pretty darn good.
结果非常好。
Well, I guess I'll prepare my frosting.
我想我该准备我的糖霜了。
To make my cream cheese frosting,
做奶油芝士糖霜，
I cream together my powdered sugar
我把糖粉搅在一起
and my cream cheese and butter
还有我的奶油奶酪和黄油
until that is ooey, gooey and delicious.
直到它变得粘稠可口。
Icing.
糖衣。
So Waffle Kingdom is known for stability.
所以华夫饼王国以稳定著称。
But you're a little crusty on the outside.
但你的外表有点硬。
We are a little crusty
我们的外表有点硬。
That's what gives us our backbone, our spine.
这就是我们的脊椎骨。
I'm light and fluffy.
我又轻又蓬松。
I don't know if you want to be fluffy.
我不知道你想不想变蓬松。
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
是的，是的，是的，是的!
Fruit rice cereal, substitute for sprinkles.
水果米麦片，代替糖屑。
And that's gonna look good on top of my cake.
放在蛋糕上一定很好看。
This is going great. Great.
进展得很顺利。太好了。
Kaniyah is dancing a lot more than usual.
Kaniyah跳得比平时多了。
Dance montage.
舞蹈蒙太奇。
**
**
Boom. This is awesome.
繁荣。这太棒了。
So I'm gonna start my buttercream.
我要开始做奶油了。
For my buttercream, it's just butter and powdered sugar.
我的奶油奶油，只有黄油和糖粉。
Ah. And I think it's gonna go really well
啊。我觉得会很顺利的
with the lemon cake.
还有柠檬蛋糕。
We're all friends. But waffles suck.
我们都是朋友。但是华夫饼糟透了。
I know it's ready to go when it looks like buttercream.
当它看起来像奶油的时候，我就知道可以吃了。
Raspberries.
树莓。
Then I start on my raspberry puree.
然后开始做覆盆子泥。
And I need sugar to make it sweet.
我需要糖来让它变甜。
I'm straining my puree to make sure there are no seeds
我把泥过滤一下，确保没有籽
because that would be nasty.
因为那样会很恶心。
Okay. Got this.
好吧。得到这个。
This is the moment of truth
这是关键时刻
because if my waffles don't turn out, it's over.
因为如果我的华夫饼做不出来，就完了。
This is my second attempt.
这是我第二次尝试。
And I don't have enough batter to do a third one.
我没有足够的面糊来做第三个。
Wow.
哇。
Now, that is a waffle. Whoo.
这就是华夫饼。喔!
So I get those in the blast chiller
我把它们放进冷风机里
and start my frosting.
开始做糖霜。
What's everyone think of the twist?
大家怎么看这个转折?
I'm just gonna sprinkle it wherever I can.
我要把它撒在我能撒的地方。
I got corn flakes
我有玉米片
because they're just nice and, like, simple.
因为它们很好，很简单。
I plan on using my cereal
我打算用我的麦片
on top of my orange curd in each layer
每一层都放在我的橘子凝乳上面
and then on top of my cake.
然后放在我的蛋糕上。
Audra, are you gonna use all those strawberries?
奥德拉，你要用所有的草莓吗?
No. Actually, I'm done with the strawberries.
不。事实上，我已经吃完了草莓。
Oh. Yeah. I need strawberries
哦。是的。我需要草莓
to make my strawberry buttercream.
做我的草莓奶油。
I put them through the strainer.
我把它们通过过滤器。
And I get all the nice strawberry juices out.
我把所有美味的草莓汁都弄出来了。
And I start to whip up my buttercream.
我开始搅拌奶油。
And it turned out really good.
结果非常好。
45 minutes left, bakers.
还有45分钟，面包师们。
45 minutes.
45分钟。
I'm making my third waffle, and my curd's on the stove.
我在做第三块华夫饼，我的凝乳在炉子上。
And I'm feeling pretty good about time.
我对时间感觉很好。
I think I'll be able to get this done
我想我能把这件事做完
and make it look beautiful.
让它看起来很漂亮。
-Team Waffles! -Pancakes!
团队华夫饼干!煎饼!
You need some butter for your waffle?
你的华夫饼需要黄油吗?
[ Laughing ]
[笑]
In each layer, I want to put fresh roasted hazelnuts.
在每一层里，我想放上新鲜的烤榛子。
So I put 'em in the oven, just to get 'em a little toasty.
所以我把它们放进烤箱，让它们稍微烤一下。
When you roast any nut,
当你烤坚果的时候，
it really brings out their oils.
它真的能把它们的油脂带出来。
And you can taste the flavors.
你可以品尝它的味道。
I'm gonna get started on my bacon.
我要开始做熏肉了。
But this bacon is, like, so thick.
但这培根太厚了。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
It's just gonna take more time
只是需要更多的时间
'cause you have to cook it way longer.
因为你得煮得更久。
Hot.
热。
Is that bacon? [ Sniffing ]
那是培根吗?[嗅闻]
All right. Everyone can stop.
好吧。每个人都可以停下来。
We got a winner.
我们有赢家了。
Not fair.
不公平的。
For the twist today,
对于今天的转折，
I'm using a cinnamon crunch cereal
我用的是肉桂脆脆麦片
because it's a cinnamon chocolate cake.
因为这是肉桂巧克力蛋糕。
So it'll work really well
所以效果会很好
with everything else that's on it.
还有上面的所有东西。
Next, I have to make my chocolate
接下来，我要做巧克力
strawberry cream cheese frosting.
草莓奶油芝士糖霜。
Chocolate!
巧克力!
I taste it.
我尝了尝。
And it is way, way, way sweet.
而且非常非常非常甜蜜。
So I need to add more salt.
所以我需要加更多盐。
If I knew when I was a kid
如果我小时候知道的话
that I could stick cake batter in a waffle iron,
我可以把蛋糕糊粘在华夫饼烤盘里
I probably would've burnt the house down.
我可能会把房子烧了。
But, man, I would have been excited.
但是，伙计，我会很兴奋的。
Well, I think this is actually gonna make my thing better.
我觉得这能让我的作品变得更好。
I choose fruit rice cereal because it's delicious.
我选择水果米粥，因为它很好吃。
I'm making a traditional vanilla buttercream
我在做传统的香草奶油
and a little sprinkle of my rainbow rice cereal.
再撒一点我的彩虹米粥。
I hope it doesn't go mushy in my buttercream.
我希望它在我的奶油里不会变成糊状。
I want to make a raspberry syrup.
我想做覆盆子糖浆。
To the pot of hot water,
对着那壶热水，
I add the raspberry jam and some cornstarch.
我加入覆盆子果酱和一些玉米淀粉。
Jason, those pancakes are, like, perfect.
杰森，那些煎饼，简直太完美了。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Yours are looking, uh, where are your pancakes?
你的在找，你的煎饼呢?
Uh, not good.
不太好。
30 minutes left, bakers.
还有30分钟，面包师们。
I'm really frustrated
我真的很沮丧
that my pancakes are not flipping.
我的煎饼没有翻。
The pancake is just getting smushed together.
烧饼快要糊在一起了。
Try using some oil, some spray.
试着用一些油，一些喷雾。
No way.
不可能。
I forgot my butter because I'm so worried
我忘了带黄油，因为我太担心了
that I'm not gonna finish in time.
我不能及时完成的任务
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary chocolate cake stacks up
解说员:普通的巧克力蛋糕堆积起来
into delicious donut cake right after this.
吃个甜甜圈蛋糕。
ANNOUNCER: How to make stacked donut cakes --
解说员:如何制作堆叠的甜甜圈蛋糕
Gather together a donut pan, cake batter,
准备一个甜甜圈锅，蛋糕面糊，
chocolate glaze and candy sprinkles.
巧克力釉和糖屑。
Pour the batter into donut molds
将面糊倒入甜甜圈模具中
and bake off your donuts.
然后把你的甜甜圈烤掉。
Dip donuts into glaze.
将甜甜圈浸入釉中。
Stack them up and add some festive sprinkles.
把它们堆起来，撒上一些节日的糖屑。
Make a stacked donut party.
做一个堆叠的甜甜圈派对。
For more fun treats like this,
想要获得更多这样的乐趣，
visit foodnetwork.com/ kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/ kidsbaking。
Dang it. You got to be kidding me. I forgot my butter.
讨厌它。你在开玩笑吧。我忘了带黄油。
I hope this will help my pancakes
我希望这对我的煎饼有帮助
stay together now.
现在待在一起。
Yay. My pancakes are working.
耶。我的煎饼很好吃。
Whew. I'm ready to start my frosting.
唷。我可以开始做糖霜了。
So I get my cream cheese, butter, and cream that.
所以我准备了奶油奶酪，黄油和奶油。
I have to have it all the way mixed.
我必须把它们全部混合。
And I'm gonna be putting my fruity cereal in my butter.
我要把我的水果麦片放进黄油里。
That's exactly what I did.
我就是这么做的。
Oh, wow. You get, like, a crunch with your frosting.
哦,哇。你的糖霜会嘎吱作响。
It looks pretty cool, like a rainbow.
看起来很酷，像彩虹一样。
DUFF: You guys need to start stacking your cakes.
达夫:你们得开始叠蛋糕了。
You got, like, 3 minutes left.
你还剩3分钟。
No, I'm kidding.
不，我开玩笑的。
-JK. -Kidding.
jk。在开玩笑。
You do have 20 minutes left.
你还剩20分钟。
Team Waffles, you've got to win.
华夫饼队，你们一定要赢。
I want this tattoo.
我想要这个纹身。
JUSTICE: He's not gonna get, like,
JUSTICE:他不会得到，
"Waffle Team" tattooed on his arm.
手臂上纹着"华夫饼队"
Why would he do that?
他为什么要这么做?
Where? Where?
在哪里?在哪里?在哪里?在哪里?
I'm ready to start building my cake.
我准备开始做蛋糕了。
Before I started putting my curd in,
在我开始放凝乳之前，
I tasted it to make sure it tastes like orange.
我尝了一下，以确保它尝起来像橙子。
And it doesn't taste a lot like orange.
而且尝起来也不太像橙子。
So I decided to get some orange extract
所以我决定弄点橙汁
and put that in there as well.
把这个也放进去。
And now it tastes more orange-y.
现在尝起来更橙了。
Justice is the only baker using curd.
正义是唯一一个用凝乳的面包师。
VALERIE: I love curd.
瓦莱丽:我喜欢凝乳。
Let them eat curd.
让他们吃凝乳。
So I start by making a dam around each waffle,
所以我先在每个华夫饼周围做一个水坝，
putting some curd in between that, cereal in.
中间放些凝乳，麦片。
-That looks amazing. -Do you really think so?
-看起来很棒。-你真的这么认为吗?
It's pretty good.
非常好。
And then I cover the top with the strawberry buttercream.
然后在上面涂上草莓奶油。
And I pipe a little border around my cake.
我在蛋糕周围画了一个小边。
That is professional piping.
这是专业的管弦乐。
-Waffles. -Pancakes.
华夫饼干。煎饼。
I need to get started on stacking.
我得开始叠东西了。
So I put a little bit of hazelnut spread down,
所以我放了一点榛子酱，
stick the waffle on, spread my buttercream,
把华夫饼放上去，涂上奶油，
put a ring of hazelnut spread around,
在四周放一圈榛子，
fresh strawberries,
新鲜的草莓,
toasted hazelnuts,
烤榛子、
cinnamon crunch cereal, stacked.
肉桂脆麦片，堆叠起来。
Forgot the bacon.
忘了培根了。
This big bake is so important
这次大烤太重要了
because I want to be the first boy
因为我想当第一个男孩
"Kids Baking" champion.
儿童烘焙大赛冠军。
And I want that $25,000.
我要那两万五千美元。
Snowing in Waffletown.
华夫镇下雪了。
Oh, my God. It's looking, uh, boo-tiful.
我的天啊。它看起来，嗯，很漂亮。
Wafflelites, winner is coming.
华夫精英们，赢家来了。
-Really? -In Waffletown?
-真的?——Waffletown吗?
Are there actual humans?
真的有人类吗?
Or are they, like, walking waffles?
还是像会走路的华夫饼?
-No. They're humans. -Humans.
-不。他们是人类。人类。
Yeah. Everybody's a human.
是的。每个人都是人。
Oh, it smells like heaven.
闻起来像天堂。
Frosting, in my book, is what really makes a cake.
在我看来，糖霜才是蛋糕的关键。
When I was little, I used to like the frosting
当我小的时候，我喜欢吃糖霜
more than the cake.
不仅仅是蛋糕。
And I might actually like it a bit more now.
我现在可能更喜欢它了。
Come on, cream cheese.
来吧，奶油奶酪。来吧，奶油奶酪。
Come on...Mm.
来吧……毫米。
I'm going to have cream cheese frosting between each layer
我要在每层之间撒上奶油芝士糖霜
and sprinkle on pecans and cereal...
撒上山核桃和麦片……
Nice little crunch.
嘎吱嘎吱。
And then repeat that process.
然后重复这个过程。
Look at my stack.
看看我的堆栈。
Don't you think it looks great?
你不觉得很好看吗?
I mean, it's a'ight. No. It looks awesome.
我是说，这是一场比赛。不。看起来棒极了。
My waffle stack is gonna be
我的华夫饼堆会
a more rustic stack of waffles.
一堆更质朴的华夫饼。
I grab some cinnamon sticks
我拿了一些肉桂棒
and put those on in a nice little cross fashion.
把它们串成漂亮的十字形。
I love cinnamon.
我喜欢肉桂。
Face it, Val.
面对现实吧，瓦尔。
Waffles are just more exciting than pancakes.
华夫饼比煎饼更让人兴奋。
Think of the royal Belgian waffle.
想想皇家比利时华夫饼吧。
No idea what's in that.
不知道里面有什么。
Pancakes are literally a cake made in a pan.
煎饼就是在平底锅里做的蛋糕。
Semantics, Val.
语义,瓦尔。
Semantics.
语义。
JASON: It's time to start stacking.
杰森:是时候开始堆叠了。
Spread the buttercream, lay a pancake.
铺上奶油，铺上煎饼。
Spread buttercream, lay pancake.
涂上奶油，铺好煎饼。
It's not the prettiest thing, but...
这不是最漂亮的东西，但是……
The cherry on top
锦上添花
will make this thing look awesome.
会让这东西看起来很棒。
I grab my "raspberry syrup"...
我抓起我的“覆盆子糖浆”……
It's more of a spread now.
现在更像是一种扩散。
Spread that on top of my pancake stack.
把它铺在我的煎饼堆上。
I'm liking this challenge.
我喜欢这个挑战。
For my topping, I mix cream cheese,
我的浇头是奶油奶酪，
milk and powdered sugar.
牛奶和糖粉。
Yummy.
美味的。
Perfect.
完美的。
I'm gonna get stacking my cakes.
我要开始叠蛋糕了。
Stack 'em. Stack 'em. Stack 'em.
叠起来，叠起来，叠起来。
I pipe a ring of icing around on the edge of the pancake.
我在煎饼的边缘涂上一圈糖霜。
And then I fill it with the raspberry filling.
然后我把覆盆子馅填进去。
The buttercream ring is gonna help
奶油戒指会有帮助的
keep the raspberry filling kept inside
把覆盆子馅放在里面
and not have it go, "Phbt!"
而不是说"Phbt!"
Somebody's going home on the waffles team.
有人要随华夫饼队回家了。
10 minutes left!
还剩10分钟!
Okay. I'm doing good.
好吧。我很好。
So hurry up!
所以快点!
'Kay!
“凯!
REESE: Wonder if any of these pancakes will work.
里斯:不知道这些煎饼是否有用。
They're all messed up.
他们都搞砸了。
I'm starting to assemble my cake.
我开始做蛋糕了。
And I build my cake by, like,
我做蛋糕的时候，
getting pieces from broken pancakes
从碎煎饼上捡碎片
and put that together.
把它们放在一起。
No. I'm, like, making a puzzle right now,
不。我现在在做一个谜题，
but with pancakes.
但是煎饼。
It's leaning!
倾斜!
It might not look like a perfect cake.
它可能看起来不像一个完美的蛋糕。
But it does look like a decent plate of pancakes.
但它看起来确实像一盘不错的煎饼。
Yay. 10 layers.
耶，10层。
I want to put chocolate and a cherry on top of my cake
我想在蛋糕上放巧克力和樱桃
because I think that would be pretty nice for presentation.
因为我觉得这对展示来说很好。
There's a lot of pressure to make this cake really well.
要做好这个蛋糕压力很大。
The clock is my enemy.
时钟是我的敌人。
Three minutes!
三分钟!
Waffle Team rocks!
华夫饼队棒极了!
-How are you doing? -Good.
-你好吗?改善情况。
-My stack's all done. -Oh, great.
-我的那堆都做完了。-哦,太棒了。
To assemble my cake, first add the waffle.
要组装蛋糕，首先加入华夫饼。
Then I add some cream cheese, add some puree.
然后我加一些奶油奶酪，一些泥。
Not the best presentation, but it'll taste delicious.
不是最好的展示，但尝起来很美味。
Sprinkle some of the corn cereal on,
撒上一些玉米麦片，
put some more cream cheese and waffle.
再放些奶油奶酪和华夫饼。
And I just keep repeating that
我一直在重复
until my cake is all assembled.
直到我的蛋糕全部组装好。
I just need a little more frosting.
我只需要再加一点糖霜。
It's really messy, which I'm worried about.
真的很乱，我很担心。
[ Gasps ] Oh, no.
(喘息)哦，不。
-Oh, no. -Oh, man.
-哦,不。-哦,男人。
Audra, honey.
Audra,亲爱的。
Waffle tectonics.
华夫格构造。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
It looks like a giant cream cheese monster
它看起来像一个巨大的奶油奶酪怪物
is getting hacked to pieces.
被砍成碎片。
[ Gasps ] Oh, no. This is terrible.
(喘息)哦，不。这太可怕了。
Oh, no. Okay.
哦,不。好吧。
A big chunk of my cake falls out.
我的蛋糕掉了一大块。
And I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我不知道我该怎么办。
Oh. Oh, no.
哦。哦,不。
There's no recovering from this avalanche.
从这场雪崩中无法恢复。
Audra's waffle stack has just collapsed.
奥德拉的华夫饼堆塌了。
And this does not look good for my side.
这对我这边来说可不太好。
-Dang it! -Two minutes.
见鬼了!两分钟。
We want to see a waffle cake and a pancake.
我们想要一个华夫饼和一个煎饼。
Cake.
蛋糕。
Pancake... Right.
煎饼……正确的。
Fruit cereal.
水果谷物。
It looks awesome.
看起来棒极了。
I'll pipe a "P" for pancake.
我会用"P"来表示煎饼。
There.
在那里。
This brings me so much joy.
这给我带来了很多快乐。
Oh, look at that.
哦，看那个。
Aidan is making ice cream, little extra credit.
艾登在做冰淇淋，一点额外学分。
Waffles and ice cream, man.
华夫饼和冰淇淋，伙计。
Yum.
好吃。
A waffle stack a la mode.
华夫饼加蛋黄酱。
Cinnamon crunch cereal ice cream.
肉桂脆脆麦片冰淇淋。
I have my bowl of milk and cereal with my ice cream.
我有一碗牛奶和麦片和我的冰淇淋。
I don't care if it gets soggy.
我不管它是不是湿透了。
I just want it to have a little cinnamon.
我只想加一点肉桂。
Oh. Delicious.
哦。美味。
I just want to straight eat this.
我只想直接吃这个。
What's stopping me?
是什么阻止了我?
My dignity.
我的尊严。
30 seconds, guys.
30秒，伙计们。
Go, go, go, bakers!
走，走，走，面包师们!
Reese, please get your cake made.
里斯，请把你的蛋糕做好。
We're running out of time.
我们没时间了。
-I'm trying. -Do you need help?
我尝试。-你需要帮助吗?
Well, can you get me a cherry?
你能给我一颗樱桃吗?
-Uh, sure. -Even though Justice
-嗯,当然。-即使是正义
is on the waffle side, he still helped me.
在华夫饼那边，他还是帮了我。
And I'm really thankful for that.
对此我非常感激。
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Just put -- scoop some on.
快点，快点，快点。把——舀上一点。
Now if I could just stop the clock...
现在如果我能让时钟停止……
Cherry on top now? Or...
现在锦上添花了?还是……
Yeah. Sure.
是的。确定。
DUFF AND VALERIE: 10...9...8...7...6...
达夫和瓦莱丽:10……9……8……7……6……
5...4...3...2...1!
5…4 3…2…1 !
DUFF: Hands up!
达夫:举起手来!
All righty.
好了。
It is the great breakfast bake-off.
这是一场伟大的早餐烘烤比赛。
-Yes. Yes. -We asked for pancake cakes...
-是的。是的。我们要的是煎饼……
-Mm-hmm. -...and waffle cakes.
-嗯。-…还有华夫饼。
Bring on the breakfast!
把早餐端上来!
Shall we call in Audra?
要不要叫奥德拉来?
I think we should.
我想我们应该。
-Audra? -Hi.
audra吗?-你好。
Tell us about your waffle cake.
跟我们说说你的华夫饼吧。
For my waffle cake, I made a strawberry cheesecake.
我做的华夫饼是草莓芝士蛋糕。
And the cream cheese frosting is the cheesecake.
奶油芝士糖霜就是芝士蛋糕。
For my cereal, I got corn cereal.
我的麦片是玉米麦片。
And I kind of just sprinkled those everywhere.
我把它们撒得到处都是。
It's a little messy, only a little.
有点乱，只有一点点。
Where's the waffle?
华夫饼在哪里?
Oh.
哦。
Um, under the frosting?
在糖霜下面?
Well, it definitely looks like
嗯，看起来确实像
that fell apart a little bit.
这有点支离破碎。
I want to taste that thing.
我想尝尝那东西。
I really don't want to go home.
我真的不想回家。
I've already told my cat, Rory, that if I win,
我已经告诉我的猫罗里，如果我赢了，
she's gonna get a bunch of toys.
她会得到一堆玩具。
So I can't let her down.
所以我不能让她失望。
Nice. Nice crispy waffle right here.
好了。脆脆的华夫饼就在这里。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
That's exactly what you want in a waffle.
这正是你想要的华夫饼。
I'm loving the flavor.
我喜欢它的味道。
Seems like the frosting's a little sweet.
看起来糖霜有点甜。
I don't really taste the cream cheese
我尝不出奶油奶酪的味道
as much as I taste the sugar.
就像我尝到糖的味道一样。
The cereal's not working like I thought it would.
麦片粥不像我想的那样起作用。
When it's in the layers,
当它在图层中，
It just kind of gets chewy. -But listen.
只是有点难嚼。但听。
You got great waffles here. -Mm-hmm.
你这里的华夫饼很好吃。-嗯。
I could really taste the strawberries.
我真的能尝到草莓的味道。
It's nice. Thanks.
它很好。谢谢。
-Bye. -Why is she so sad?
再见。-她为什么这么伤心?
She was hanging her head.
她垂着头。
I don't want to hurt her feelings.
我不想伤害她的感情。
She knows she didn't do a good job.
她知道自己做得不好。
Justice.
正义。
That looks spectacular.
看起来很壮观。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
This is what you should be doing in life.
这是你一生中应该做的事情。
So for my waffle cake,
做华夫饼的时候，
I made an orange cake
我做了一个橘子蛋糕
and then orange curd to go in between each layer.
然后在每层之间放入橙凝乳。
And I sprinkled corn flakes on top of the cake.
我把玉米片撒在蛋糕上。
I also piped strawberry buttercream
我还吹了草莓奶油
around each one and then did it on top, too.
在每一个周围，然后把它放在上面。
That's amazing.
这是惊人的。
I love your color palette. -Mm-hmm.
我喜欢你的配色。-嗯。
I mean, everything goes together.
我的意思是，所有的东西都在一起。
It's absolutely beautiful.
真是太美了。
Let's taste it.
让我们尝一尝。
Well, Duff, I can be a worker at Charm City Cakes.
达夫，我可以去魅力城市蛋糕店工作。
Delicious waffles.
美味的蛋奶烘饼。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
They're moist where they should be moist.
本该湿润的地方却湿润了。
They're crispy where they should be crispy.
应该酥脆的地方却变脆了。
I mean, your buttercream is really good.
我是说，你的奶油真的很好吃。
I love the use of the cereal.
我喜欢麦片的味道。
You got a little tiny crunch in there.
你这儿有点脆。
The one thing I can say is I think you used
我唯一能说的是我觉得你用了
a tiny bit too much of the zest.
柠檬皮放多了一点。
Yeah.
是的。
The curd is almost too sweet.
这豆腐几乎太甜了。
And it's almost too bitter.
而且它几乎太苦了。
It really needs to be evened out.
真的需要平衡一下。
But you're really coming into your own
但你真的要进入自己的状态了
late in this contest.
在这场比赛的后期。
And you're just shooting for it, aren't you?
而你正在努力争取，不是吗?
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Thank you, Justice. -Thank you.
谢谢你，法官。-谢谢。
-Thanks, man. -This is not a good curd.
-谢谢,伙计。-这不是一个好的凝乳。
He could have left the curd out.
他可能把凝乳忘在外面了。
And it would have been a perfect waffle cake.
那就是完美的华夫饼了。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。是的。
Hi, Aidan.
嗨,艾丹。
Tell me about your waffle cake.
跟我说说你的华夫饼。
It's a vanilla cake with a cinnamon swirl.
这是香草蛋糕，上面有肉桂漩涡。
And I have a cream cheese frosting
还有奶油芝士糖霜
with a little bit of pecans and cinnamon crunch cereal.
再加上一点山核桃和肉桂脆脆麦片。
Now, what's going on in here?
现在，这里发生了什么?
That is a cinnamon crunch cereal ice cream.
那是一种肉桂脆脆麦片冰淇淋。
It's kind of like a bowl of cereal.
有点像一碗麦片粥。
I love it. I think it's a nice-looking cake.
我喜欢它。我认为这是一个漂亮的蛋糕。
It's a little bit messy.
这有点乱。
But it's a good messy. -Okay.
但这是一个很好的混乱。-好的。
I think you thought about how you were
我觉得你想过自己是怎样的人
gonna incorporate the cereal into your waffles.
把麦片混到你的华夫饼里。
It's absolutely beautiful. -I think we should taste it.
真是太美了。-我想我们应该尝尝。
Am I gonna bite into something delicious?
我要咬点好吃的吗?
Yes, you are.
是的，你是。
I just don't want to bite into one
我只是不想咬一口
of those cinnamon sticks.
那些肉桂棒。
Yeah. Oops.
是的。哦。
I wish that I could eat these waffle slices.
真希望我能吃这些华夫饼。
You guys are so lucky.
你们太幸运了。
You get to eat all of this stuff.
你可以把这些都吃了。
Thank you, Aidan.
谢谢你，艾登。
I'm excited about this ice cream.
我对这个冰淇淋很兴奋。
Mmm.
嗯。
Texture's amazing.
质地很神奇。
It tastes like I'm eating a heightened version
我吃起来就像吃了强化版的
of a bowl of cinnamon crunch cereal.
一碗脆脆的肉桂麦片。
Oh, man.
哦,男人。
Cinnamon waffles.
肉桂华夫饼干。
Dang.
见鬼。
That's awesome.
太棒了。
That cream cheese frosting is perfectly balanced,
奶油芝士糖霜非常均衡，
just sweet enough, taste the cream cheese.
足够甜，尝尝奶油奶酪。
All the flavors are going so perfectly together.
所有的味道都完美地融合在一起。
I would've just pulled back on the sugar a little bit.
我就会少放一点糖。
Okay.
好吧。
So I could have tasted the cream cheese more.
所以我可以多尝尝奶油奶酪。
Thank you, Aidan. -Thank you. Bye.
谢谢你，艾登。-谢谢。再见。
-Dang.
见鬼。见鬼。
Dang.
见鬼。
Breakfast desserts,
早餐的甜点,
we are brilliant for thinking this up, man.
我们能想出这个主意真是太棒了。
This is a good one. -Yep. My idea.
这个不错。是的。我的主意。
-Let's bring in Cole. -Yes.
-让科尔进来吧。-是的。
Hey, Cole.
嘿,科尔。
Tell me what kind of waffle cake you made.
告诉我你做了什么样的华夫饼。
It's a chocolate waffle.
这是巧克力华夫饼。
And then in each layer,
然后在每一层，
it's chocolate strawberry cream cheese buttercream
这是巧克力草莓奶油芝士奶油
and then a ring of hazelnut spread.
然后是一圈榛子酱。
And then there's strawberries, toasted hazelnuts,
还有草莓，烤榛子，
bacon and cinnamon crunch cereal.
培根和肉桂脆脆麦片。
Where's the kitchen sink?
厨房的水槽在哪里?
What?
怎么啦？
She's just pulling your leg.
她只是在跟你开玩笑。
Just teasing. Just teasing. It looks gorgeous.
只是取笑。只是取笑。看起来很漂亮。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Like, it looks professionally made.
比如，它看起来很专业。
I love the way that the chocolate's
我喜欢巧克力的样子
coming out between each layer.
从每层之间出来。
And I know Duff was hoping, "Please,
我知道达夫希望"求你了，
somebody make me some bacon today."
今天谁给我做点熏肉。”
Let's taste it.
让我们尝一尝。
Here. Valerie gets the pretty piece.
在这里。瓦莱丽得到了漂亮的那块。
-Oh. Thank you, Cole. -Looking good.
-哦。谢谢你，科尔。风格的好。
Oh, isn't that pretty?
哦，那不是很漂亮吗?
I'm loving the bacon in there.
我喜欢里面的培根。
It adds that saltiness, that smokiness in there.
它增加了咸味和烟熏味。
The cake is cooked perfectly.
蛋糕做得很好。
-Mm-hmm. -It's really yummy and moist.
-嗯。-真的很好吃又湿润。
And I didn't get much of the hazelnut.
我没吃到多少榛子。
Hazelnuts happen to be my favorite nut.
榛子是我最喜欢的坚果。
I do wish that you had cooked the bacon a little longer.
我真希望你把培根烤得再久一点。
Right? You want that bacon really crispy, right?
对吧?你想要培根非常酥脆，对吧?
But, you know, I think you got really,
但是，我觉得你真的，
really good flavors there.
味道真的很好。
You made a beautiful cake. -Thank you.
你做了一个漂亮的蛋糕。-谢谢。
-Hi, Reese. -Hi.
-你好,瑞茜。-你好。
I made a carrot cake pancake
我做了一个胡萝卜蛋糕煎饼
with a cream cheese frosting
加上奶油芝士糖霜
with my fruit cereal inside.
里面有我的水果麦片。
You got, like, frosting sticking out.
你把糖霜都露出来了。
And you got cereal coming out of there.
然后麦片就从那里出来了。
And there's chocolate all over.
到处都是巧克力。
I mean, it looks like it's gonna taste good.
我是说，看起来会很好吃。
But it just looks like you didn't put a lot of effort
但看起来你没怎么努力啊
into sort of putting it together.
把它们放在一起。
-Let's taste it. -Okay.
-让我们尝尝。-好的。
REESE: Duff, you shouldn't be able to eat this
里斯:达夫，你不应该吃这个
'cause you're the king of waffles.
因为你是华夫饼之王。
There you go. -Why don't I get any?
好了。-为什么我没有?
Go play with your waffle team.
去和你的华夫饼队玩吧。
It's a lot of nutmeg.
有很多肉豆蔻。
-Oh. -I do love nutmeg.
-哦。-我喜欢肉豆蔻。
But you just went over the edge, just a little bit.
但你只是有点过了底线而已。
I added more 'cause I wanted a good color.
我加了更多，因为我想要一个好的颜色。
Nutmeg is not a food coloring.
肉豆蔻不是食用色素。
Whoa.
哇。
And I tell you, this chocolate is doing you no favors.
我告诉你，这巧克力对你一点好处都没有。
It just doesn't belong.
它就是不属于这里。
But your cream cheese frosting's really good.
但你的奶油芝士糖霜真的很好吃。
Now I like the color
现在我喜欢这个颜色了
that the fruit cereal has added here.
水果麦片中添加的。
-Mm-hmm. -I don't taste it.
-嗯。-我没尝过。
I don't taste the flavor of the fruit cereal.
我尝不出水果麦片的味道。
I just get that extra little bit of crunch.
我只是得到了一点额外的嘎吱声。
That is really good cream cheese frosting.
奶油芝士糖霜真的很好吃。
-Okay. -Thank you, Reese.
-好的。-谢谢你，里斯。
-Thanks, Reese. -Thank you.
-谢谢,瑞茜。-谢谢。
Pancake queen actually gets me.
煎饼女王真的懂我。
-How's it going, Kaniyah? -Good.
-最近怎么样，Kaniyah?改善情况。
That is one beautiful pancake cake.
这是一个漂亮的煎饼蛋糕。
I made a rainbow lemon
我做了一个彩虹柠檬
and raspberry pancake cake with buttercream
还有奶油覆盆子煎饼蛋糕
and raspberry puree in the middle and fruit cereal.
中间是覆盆子泥和水果麦片。
You know what I love? It looks like Dr. Seuss made it.
你知道我喜欢什么吗?看起来像是苏斯博士做的。
-Yes. -Doesn't it?
-是的。没有改变吗?
Yes. My favorite author.
是的。我最喜欢的作家。
You know, really colorful,
你知道，非常丰富多彩，
really kind of wonky a little bit.
真的有点不稳定。
But meant to be that way.
但这是命中注定的。
Thank you. Yay.
谢谢你！耶。
-Kaniyah, you smiling? -Yeah.
-Kaniyah，你在笑吗?-是的。
You should be. This is really cool.
你应该这样。这真的很酷。
-It's really beautiful. -Really.
-真的很漂亮。-真的。
* And they liked all the colors *
他们喜欢所有的颜色
* They liked all the colors, they liked all the colors *
他们喜欢所有的颜色，他们喜欢所有的颜色
Proof is in the pudding.
事实就是这样。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
You like it?
你喜欢吗?
Duff, do you like it?
达夫，你喜欢吗?
I do.
我做的事。
I like it a lot.
我非常喜欢它。
-Yeah. -You know what I like?
-是的。你知道我喜欢什么吗?
Your buttercream is very buttery.
你的奶油很香。
So the butter on top of a pancake
所以煎饼上的黄油
really makes me think of breakfast, you know?
让我想起了早餐，你知道吗?
That's good.
这很好。
I think you got too much lemon in here.
我觉得你柠檬放多了。
I don't.
我不喜欢。
Not at all 'cause you got
一点也不，因为你
all that sweetness with the raspberry
覆盆子的甜味
in there and the tartness with the lemon,
还有柠檬的酸味，
all flavors that are going really well together.
所有的味道都很好地融合在一起。
-Thank you, Val. -Thank you.
-谢谢你，瓦尔-谢谢
KANIYAH: I'm feeling like I'm gonna be safe,
我觉得我很安全，
even though it was too much lemon.
虽然柠檬太多了。
But I'm gonna be safe.
但我会很安全的。
Jason!
杰森!
So for my pancake, I had just vanilla.
我的煎饼只放了香草。
And my buttercream,
还有我的奶油，
I have little pieces of rainbow cereal.
我有一小块彩虹麦片。
And I have a strawberry syrup.
我还有草莓糖浆。
I think your pancake cake looks festive.
我觉得你的煎饼看起来很有节日气氛。
It looks incredibly happy.
它看起来非常快乐。
The joy that you had in making that
你做那件事的快乐
is very evident.
是非常明显的。
You had a really good time today, didn't you?
你今天过得很开心，是吗?
-Yeah. -I mean, look at that face.
-是的。-我是说，看看那张脸。
Why don't you cut into it and give us a slice?
你为什么不把它切开，给我们一片呢?
Please like it.
请喜欢它。请喜欢它。
This looks so ridiculous.
这看起来太可笑了。
-Thank you, Jason. -You're welcome.
-谢谢你，杰森。你是受欢迎的。
Enjoy your, uh, 2,000 calories.
好好享受你的2000卡路里吧。
Jason, the -- the frosting is too sweet.
杰森，这糖霜太甜了。
I'm actually grateful that there's not too much of it
事实上，我很感激它没有太多
'cause it's just too sweet.
因为这太甜蜜了。
It's good. It's, like, a really good vanilla cake.
很好。这是一个非常棒的香草蛋糕。
Okay.
好吧。
I'm just -- I'm not blown over by it.
我只是，我没有被它吓倒。
I feel you.
我理解你。我理解你。
I think it's delicious.
我觉得很好吃。
But it's vanilla.
但这是香草味的。
And your cake is dry.
你的蛋糕是干的。
I feel like your pancake cake
我感觉像你的煎饼蛋糕
has your spirit on the outside.
你的灵魂在外面。
I just don't feel like you gave it your spirit on the inside.
我只是觉得你并没有把你的灵魂放在里面。
Darn it.
真讨厌。
-That's what it's missing. -Yeah.
-这就是它所缺少的。-是的。
Thank you, queen of pancakes.
谢谢你，煎饼女王。
And goodbye, king of waffles.
再见了，华夫饼之王。
He's funny, man.
他很有趣，伙计。
I love him.
我爱他。
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package
会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包吗
that includes a future story in "Food Network Magazine"...
包括《美食网络杂志》的未来故事…
Hallelujah!
阿利路亚!
-And... -$25,000.
——……——25000美元。
Winner is coming.
赢家来了。
Okay.
好吧。
It's waffles versus pancakes, stacked cakes.
这是华夫饼对薄煎饼，叠蛋糕。
Let's go favorite.
我们去最爱吧。
Kaniyah. That was so pretty,
Kaniyah。太漂亮了，
that cake, all the colors.
那个蛋糕，所有的颜色。
She used the fruit cereal perfectly.
她把水果麦片吃得很好。
It had a little too much lemon in it, though.
不过柠檬味有点多。
No, no, no, no. I beg to disagree.
不，不，不。我不敢苟同。
I got to bring up Aidan.
我得说说艾登
That was really tasty.
那真的很好吃。
-Right? I mean, come on. -Yeah.
-对吗?我是说，拜托。-是的。
But I know you weren't really fond of using
但我知道你不太喜欢用
the cinnamon sticks as a garnish.
肉桂棒作为装饰。
Yeah.
是的。
The waffle cake that Justice made us
贾斯蒂斯给我们做的华夫饼
with the orange was amazing.
这个橙子太棒了。
But I was a little disappointed in the orange curd.
但我对橘子凝乳有点失望。
Audra.
Audra。
Now Audra had some problems.
现在，奥德拉遇到了一些问题。
It was a mess, but it tasted good.
它是一团乱，但味道很好。
It did taste good.
味道确实不错。
Let's talk about Reese and his nutmeg.
我们来谈谈里斯和他的肉豆蔻。
Way too much nutmeg.
肉豆蔻太多了。
I think there's a hole.
我觉得有个洞。
I think I can still taste it on my tongue.
我觉得我的舌头上还能闻到。
Reese also gave us chocolate on top of a carrot cake.
里斯还给了我们一块胡萝卜蛋糕上的巧克力。
He really gave us a good cream cheese frosting, though.
不过他给我们的奶油芝士糖霜真的很好吃。
Ahh!
啊!
Once we figure out which side won this,
一旦我们弄清楚哪一方赢了，
we have to figure out who we're sending home
我们得想好要送谁回家
from the losing side.
输的一方。
Oh.
哦。
You ready to make your decision, Valerie?
准备好做决定了吗，瓦莱丽?
No! I'm not ready to make my decision!
不!我还没准备好做决定!
Well, I am. Hurry up, lady!
嗯，我是。快点，女士!
Oh!
哦!
The waffle side should definitely win
华夫饼一方肯定会赢
because the boys rocked it.
因为男孩们太棒了。
Bakers, only one side
面包师，只有一面
of the great breakfast dessert divide,
伟大的早餐甜点划分，
waffles or pancakes...
华夫饼或煎饼……
-Pancakes! -Waffles!
煎饼!华夫饼!
...will be safe from elimination today.
…今天将不会被淘汰。
Uh-oh.
哦。
And the winning side is...
获胜的一方是……
* Waffles *
*华夫饼*
AUDRA: I don't know if my teammates can save me.
我不知道我的队友能不能救我。
My heart is pounding.
我的心怦怦直跳。
DUFF: ...waffles.
达夫:……华夫饼干。
[ Cheering ]
[欢呼]
You have to get a tattoo tonight.
你今晚得去纹身。
Me and my big mouth.
我和我的大嘴巴。
Very nice job, waffle side.
干得好，华夫饼面。
So the four of you are safe from elimination.
所以你们四个不会被淘汰。
Yay!
耶!
Yay! I'm so happy! Safe for another week.
耶!我太高兴了!再安全一周。
I hereby declare the best waffle cake baker
我在此宣布最佳华夫饼烘焙师
in all the land is...
在所有的土地上……
...Aidan.
艾丹。
Yes!
是的!
-Good job, Aidan! -Good job, Aidan.
-干得好，艾登!-干得好，艾登。
-Good job. -Another cat fist bump.
改善工作。-又是猫拳。
-Meow! -Meow.
猫叫!猫叫。
I can't believe I won. I was in the bottom last week.
我不敢相信我赢了。我上周排名垫底。
And I won the waffle challenge. * Da -- *
我赢了华夫饼挑战。* Da——*
WOMAN: Aw!
女人:哦!
All righty.
好了。
Now, oh, that leaves the pancake side.
现在，哦，只剩下煎饼那一面了。
Now, Duff and I did agree that there was one baker
达夫和我都认为有一个面包师
whose stacked cake was good enough
谁的蛋糕够好吃
to keep them in the competition.
让他们继续竞争。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Kaniyah.
……Kaniyah。
-Yes! -Oh, my God.
-是的!-我的天啊。
-Oh, yes. -Good job, Kaniyah.
-哦,是的。-干得好，Kaniyah。
Respect for the little ladies
尊重小女士们
'cause there are no girls left.
因为已经没有女孩了。
Unfortunately, that means,
不幸的是，这意味着，
Jason and Reese, you're in the bottom.
杰森和里斯，你们在底部。
Please come forward.
请站出来。
Man, seriously?
人,严重吗?
Reese, you used way too much nutmeg
里斯，你用了太多肉豆蔻
in your carrot cake creation.
在你的胡萝卜蛋糕创作中。
Your stacked cake was a little messy.
你的蛋糕堆得有点乱。
And the addition of chocolate was an odd choice.
加上巧克力是一个奇怪的选择。
Jason, the pancakes in your enormous
杰森，煎饼在你的大
vanilla stacked cake were dry.
香草堆叠蛋糕是干的。
And the frosting was way too sweet.
而且糖霜也太甜了。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
But the baker that will be going home is...
但是要回家的面包师是……
JASON: Please don't pick me. Please don't pick me.
杰森:请不要选我。请不要选我。
...Reese.
瑞茜。
Sorry, man. -We're so sorry, Reese.
对不起,男人。-我们很抱歉，里斯。
You have a smile that lights up the whole room.
你的微笑照亮了整个房间。
And we're really gonna miss you.
我们会很想你的。
You can say your goodbyes.
你可以说再见了。
REESE: Even though I'm going home,
里斯:虽然我要回家了，
this is one of the best things
这是最好的事情之一
that happened to me in my whole entire life.
这种事在我这辈子都发生过。
AUDRA: I'll miss you, Reese.
我会想你的，里斯。
I think my whole family's gonna be really proud of me
我想我全家都会为我感到骄傲的
in how long I've stayed here.
我在这里待了多久
Don't forget your tattoo!
别忘了你的纹身!
Believe me, I will not forget my tattoo.
相信我，我不会忘记我的纹身的。
VALERIE: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
瓦莱丽:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
I challenge you to a breakfast cake-off,
我向你挑战吃早餐蛋糕，
waffles versus pancakes.
华夫饼vs煎饼。
Gosh, my pancakes are not flipping.
天啊，我的煎饼不动了。
You should get a waffle tattoo.
你应该纹个华夫饼纹身。
Team Waffles, if you guys bring home the gold,
华夫饼队，如果你们拿了金牌，
I will get a waffle tattoo.
我要纹个华夫饼纹身。
Dang.
见鬼。
That's awesome.
太棒了。
Waffles.
华夫饼。
-Yay! -Aidan.
耶!艾丹。
Yes. I did it.
是的。我做到了。
The baker that will be going home is Reese.
要回家的面包师是里斯。
-Aw. -Sorry, man.
哦。对不起,男人。
[ Cellphones ringing ]
[手机铃声]
-What is this? -Ooh.
-这是什么?-哦。
-Oh, boy. -What is this?
-哦,男孩。-这是什么?
-Oh, my gosh. -It's a phone.
-哦，我的天哪。-这是电话。
JASON: It's a bunch of baking apps.
杰森:是一堆烘焙软件。
"Pastry Chef Go."
“糕点师加油。”
-"Fruitcake Ninja." -"Snackchat."
——“水果蛋糕忍者。”——“Snackchat”。
-"Sugar Scoop." -Ooh, "Pieterest."
——“糖勺。”-哦,“老”。
"Spot-A-Fry." That's hilarious.
“Spot-A-Fry。”这是搞笑的。
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事?
Shh. Here they come.
嘘。他们来了。
-Welcome back. -Hi.
欢迎回来。-你好。
Hello, bakers.
你好,面包师。
-Hello. -Where's your tattoo?
-你好。-你的纹身呢?
-Did you get a tattoo? -Did you get the tattoo?
-你有纹身吗?-你纹了吗?
My guy was booked up, so I haven't gotten it yet.
我的人预约满了，所以我还没拿到。
-Aw. -I will. Don't worry.
哦。我将。别担心。
Duff, I'll believe it when I see it.
达夫，我亲眼所见才会相信。
Whew. We started out with 12 bakers.
唷。一开始我们有12个面包师。
And now we're down to six of you.
现在只剩六个人了。
Pretty exciting, right?
很令人兴奋，对吧?
The boys are killing this thing.
男孩们杀了这东西。
There's only two girls left.
只剩下两个女孩了。
I have a feeling that the boys are gonna win it this year.
我有一种感觉，男生们今年会赢。
You guys represent the next generation of bakers.
你们代表了新一代的面包师。
You have impressive baking skills.
你的烘焙技术令人印象深刻。
And you keep up with the latest baking trends on TV,
你还能跟上电视上最新的烘焙潮流，
the Internet and mobile apps.
互联网和移动应用。
I love virtual baking.
我喜欢虚拟烘焙。
For this big bake,
为了这个大蛋糕，
we have filled this cellphone
我们的手机已经满了
with imaginary food apps.
用想象中的食物应用程序。
You will have 90 minutes to bake
你有90分钟的时间来烤
and decorate one dozen sugar cookies...
然后装饰一打糖饼干……
-Yes!
-是的!-是的!
...with the perfect icon for three of these apps.
…有三个应用程序的完美图标。
-Sugar cookies.
四种不同食物的饼干。四种不同食物的饼干。
It's all about the decorating today.
今天的重点是装饰。
And how tasty is that sugar cookie?
那块甜饼有多好吃?
During tasting, we want you to come up
在品尝过程中，我们希望你上来
with a fun explanation
一个有趣的解释
of what each make-believe app does.
每个虚拟应用程序的功能。
-Uh-oh. -Gosh, this is gonna be hard.
啊哦。-天哪，这太难了。
All right, bakers.
好了，面包师们。
90 minutes, one dozen sugar cookies,
90分钟，一打甜饼，
three different app designs.
三种不同的应用设计。
And your baking time starts...
你的烘焙时间开始了…
now. -Now!
现在。-现在!
Oh, go slow.
哦，慢慢来。
Go slow, slow, slow.
慢点，慢点，慢点。
COLE: I reach for Snackchat.
科尔:我伸手去拿零食。
And Kaniyah was like... -Give me that.
Kaniyah说……-给我。
...wa-pow.
……wa-pow。
Rips my arm away, and then she grabs it.
扯掉我的胳膊，然后她抓住了。
She's strong.
她很坚强。
Yes! Ha ha!
是的!哈哈!
I mean, her mom's a cop.
我是说，她妈妈是个警察
-Look at this guy. -Waiting.
-看这家伙。等着。
-Oh. -I just like to wait.
-哦。-我只是喜欢等。
Everyone else is like, "Oh, my God.
其他人都会说，“哦，我的天哪。
It's the end of the world. I need my apps."
这是世界末日。我需要我的应用。”
And I'm just like,
我就说，
"Just getting my apps without dying."
“只是在不死机的情况下获取应用程序。”
-Ah! -Oh, yes.
——啊!-哦,是的。
I got Dessert Craft.
我选了甜点工艺。
I got Pastry Chef Go, Clash of Carbs.
我要上甜点大厨课，碳水化合物冲突。
Yes. Let's think.
是的。让我们思考。
For Clash of Carbs, I'm going to make it
对于碳水化合物的冲突，我会做到的
so it's kind of like a food fight-ish game.
所以这有点像食物大战游戏。
I play game apps on my tablet all the time.
我一直在平板电脑上玩游戏应用程序。
So coming up with stories should be awesome.
所以编故事应该很棒。
Perfect. Okay.
完美的。好吧。
I'm making a lemon sugar cookie
我在做柠檬糖饼干
because last time I made a lemon flavor...
因为上次我做了柠檬味的…
Whoo.
喔!
...I kind of totally bombed.
…我完全搞砸了。
That's really sweet.
你真贴心。
So I had to make up for that lemon.
所以我得弥补那个柠檬。
Let's cream some stuff.
我们来涂点奶油吧。
First, I combine my butter, sugar and eggs.
首先，我把黄油、糖和鸡蛋混合。
And then I put in my dry ingredients --
然后我把干的配料放进去
some baking powder, salt and flour
一些发酵粉，盐和面粉
and then add some lemon extract.
然后加入一些柠檬汁。
Hope that's lemony enough.
希望柠檬味够了。
Remember, like, this is about how big phones were
记住，这是关于手机有多大的
back in the day.
在过去。
Like, what? What? I can't hear you. Hold on.
像什么?怎么啦？我听不见你说什么。等一等。
Click, click, click. -They get really big.
咔哒，咔哒，咔哒。-它们变得很大。
And then they get really small. And then they're big again.
然后它们变得非常小。然后又变大了。
Now they're big again. Yeah.
现在他们又变大了。是的。
Oh, that smells good.
闻起来真香。
I form that into a ball... Perfect.
我把它揉成一个球…完美的。
...and put it in the blast chiller
…然后把它放进冷冻机
to kind of harden up a little bit.
让它变硬一点。
If you don't chill your dough,
如果你不冷藏面团
then it's gonna be mushy and sticky
然后就会变得粘稠
and very hard to work with.
而且很难合作。
Voilà. Done.
瞧。完成了。
Hey, we need to come up with a twist for these guys.
嘿，我们得想个办法对付这些家伙。
Oh, don't worry. There's an app for that.
哦，别担心。有一个应用程序可以做到这一点。
Oh, yeah?
噢,是吗?
-Done. -Huh.
完成。嗯。
I got Graham Hacker, Parmville and Eclairiscope.
我有Graham Hacker, Parmville和Eclairiscope。
For my cookies, I'm going to use rose water
我要用玫瑰水来做饼干
because rose is a nice and, like, elegant flavor
因为玫瑰的味道很好，很优雅
to go in my elegant sugar cookies.
放进我优雅的糖饼干里。
First, I add some butter and some sugar and eggs.
首先，我加了一些黄油，一些糖和鸡蛋。
And I cream that up in a mixing bowl.
然后在搅拌碗里搅匀。
And then I add my rose-water extract.
然后加入玫瑰水提取物。
As I add my dry ingredients,
当我加入干料的时候，
I start mixing it by hand,
我开始用手搅拌，
so that it's not overmixed
这样就不会过度混合
'cause I have more control over what I'm mixing with.
因为我能更好地控制混和的东西
Ooh.
哦。
Hey, Valerie. Did you order something
嘿,瓦莱丽。你点了什么吗?
from twistazon.com?
从twistazon.com ?
-I did. -Huh.
我所做的。嗯。
Attention, bakers.
注意,面包师。
Your twist just arrived.
你的转折刚到。
-Oh, my God. -Already?
-我的天啊。造成?
Oh, my gosh. It's citrus.
哦，我的天啊。这是柑橘类。
You must incorporate the flavor
你必须把味道混合起来
of one of these citrus fruits...
这些柑橘类水果中的一种
Ooh.
哦。
...orange, lemon or lime into your app cookies.
…将橙子、柠檬或酸橙放入应用程序cookie中。
I already have rose water in there.
我已经在里面放了玫瑰水。
Ugh.
啊。
There's plenty for everyone.
每个人都有很多。
-There's plenty.
——很多。——很多。
AUDRA: I was already making lemon.
我已经在做柠檬了。
I was already making it, duh.
我已经在做了，废话。
-Well, duh. -Orange.
-嗯,咄。橙色。
This is not my station.
这不是我的位置。
We can make it harder for you if you want.
如果你愿意，我们可以让你更困难。
No, thank you.
不，谢谢。
Mm, I could really go for a nice cup
我真想喝杯好酒
of fresh-squeezed orange juice right now.
鲜榨橙汁。
For my app cookies...
对于我的应用程序cookie…
Sugar.
糖。
...I got Hangry Nerds, Sugar Scoop and Tummy Rumble.
…我有饿怒书呆子，糖勺和肚子隆隆。
I'm making a vanilla-orange sugar cookie.
我在做香草橙糖饼干。
I juiced the orange and poured that into my batter.
我把桔子榨汁倒进面糊里。
And I think that'll do the trick.
我想这样就行了。
Smells like oranges.
闻起来像橘子。
What else did we have that is out now,
还有什么是我们现在知道的，
and they don't know of?
他们不知道吗?
They'd have to go see it in a museum.
他们得去博物馆看。
You know what, Val?
你知道吗，瓦尔?
I'm gonna go make you a mixtape.
我去给你做个混音带。
I know. That used to be, like,
我知道。以前是这样的，
the ultimate in a romantic gesture...
浪漫的终极姿态……
-Oh, man. -...getting a mixtape.
-哦,男人。-…拿一张混音带。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦，是的，是的。
-Hi, Cole. -Hi.
-你好,科尔。-你好。
-How's it going? -Good.
-最近怎么样?改善情况。
Yeah? You got a smile on your face.
是吗?你脸上挂着微笑。
So tell me what apps you picked.
告诉我你选了什么应用。
I got Spot-A-Fry,
我得到了Spot-A-Fry，
Noodle Maps and Cakemaker 1000.
面条地图和蛋糕机1000。
Oh, that sounds like an app you could come up with.
哦，这听起来像是一个你可以想出的应用程序。
-Yes. -Have you come up
-是的。-你上来了吗
with a story for each of your app,
每个应用都有一个故事，
like, why you invented them?
比如，你为什么要发明它们?
-Um, no, not yet. Nope. -Not yet?
-不，还没有。不。——不是吗?
You picked lemons for your twist?
你挑柠檬来扭?
Yes.
是的。
Cool. Sounds to me like the only thing
酷。我觉得这是唯一的办法
you have to work on is your stories.
你必须努力的是你的故事。
-Yes. -You got it.
-是的。-你说对了。
Have fun. -Thank you.
玩得开心。-谢谢。
I know that Valerie loves lemon.
我知道瓦莱丽喜欢柠檬。
So why not impress her
那为什么不打动她呢
and make her happy so that I win?
让她开心，这样我就赢了
So I'm gonna use lemon zest and lemon juice.
我要用柠檬皮和柠檬汁。
This lemon is really, really juicy.
这个柠檬真的非常多汁。
So I add a little extra flour.
所以我多加了一点面粉。
There we go.
好了。
And it's perfect.
这是完美的。
You know when you have perfect sugar-cookie dough,
当你有了完美的糖曲奇面团，
you can touch it.
你可以触摸它。
And it won't stick to your hands.
而且不会粘在手上。
Hour and 15 minutes left, bakers.
还有1小时15分钟，面包师们。
What? It's already been 15 minutes?
怎么啦？已经15分钟了?
COLE: Go, bakers, go.
科尔:走吧，面包师们，走吧。
I got Pieterest, Cheesecake Chess
我有Pieterest, Cheesecake Chess
and Fruitcake Ninja.
还有水果蛋糕忍者。
Still stumped on what my flavoring's gonna be.
我还不知道该放什么调味料。
I don't bake sugar cookies that often.
我不常烤甜饼干。
But during the holidays,
但在假期里，
they're one of my favorite treats of all time,
它们一直是我最喜欢的食物之一，
especially the super chewy ones.
尤其是超级耐嚼的那种。
Why don't I make an orange sugar cookie?
为什么我不做一个橙糖饼干呢?
You're making orange sugar cookies?
你在做橘子糖饼干?
-Yeah. -That's what I'm doing.
-是的。-这就是我在做的。
And the icons that I have are Snackchat,
我用的图标是零食聊天，
Buttercream Bingo and Crumbtown.
奶油宾果和面包屑镇。
-Hi, Kaniyah. -Hello.
-你好,Kaniyah。-你好。
What you making?
你在做什么?
I am making a orange sugar cookie.
我正在做一个橙糖饼干。
Or what are you making besides a mess?
或者你除了搞得一团糟还搞什么?
What is going on back here?
这里到底发生了什么?
I have no clue.
我不知道。
I'm the Cookie Monster.
我是饼干怪兽。
Okay. So you're making an orange sugar cookie.
好吧。所以你在做一个橙糖饼干。
-Yeah. -Cool, man.
-是的。酷,伙计。
Jason, do you have the orange extract?
杰森，你有橙汁吗?
Uh, yeah, right there. You can have it.
嗯，是的，就在那儿。你可以拥有它。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
JUSTICE: Forget rose. Now I'm doing orange
JUSTICE:忘了rose吧。现在我用橙色
because I want it to taste
因为我想让它有味道
like the oranges off of my orange tree.
比如从我的橘子树上摘下来的橙子。
I don't want to have a lot of water in my dough.
我不想面团里有太多的水。
So I just put a dash of juice in there.
所以我放了一点果汁进去。
But mostly, I'll put orange extract.
但主要还是放橙汁。
And then I make an orange buttercream
然后我做了一个橙色奶油蛋糕
so that it'll mask the rose flavor
这样就能掩盖玫瑰的味道
and let the orange shine.
让橙色闪耀。
How's your cookies going, Justice?
你的饼干怎么样了，法官?
-Good. How 'bout you? -Pretty good.
改善情况。你呢?-相当好。
Are yours already in the oven?
你的已经在烤箱里了吗?
Nope. Are yours?
不。是你的吗?
Uh, I'm going to put them in the oven very shortly.
我马上把它们放进烤箱。
Did you put 'em in the blast chiller
你把它们放进冷冻机了吗
to cool off?
为了降温?
Before you put them in the oven,
在把它们放进烤箱之前，
you have to put them in the blast chiller.
你得把它们放进冷风机里。
I don't think so.
我不这么想。
Okay.
好吧。
I've never done it that way before.
我从来没这么做过。
JASON: Oh, boy. No.
杰森:哦，天哪。不。
This doesn't feel right.
这感觉不对。
Ah.
啊。
Check out Jason.
看看杰森。
He is struggling to get those cookies
他正在努力去拿那些饼干
off his cutting board.
从砧板上拿下来。
They're mis-shapened apps.
它们是畸形的应用程序。
I mean, he could scrape all those cookies off,
我是说，他可以把饼干刮下来，
reform the dough and reroll it.
把面团揉匀，再擀一卷。
But then they're gonna start getting really tough.
但接下来他们会变得非常强硬。
It'll be okay. It'll be fine.
会没事的。会没事的。
I made a few extra cookies.
我多做了一些饼干。
If I have a few duds,
如果我有几个哑弹，
I'll have spare cookies just in case.
我准备了多余的饼干以防万一。
I start my cookies in the oven.
我开始在烤箱里烤饼干。
Wait, who else is making orange?
等等，还有谁在做橙汁?
Jason is also making orange.
杰森也在做橙汁。
Okay. I'm not doing orange.
好吧。我不是用橙色。
Limes it is.
是酸橙。
I want to be different with my sugar cookies.
我想让我的糖饼干与众不同。
And no one else picked lime.
没有人选酸橙。
I'm just gonna add zest and juice.
我要加些香料和果汁。
And I think that'll really pop.
我想这会很流行的。
Not enough. I taste my dough.
不够的。我品尝我的面团。
And there's no lime flavor.
而且没有酸橙味。
So I need to add more juice.
所以我需要加更多的果汁。
I, like, don't taste any lime.
我尝不出酸橙的味道。
Okay. According to my cookie timer,
好吧。根据我的饼干计时器，
you have 1 hour left, bakers.
面包师们，你们还有1个小时。
-Oh, boy. -Oh, my gosh.
-哦,男孩。-哦，我的天哪。
People are already rolling out their dough.
人们已经开始花钱了。
I'm adding a final dash of lime.
最后加一点青柠。
Oh, gosh.
哦,天哪。
Oh, that's really, really kind of wet.
哦，真的，真的有点湿。
If my dough's too wet, it probably won't bake properly.
如果我的面团太湿，可能就烤不好了。
It'll probably look weird.
它可能看起来很奇怪。
Oh, my gosh. This is a disaster.
哦，我的天啊。这是一场灾难。
I don't have enough time to start all over.
我没有足够的时间重新开始。
You have 1 hour left, bakers.
面包师们，你们还有1个小时。
-Oh, boy. -For real?
-哦,男孩。——真的吗?
Oh, my gosh. This is a disaster.
哦，我的天啊。这是一场灾难。
We are expecting amazing mobile app cookies.
我们期待着惊人的移动应用cookie。
Ooh, that's really, really kind of wet.
哦，真的，真的有点湿。
The twist is we have to incorporate a citrus flavor.
关键是我们要加入柑橘的味道。
And I've splashed in maybe about 1/2 cup,
我倒了大概1/2杯，
at this point, of lime juice.
现在，是酸橙汁。
Gosh. What am I gonna do?
天啊。我该怎么办?
Hey, remember what happens when you add
嘿，记住当你加的时候会发生什么
too much liquid to something,
太多的液体，
and you throw off the ratio.
你忽略了这个比率。
Baking is science.
烘焙是一门科学。
Oh. [ Gasps ] Wait a second.
哦。[喘息]等一下。
Okay.
好吧。
Just come together.
大家一起来。
Please. Please. Please, work.
请。请。请工作。
So I add a little extra flour
所以我多加了一点面粉
to help balance out all that juice.
来平衡所有的果汁。
You know what? The flour's gonna help it.
你知道吗?面粉会有帮助。
Finally, it looks okay enough.
最后，看起来足够好了。
And I need to get this rolled out fast.
我得尽快把这事办好。
I've had better days.
我也有过好日子。
What am I doing?
我在做什么?
-Rotary phone. -Right.
旋转手机。-对。
They don't know what a rotary phone is.
他们不知道转盘电话是什么。
Oh, yeah. They see one of these,
哦,是的。他们看到其中一个，
they're like, "Uh, I don't..." -What do you do with that?
他们会说，“呃，我不……”-你用它做什么?
You always hated when your numbers were,
你总是讨厌你的数字，
like, nines or zeroes in it
比如9或0
because it took longer.
因为花的时间更长。
Come on.
来吧。
-How are you doing, Kaniyah? -Good.
-你好吗，Kaniyah?改善情况。
It's time to roll out my sugar-cookie dough.
是时候把我的糖曲奇面团擀开了。
Okay. Just...
好吧。只是…
As I'm rolling, I look down and...
当我滚动时，我向下看…
Oh, snap. I have me an orange.
哦,提前。我有一个橘子。
Oops. No.
哦。不。
I didn't add my orange.
我没有加橘子。
I cannot believe I forgot the orange.
真不敢相信我忘了拿橘子。
Oopsies. So I'm squeezing orange juice into the batter.
Oopsies。我把橙汁挤进面糊里。
So then I have to put more flour up there.
然后我要在上面放更多的面粉。
And I roll it out again.
我再把它擀开。
Bro.
兄弟。
Kaniyah just keeps rolling out her dough
Kaniyah一直在揉面团
and rolling out her dough.
揉着她的面团。
The thing about, like, a sugar-cookie dough,
比如，一个糖曲奇面团，
you need to have a light touch with it.
你需要轻轻触碰它。
So it comes out really tender.
所以出来的时候非常嫩。
Yeah. You want a light, crispy sugar cookie.
是的。你想要一个轻脆的糖饼干。
Now, 40 decorations.
现在，有40个装饰品。
All right, bakers. It sounded pretty easy
好了，面包师们。听起来很简单
when we first told you this challenge.
当我们第一次告诉你这个挑战的时候。
-No, it didn't. -How's it going now?
-不，没有。-现在怎么样了?
Still good. No pressure.
还好。没有压力。
I like your attitude, Kaniyah.
我喜欢你的态度，卡尼亚。
You really have to app-ply yourself
你真的需要自己努力
if you want to impress us.
如果你想给我们留下好印象。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝。
Is there an app for going back in time,
有没有一款应用可以让你回到过去，
so I didn't hear that horrible joke?
所以我没听到那个可怕的笑话?
Let's come up with one.
让我们想出一个。
COLE: One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
科尔:1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8。
When sugar cookies are in the oven,
当糖饼干在烤箱里的时候，
tend to spread.
倾向于扩散。
A perfectionist cannot have that.
完美主义者不能拥有这些。
So I'm only doing six on each sheet,
每张纸我只做了六个，
so that they're not even close to touching.
这样它们就不会碰在一起了。
What you making over there?
你在那边做什么?
Lemon rose-water glaze.
柠檬玫瑰水釉。
-That sounds delicious. -I hope.
-听起来很好吃。我希望。
I'm gonna make my glaze by combining powdered sugar,
我要把糖粉混合在一起，
milk and lemon zest.
牛奶和柠檬皮。
I want to use rose water
我想用玫瑰水
because I want to wow the judges with unique flavors.
因为我想用独特的口味让评委们惊叹。
Is that rose water at Cole's station?
科尔站的是玫瑰水吗?
It's a tricky little ingredient to get right.
这是一种很棘手的配料。
-Yes, it is. -Too much is too much.
-是的。-太多就是太多。
It's like drinking perfume.
就像喝香水一样。
Hmm.
嗯。
JUSTICE: While my cookies are in the oven,
法官:当我的饼干在烤箱里的时候，
I really need to start on my fondantwork for the apps.
我真的需要开始为应用程序做准备了。
If you're using fondant,
如果你用软糖，
you really always want to make it really thin
你总是想把它做得很薄
'cause fondant's not the best-tasting thing.
因为软糖不是最好吃的东西。
It's more of a decoration not a flavor.
它更像是一种装饰，而不是一种风味。
Okay. Perfect.
好吧。完美的。
I finally get my dough rolled out.
我的钱终于滚出来了。
But when I cut them, some were really thin
但当我切开它们时，有些真的很薄
and then some are really thick.
还有一些非常厚。
Oh, that's way too thick.
哦，太厚了。
And a little messier than I would like.
而且比我想的还要乱。
Ugh. That one's just a fail.
啊。那只是一个失败。
Audra's been working on her dough for a long time.
奥德拉做面团已经很久了。
She has got to get that in the oven.
她得把它放进烤箱。
I really wanted to give a pop to my sugar cookies.
我真的很想给我的糖饼干来个爆破声。
So I'm adding extra salt.
所以我加了额外的盐。
And I just hope it's not too salty.
我只希望不要太咸。
45 minutes left, bakers.
还有45分钟，面包师们。
-Ah. -A lot of armwork, Mommy.
——啊。-好多装饰啊，妈妈。
Make a cookie that will whet our app-etites.
做一块能刺激我们食欲的饼干。
Again, with the puns.
还是用双关语。
-Don't stop the puns ever. -Oh, I didn't hear it.
-永远不要停止双关语。-哦，我没听到。
-Keep 'em coming. -Tell me the pun.
-让他们继续。-告诉我那个双关语。
Puns are a sign of genius, Jason.
双关语是天才的标志，杰森。
-Oh, my... -Oh, boy.
-哦,我的…-哦,男孩。
I smell something burning.
我闻到有东西烧焦了。
-Oh, no. Wait. -I do too.
-哦,不。等待。-我也是。
I just put mine in.
我刚把我的放进去。
Where's my...timer anyways?
我的……定时器不管怎样?
Oh. I was so busy on this glaze,
哦。我忙着做釉料，
I forgot about my cookies.
我忘了我的饼干。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
No. Please, no burned cookies.
不。请不要烤焦了的饼干。
-You burnt your cookies? -This is terrible.
-你的饼干烧焦了?-这太可怕了。
Some of them. This is an absolute disaster.
其中一些。这绝对是一场灾难。
JASON: No, please, no burned cookies.
杰森:不，请不要烤焦了的饼干。
You burnt your cookies?
你把饼干烤焦了?
JASON: Some of them.
杰森:有一些。
Okay, good, they're soft.
很好，它们很软。
30 minutes left, bakers.
还有30分钟，面包师们。
Got to go. Got to go. Got to go. Got to go. Got to go.
我得走了。我得走了。我得走了。我得走了。我得走了。
A dozen sugar cookies with
一打糖饼干
three different app designs with a citrus twist.
三种不同的应用程序设计与柑橘的扭曲。
Smells like lime.
闻起来像酸橙。
-This is so hard. -They're soft still.
-这太难了。-还是很软。
They're not, like, completely burned.
它们并没有完全烧焦。
Thankfully, my cookies are nice and soft.
谢天谢地，我的饼干又软又好吃。
So I throw 'em in the blast chiller,
所以我把它们扔进冷冻机
so they don't cook anymore.
所以他们不再做饭了。
Now I have to figure out what I'm gonna do
现在我得想想我该怎么做
with my app designs.
我的应用程序设计。
Angry Nerds...
愤怒的书呆子…
Rumble...
隆隆作响……
Sugar Scoop...
糖勺……
I knew it was gonna be hard.
我就知道会很难。
But I didn't think it would be this hard.
但我没想到会这么难。
What am I even doing?
我到底在做什么?
JUSTICE: It's time to decorate.
JUSTICE:该装修了。
Each app has its own different job.
每个应用程序都有自己不同的工作。
And for each one, it's gonna have its own unique design.
每一个都有自己独特的设计。
For Graham Hacker, I cut rectangles.
为Graham Hacker，我切割矩形。
So it looks like a graham cracker.
所以它看起来像全麦饼干。
And I put little dots in it.
我在上面画了些小点。
I get the edible marker.
我得到了可食用的马克笔。
And I draw on his sunglasses like evil graham cracker.
我把他的墨镜画得像个邪恶的全麦饼干。
Wa-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wa-ha-ha-ha-ha。
Eclairiscope is a gossip news app for eclairs.
Eclairiscope是泡芙饼干的八卦新闻应用。
I think I'll just do a eclair with a paper
我想我还是用纸做个泡芙吧
running down it, kind of like the eclair is a scroll.
顺着它走，有点像泡芙是一个卷轴。
And I'm doing a cheese house for Parmville.
我要为帕姆维尔做一个奶酪屋。
Decorate this cookie.
装饰这个饼干。
For my decorations,
为了我的装饰，
I'm going to use fondant on fondant and on fondant.
我要用软糖，软糖，软糖。
Doesn't taste good, but it looks pretty.
味道不太好，但看起来很漂亮。
I got this.
我来吧。
I'm gonna decorate Snackchat by spray-painting it yellow
我要把零食网喷成黄色
and putting a fondant cookie on top.
再在上面放一块软糖饼干。
Yes. Now Buttercream Bingo.
是的。现在是奶油宾果。
For the Buttercream Bingo, I'm gonna use white fondant.
做奶油宾果，我要用白色的方糖。
And I'll draw on it with edible markers
我会用可食用的马克笔在上面画
to make it look like a bingo board.
让它看起来像宾果游戏板。
Bingo, bingo, bingo.
宾果，宾果，宾果。
Crumbtown, I'm gonna spray-paint it blue
crumtown，我要把它喷成蓝色
and crush up cookies and put 'em on top.
把饼干压碎，放在上面。
Hallelujah.
哈利路亚。
24 minutes left.
还剩24分钟。
For real?
真的吗?
COLE: I have to make a Spot-a-Fry app,
科尔:我得做个快餐应用，
a Noodle Maps app and a Cakemaker 1000 app.
一个Noodle Maps应用和一个cakeemaker 1000应用。
That -- that's a lot.
那是很多。
I'm dipping each cookie in a lemon rose-water glaze.
我把每块饼干都浸在柠檬玫瑰水里。
And then I'm just gonna airbrush
然后我要喷枪
and then do decorations on top of that.
然后在上面做装饰。
So I have to work quickly.
所以我得抓紧时间。
First, I'm gonna airbrush four cookies red
首先，我要把四块饼干喷成红色
and then four cookies purple and then four cookies blue.
然后是四块紫色的饼干和四块蓝色的饼干。
Noodle Maps -- The streets are gonna be, like, spaghetti.
面条地图，街道会像意大利面一样。
I'm using a toothpick.
我在用牙签。
And I'm indenting all the different streets
我在缩进不同的街道
for the yellow to fall in.
让黄色落进去。
JASON: Cole, that is genius.
杰森:科尔，真是天才。
Cakemaker 1000 -- very self-explanatory.
蛋糕机1000——不言自明。
It's just gonna be a cake on top that I can decorate.
只是在上面放个蛋糕，我可以装饰一下。
And then Spot-a-Fry is gonna have fries on the front.
然后Spot-a-Fry会在前面放薯条。
And I think that'd look really, really slick.
我觉得那样看起来会非常非常光滑。
AUDRA: So my cookies are out of the oven.
我的饼干从烤箱里出来了。
And I go to lift one off.
我要把一个举起来。
Oh, my God. Those are raw. These are raw.
我的天啊。那些是生的。这些是生的。
15 minutes left, bakers.
还有15分钟，面包师们。
You got 15 minutes.
给你15分钟。
So I have to get them back in the oven.
所以我得把它们放回烤箱里。
And I have no idea if I'm gonna have enough time to bake them.
我不知道我是否有足够的时间来烤它们。
Oh, gosh.
哦,天哪。
Ooh, looking good.
哦，看起来不错。
My cookies don't need to bake for that long
我的饼干不需要烤那么久
because I like my sugar cookies really chewy
因为我喜欢有嚼劲的甜饼干
and super soft.
而且超级柔软。
Aidan just pulled his cookies out of the oven.
艾登刚把饼干从烤箱里拿出来了。
They look pretty blond to me.
在我看来，她们都是金发碧眼。
And that's a nice way of saying,
这是一种很好的说法，
"I don't think they're done."
“我认为他们还没有结束。”
Oh, the sugar cookies look delicious.
哦，糖饼干看起来很好吃。
I don't really like fondant.
我不太喜欢软糖。
But it will work in this situation the best.
但在这种情况下，它会发挥最好的作用。
I don't want, like, too big of a thick slab of fondant.
我不想要太厚的软糖。
For my Cheesecake Chess,
我的芝士蛋糕象棋，
I have to cut out each of the little squares of fondant
我要把每一块方糖都切下来
for the chessboard
为了棋盘
and just apply a little bit of water
然后浇一点水
to each one to help it stick.
每个人都要坚持下去。
And I have little blueberries and strawberries on each end.
我在两端都放了一些蓝莓和草莓。
Strawberries versus blueberries.
草莓vs蓝莓。
For my Fruitcake Ninja,
对于我的水果蛋糕忍者，
I'm going to have a ninja standing there.
我会让一个忍者站在那里。
Awesome. And I'm gonna have the evil fruitcakes next to him.
太棒了。我要把邪恶水果蛋糕放在他旁边。
Just keep drawing.
继续画。继续画。
And for my Pieterest, I'm going to have a big pie
我的彼得莱斯特，我要一个大馅饼
with some fruits on the edges --
边上有一些水果
some cherries, some lemons.
一些樱桃，一些柠檬。
Kaniyah, yours looks so good.
Kaniyah，你的看起来真不错。
KANIYAH: Thank you.
卡尼亚:谢谢。
My Snackchat cookies look really cool,
我的零食饼干看起来很酷，
but it's too much fondant.
但是糖太多了。
See what happens if I do this.
看看如果我这么做会发生什么。
So why not make it with a real cookie?
那为什么不用真正的饼干来做呢?
Quick.
快。
10 minutes!
10分钟!
Okay.
好吧。
Come on, cookies. Come on. Come on, cookies.
加油，小甜饼。来吧。加油，小甜饼。
Ugh, just don't want to cook.
呃，只是不想做饭。
I need to start decorating.
我要开始装饰了。
JASON: Ugh!
杰森:啊!
I'm gonna have, like, a white background.
我要用白色的背景。
I'm just using a regular vanilla glaze
我用的是普通的香草酱
and making different colors for my artwork.
并为我的艺术品制作不同的颜色。
Usually, most apps just have, like,
通常，大多数应用程序都有，
a picture or a symbol on it.
上面有一幅画或一个符号。
Hangry Herd. Hangry Nerds.
饥饿“群。饥饿“书呆子。
This glaze is thick.
这釉很厚。
There we go.
好了。
I'm trying to decorate with this glaze.
我想用这种釉来装饰。
But it's way too sloppy.
但这太草率了。
What! I don't even know what that is.
什么!我都不知道那是什么。
Nerd lump things.
书呆子的东西。
Uh, Sugar Scoop.
糖勺。
Silver Scoop.
银勺。
Maybe just, like, a scoop with sugar in it.
也许就来个加糖的勺子。
Much better, kind of.
好多了，某种程度上。
My Tummy Rumble app,
My Tummy Rumble应用程序，
I'm having a sandwich on the top.
我要在上面放一个三明治。
Only eat bread...
只吃面包……
Want tomatoes in my sandwich.
我的三明治里要西红柿。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
This is an absolute mess.
这绝对是一团糟。
My sandwich looks kind of like a sandwich.
我的三明治看起来有点像三明治。
Well...
嗯…
But not really.
但事实并非如此。
All right, bakers. Five minutes left.
好了，面包师们。还剩五分钟。
So hurry app.
所以快点吧。
I have to get these out and cooling.
我得把这些拿出来降温。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
God, I left them in too long.
天啊，我把他们留在屋里太久了。
Some of my cookies are different sizes.
我的一些饼干大小不一。
The thin ones are brown and ugly.
瘦的是棕色的，很丑。
This really upsets me.
这真让我心烦。
No.
不。
I have to get started on some decorations for my cookies.
我得开始装饰我的饼干了。
Gonna make the most of these ones
我要好好利用这些机会
that, you know, aren't burnt.
你知道，没有烧焦。
I'm going to start with my Dessert Craft.
我要从我的甜点工艺开始。
I grab some vanilla fondant.
我拿了一些香草软糖。
I'm going to try and cut out some people.
我要试着切掉一些人。
And I see a flower cookie cutter.
我看到了一个花饼干切割器。
Stretch out the legs a little bit.
把腿伸展一下。
Boom, person.
繁荣,人。
kind of looks like a human with really,
看起来有点像人类，
really fat hands and really, really fat legs but, you know.
手很肥，腿也很肥，但是。
I'm gonna put something in his hand.
我要在他手里放点东西。
I draw a cake on there.
我在上面画了一个蛋糕。
And I grab a ton of sprinkles to decorate my cake.
我拿了一堆糖屑来装饰我的蛋糕。
For my Clash of Carbs,
在我的《碳水化合物的冲突》中，
it's basically a food-fight game.
这基本上是一个食物大战游戏。
I pipe a little person on it.
我在上面放了一个小人。
And I'm just, like, sticking candy on it.
我就像在上面粘糖一样。
And it looks like food.
它看起来像食物。
Oh, no. I still have to do my Pastry Chef Go.
哦,不。我还得去做我的糕点大厨。
One minute.
一分钟。
No. I'm not gonna finish.
不。我说不完了。
Audra, are you gonna finish?
奥德拉，你能讲完吗?
-Probably not. -Go, go, go.
或许不是。-走，走，走。
JASON: This is terrible.
杰森:这太可怕了。
30 seconds, bakers. 30 seconds.
30秒，面包师们。30秒。
Get 'em on the plate.
把它们放到盘子里。
Hustle, hustle, hustle, hustle.
快点，快点，快点，快点。
BOTH: 10...9...8...
两种:10 8 9……
7...6...5...4...3...2...1.
七……六……五……四……三……2…1。
-Oh, my God. -Hands up.
-我的天啊。手了。
Audra, you about gave me a heart attack.
奥德拉，你差点把我吓出心脏病。
Wait for it.
等一下。等一下。
App-plause.
App-plause。
I look down at my three app cookies.
我低头看了看我的三个应用程序cookie。
And they look so messy.
而且它们看起来很乱。
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary sugar cookies, hit the send button.
普通的糖饼干，按发送键。
A sweet mobile text right after this.
这之后再来条贴心的手机短信。
ANNOUNCER: How to make text-message cookies.
播音员:如何制作短信饼干。
Gather together flour, sugar-cookie dough,
把面粉，糖饼干面团，
a rolling pin, a pizza cutter
擀面杖，披萨刀
and an assortment of colored frostings.
还有各种各样的彩色糖霜。
Flour your surface.
在你的表面撒上面粉。
Roll out your dough.
把面团擀开。
Cut the cookies into rectangles and bake.
把饼干切成长方形，然后烤制。
Frost them with a background color and let dry.
给它们涂上一层背景色，然后晾干。
Then pipe on text boxes
然后输入文本框
and a whole colorful conversation.
还有一场丰富多彩的谈话。
Emoticons never tasted so sweet.
表情符号从来没有这么甜蜜过。
For more fun treats like this,
想要获得更多这样的乐趣，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
Make-believe food app cookies.
虚构的食物应用程序饼干。
This was pretty cool, right?
这很酷，对吧?
VALERIE: I love this one.
瓦莱丽:我喜欢这个。
You want to bring in Cole?
你想把科尔带来吗?
All right. Hey, Cole. -Mm-hmm?
好吧。嘿,科尔。-嗯?
Cole, so what were your apps?
科尔，你的应用程序是什么?
I had Spot-A-Fry,
我吃了鱼苗点点，
Noodle Maps and Cakemaker 1000.
面条地图和蛋糕机1000。
What do each of those apps do?
这些应用都是做什么的?
Cakemaker 1000 -- The mean Duff walks in.
蛋糕师1000——卑鄙的达夫走了进来。
-Is that how I walk? -And he tries to...
-我就是这样走路的吗?-他试图…
Yeah. He tries to, like, smash your cake.
是的。他想砸你的蛋糕。
So you have to, like, fight him off.
所以你得跟他打一架。
-So it's a game app. -Yes.
-所以这是个游戏软件-是的
-Okay. -A game.
-好的。——游戏。
Yeah, I'm like the old bad guy.
是啊，我就像个老坏蛋。
All righty, then.
那好吧。
Cole, I love the way that these are decorated.
科尔，我喜欢这些装饰的方式。
Absolutely. But, you know, I got to say,
绝对的。但是，我得说，
I could not tell that that was a 1000.
我看不出那是1000。
-Yeah.
-是的。-是的。
You probably would have done better
你可能会做得更好
if you used a little bit thicker
如果你用厚一点的
consistency of frosting for the details.
细节磨砂的一致性。
And they wouldn't have spread out as much.
这样它们就不会分散得那么多。
-Mm-hmm. -Well, what's the next one?
-嗯。-下一个是什么?
For Noodle Maps, the noodles in Noodle Town
面条地图，面条镇的面条
are all running as fast as they can
他们都在尽可能快地跑吗
to go in their broth.
放进他们的汤里。
If they don't get there in time,
如果他们不能及时赶到，
they'll dry out and die.
它们会干涸而死。
He's got stories.
他有故事。
Awesome.
太棒了。
The Noodle Map app is really cool-looking.
“面条地图”应用看起来真的很酷。
It looks like a map. I like it, man.
它看起来像一张地图。我喜欢，伙计。
And in Spot-A-Fry,
在《鱼苗点》中，
the fries are fighting to get to the ketchup.
薯条在争抢番茄酱。
But if, like, one of the fries gets cut in half,
但如果其中一根薯条被切成两半，
the mustard comes out.
芥末出来了。
And they die.
然后他们就死了。
Okay. I got to tell you.
好吧。我得告诉你。
I just -- I love the different colors you chose.
我喜欢你选的不同颜色。
That really looks like a thing of fries to me.
在我看来，那真的很像薯条。
Well done.
做得很好。
Bon app-etite.
Bon app-etite。
Ha ha.
哈哈。
Well, they got beautiful color on 'em.
嗯，它们的颜色很漂亮。
So what kind of cookies did you make and frosting?
你做了什么样的饼干和糖霜?
A lemon sugar cookie with a lemon rose-water glaze.
柠檬糖饼干，上面有柠檬玫瑰水。
Hmm, Cole.
嗯,科尔。
Have you ever used rose water before?
你以前用过玫瑰水吗?
When you use it right, it's just, like, a hint.
如果你用对了，这就像是一个暗示。
When you use too much, it gets very perfumy.
当你用太多的时候，它会变得很香。
I think you got a little too much in here.
我觉得你放的太多了。
The glaze has that really nice lemon flavor,
釉料有很好的柠檬味，
but it's overshadowed by rose water.
但它被玫瑰水掩盖了。
Excellent sugar cookie, though.
不过，甜饼棒极了。
The cookie is nice and crunchy and crisp.
饼干很好吃，又脆又脆。
[ Deep voice ] Good job, Cole.
(低沉的声音)干得好，科尔。
Thank you.
[低沉的声音]谢谢。
-Thank you, Cole. -[ Normal voice ] Thank you.
-谢谢你，科尔。-[正常声音]谢谢。
Not a favorite flavor of mine.
不是我最喜欢的口味。
Yeah, rose water, it's tough.
是的，玫瑰水，很硬。
How's it going, Audra? -Good.
最近怎么样，奥德拉?改善情况。
You want to tell us what your cookies were today,
你想告诉我们你今天的饼干是什么吗，
what your apps were and your stories?
你的应用是什么，你的故事是什么?
For Clash of Carbs,
对于碳水化合物的冲突，
it's kind of like a food-fight game.
有点像食物大战游戏。
So you just, like, throw food at people.
所以你就朝别人扔食物。
I love food fights.
我喜欢食物大战。
Oh, no. I'm thinking that's the middle one.
哦,不。我想应该是中间那个。
Is that Clash of Carbs?
这是碳水化合物的冲突吗?
-Yeah.
-是的。-是的。
Have you ever been in a food fight?
你参加过食物大战吗?
One time, I threw a fry at someone.
有一次，我朝别人扔了一根薯条。
But that doesn't really count.
但这并不算。
-A fry? -Yeah.
——弗莱?-是的。
So which ones are these two?
这两个是哪两个呢?
The one with the flower-looking thingy,
那个戴着像花一样东西的，
that's Dessert Craft.
这就是甜点工艺。
That's supposed to be a human, by the way.
顺便说一下，那应该是个人。
And then he's holding a little birthday cake in his hand.
然后他手里拿着一个小生日蛋糕。
It's abstract, app-stract.
它是抽象的，应用程序抽象的。
Okay. Well, what do you do in this game?
好吧。那么，你在这个游戏中做什么?
You can bake anything you want,
你可以烤任何你想烤的东西
but you have to find the resources for it.
但你必须为它找到资源。
You have to find your baking ingredients?
你还得找烘焙材料吗?
-Yeah. -Okay.
-是的。-好的。
And this one is... -Pastry Chef Go.
这个是……-糕点师走吧。
You are the culinary teacher.
你是烹饪老师。
And whoever is teaching just runs away.
教课的人就跑了。
And you have to catch them.
你必须抓住他们。
Sounds like fun.
听起来很有趣。
I guess I'm having a hard time
我想我的日子不好过
figuring out which app is which.
弄清楚哪个应用是哪个应用。
I mean, I just don't know that these tell me
我是说，我只是不知道这些能告诉我什么
what I'm about to click into.
我要点进去的东西
What happened with your time management today?
你今天的时间管理怎么样了?
I felt like I was moving fast.
我觉得我走得很快。
But I guess I went slow.
但我想我走得太慢了。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Uh, what flavor cookies did you pick?
你选了什么口味的饼干?
A lemon cookie,
一块柠檬饼干，
and then I did a vanilla frosting.
然后我做了香草糖霜。
-Did you put salt in there? -Depends. Is it too salty?
-你放盐了吗?视情况而定。是不是太咸了?
I'm tasting salt with the sugar.
我在用糖尝盐。
It's very pleasing to my palate.
这味道很合我的口味。
Oh, well, yeah. I did.
哦，好吧，是的。我做到了。
Not the prettiest cookies in the world,
不是世界上最漂亮的饼干，
but they're really delicious. -Thank you.
但是它们真的很好吃。-谢谢。
Um, I could use a little bit more lemon.
我还可以再加点柠檬。
I'm not getting a whole bunch.
我没有得到一大堆。
-Subtle. -Thanks, Audra.
微妙的。Audra, -谢谢。
-Thank you.
Audra, -谢谢。-谢谢。
You can really taste the salt on the crispy one.
脆脆的那只真的能尝出盐的味道。
-Yeah. -But they're a mess.
-是的。-但他们一团糟。
Jason.
杰森。
Did you have a good day?
你今天过得好吗?
Yeah, I got some new apps on my phone.
是啊，我手机上有新应用。
Oh, cool. Tell me about 'em. What'd you get?
哦,很酷。跟我说说，你得到了什么?
The Tummy Rumble app is the sandwich.
“Tummy Rumble”应用程序就是三明治。
-Are you sure that's a sandwich? -I tried...
-你确定那是三明治吗?我试过……
It's kind of hard to decorate with glaze.
用釉料装饰有点困难。
That looks more like a meatball
那看起来更像肉丸
with marinara and parsley on it.
上面放着番茄酱和欧芹。
-I'm good with a meatball. -Okay.
-我擅长做肉丸子。-好的。
What does Tummy Rumble do?
肚子咕咕叫是做什么的?
I have no idea. I haven't played it yet.
我不知道。我还没玩过呢。
-We need stories, Jason. -What's the next app?
-我们需要故事，杰森。下一个应用是什么?
Um, the Sugar Scoop game,
糖勺游戏
you try to do something in the game.
你试着在游戏中做点什么。
I haven't really come up with it.
我还没想出来。
It's still in the beta version right now.
它现在还在测试阶段。
Um...
嗯…
How much sugar did you put in this sugar scoop?
你在这个糖勺里放了多少糖?
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Geez, that's a lot of sugar on there, man.
天啊，上面的糖太多了。
So what, uh, what are we doing here with this?
那我们，我们在这干嘛呢?
-What's that app? -Hangry Nerds.
-那个应用程序是什么?饥饿“书呆子。
Hangry Nerds. Okay. What happens in Hangry Nerds?
饥饿“书呆子。好吧。《饿怒的书呆子》里发生了什么?
-I have no idea. -You've said all along
-我不知道。-你一直都说
that decorating is not your strong suit.
装修不是你的强项。
-Yeah. -I believe you.
-是的。-我相信你。
These are not that good.
这些不是很好。
But I feel like if you had the story
但我觉得如果你有故事
to go with your cookies,
为了搭配你的饼干
I feel like I could forgive the decorating a little bit.
我觉得我可以原谅这里的装饰。
You want to hear something positive?
你想听点积极的吗?
That's a really nice-looking bottom of a cookie.
这是一块非常好看的饼干。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
What flavor are your cookies?
你们的饼干是什么口味的?
I used some orange juice.
我用了一些橙汁。
You -- are you getting any orange?
你有橙汁吗?
Not getting a little orange.
没有一点橘色。
-Oh. -Mnh-mnh.
-哦。-Mnh-mnh。
But I like the texture of the cookie.
但我喜欢饼干的质地。
It's crunchy. I think it's done.
脆脆的。我想已经完成了。
Jason, I think you got a good cookie.
杰森，我觉得你的饼干很好吃。
-Thank you. -But you're super smart.
-谢谢。-但你非常聪明。
You're funny. You're creative.
你有趣。你是有创意的。
And you didn't have any stories for us, man.
你也没给我们讲什么故事，伙计。
Come on.
来吧。
I don't know. All right. Take it easy, man.
我不知道。好吧。别紧张，伙计。
Thanks, Jason.
谢谢你,杰森。
Chocolate.
巧克力。
Nice.
好了。
We've created a monster.
我们创造了一个怪物。
Mobile app cookies. I'm telling you now.
移动应用程序cookie。我现在告诉你。
We're gonna make a million bucks off one of these things.
我们要靠这东西赚一百万了。
Justice? Hi.
正义吗?嗨。
Tell us the apps that you got
告诉我们你有哪些应用
and then the stories behind the apps.
然后是应用程序背后的故事。
Eclairiscope is a, like,
Eclairiscope就像，
gossip news channel for eclairs.
泡芙的八卦新闻频道。
Like, "Mrs. Eclair this morning,
比如"今天早上埃克莱尔太太
when she was going to go perform on stage,
当她准备上台表演时，
she got so nervous that all her cream filling
她太紧张了，所有的奶油都被填满了
just came right out of her."
就从她嘴里说出来的。”
An eclair gossip channel.
泡芙八卦频道。
I love this. -I like it. Okay.
我喜欢这个。-我喜欢。好吧。
So it's an eclair. And it has paper coming out.
这是一个泡芙。它有纸出来。
Yeah, I'm -- I'm trying to figure out
是啊，我在想办法
if it looks like an eclair or, like, a meatball sub.
如果它看起来像泡芙或者肉丸三明治。
-Or a hot dog even. -It's something.
-甚至热狗也不行。-是。
-Okay. -Okay, next one.
-好的。-好的，下一个。
Parmville is, like, is little mice.
帕姆维尔就像小老鼠。
They have these cheese houses.
他们有这些奶酪屋。
And they need to go to Catville to get some food.
他们得去卡维尔弄点吃的。
But then the cats see them.
但是猫看到了他们。
So they have to run through obstacles to get home.
所以他们必须穿越障碍才能回家。
Okay, wait a minute. They don't have any food.
好吧，等一下。他们没有任何食物。
But they live in houses made of cheese.
但他们住在奶酪做的房子里。
It's poisonous cheese.
这是有毒的奶酪。
That's what it is.
就是这样。
He's right on top of it.
他就在上面。
Say no more. Say no more. Okay.
别再说了。别再说了。好吧。
Now, that definitely, 100%,
现在，绝对，100%，
looks like a house made of cheese.
看起来像个奶酪做的房子。
Mm-hmm. All right. And then Graham Hacker.
嗯哼。好吧。然后是Graham Hacker。
Graham Hacker, one dark and stormy night,
格雷厄姆·哈克，在一个风雨交加的夜晚，
there was a scientist.
有一个科学家。
And he was just like,
他就说，
"These graham crackers must taste so much
“这些全麦饼干一定很好吃
better than normal graham crackers."
比普通全麦饼干好。”
And why was he Russian?
为什么他是俄罗斯人?
Because it sounds more evil.
因为听起来更邪恶。
Okay. All right.
好吧。好吧。
And the lightning struck his building.
闪电击中了他的房子。
And then all his potions exploded.
然后他所有的魔药都爆炸了。
And they all went over graham cracker.
他们都在吃全麦饼干。
And he grew and grew into Graham Hacker.
他逐渐成长为格雷厄姆·哈克。
Wow. Okay. All right.
哇。好吧。好吧。
-Lots of fun stories. -Yeah.
-有很多有趣的故事。-是的。
You have a very, very vivid imagination.
你的想象力非常非常丰富。
Graham Hacker, you know, he kind of looks...
格雷厄姆·哈克，你知道，他看起来有点…
-Yep. -...like a jerk, you know?
是的。-…就像个混蛋，你知道吗?
He looks like, I don't want nothing to do with that guy.
他看起来像，我不想和他有任何关系。
-Okay. -Wow.
-好的。-哇。
Wa-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wa-ha-ha-ha-ha。
I am the graham cracker.
我是全麦饼干。
I think your presentation is great.
我认为你的报告很棒。
-Nice thin fondant. -They look tight, clean.
-薄薄的软糖。-看起来又紧又干净。
Maybe a little issue on the vividness of the color
也许在颜色的鲜艳度上有点小问题
because when you look at your phone
因为当你看手机的时候
with the apps on it,
有了上面的应用，
all of them have vibrant colors on it.
它们都有鲜艳的颜色。
These are a little subdued.
这些有点柔和。
Let's eat this cookie.
我们吃这块饼干吧。
Mm.
毫米。
Tell us about your flavor.
跟我们说说你的口味。
I did an orange sugar cookie with an orange buttercream.
我做了一个橙糖饼干和橙奶油。
It's all over me.
我浑身上下都是。
That's a really good sign, by the way.
顺便说一句，这是个好兆头。
-Mm-hmm. -Thank you.
-嗯。-谢谢。
You did not beat your dough up, really tender.
你没有把面团揉碎，真的很嫩。
I can taste the orange. -Yeah, I really like it.
我能尝到橘子的味道。-是的，我很喜欢。
It's nice and subtle in the buttercream.
奶油里的味道很好，很微妙。
It just layers on that orange flavor.
它会让橘子的味道更浓。
-Good job, man. -Thank you.
-干得好，伙计。-谢谢。
-All right. -It's an app.
-好的。-是一个应用程序。
It needs to be more colorful. -Totally. No, I -- I agree.
它需要更丰富多彩。完全。不，我同意。
But definitely best flavor.
但绝对是最好的口味。
-What's up, Kaniyah? -'Sup.
-怎么了，卡尼亚?——“吃晚饭。
Tell me about your app cookies. What happens in Crumbtown?
告诉我你的应用程序cookie。在克伦镇发生了什么?
This crumb guy is running across all these booby traps.
这个吃面包屑的家伙正在穿越这些陷阱。
And if he steps on a booby trap,
如果他踩到了诡雷，
he gets eaten by a crumb dragon.
他被面包屑龙吃掉了。
I -- I want to meet a crumb dragon.
我，我想见见面包屑龙。
Me too. I feel like that'd be a lot of fun.
我也是。我觉得那会很有趣。
I like the crumbs on it.
我喜欢上面的面包屑。
You know, very inventive use of crumbs.
面包屑的用法很有创意。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Now, what about Buttercream Bingo?
现在，奶油宾果怎么样?
In Buttercream Bingo, the old lady cakes
在奶油宾果，老太太蛋糕
are fighting over
正在争夺
which one could get iced first
哪一个可以先被冰冻
and then have bingo.
然后是宾果游戏。
All right.
好吧。好吧。
And bingo looks like bingo.
宾果游戏看起来就像宾果游戏。
I even put Free in the middle of it.
我甚至把Free放在了中间。
"That's a bingo."
“这是一个宾果游戏。”
And then Snackchat.
然后是零食聊天。
This cookie tries to attack this person.
这个饼干试图攻击这个人。
And the person's like, "No! Let's talk this out."
那个人说:“不!让我们谈谈这件事。”
You know what? I really like your stories.
你知道吗?我真的很喜欢你的故事。
I think they're -- they're really fun.
我觉得他们，他们真的很有趣。
I love the Snackchat cookie 'cause it's like a cookie
我喜欢Snackchat饼干，因为它就像一块饼干
used as a decoration on another cookie.
用作另一块饼干上的装饰。
And I think that's amazing.
我觉得这很神奇。
I'm wondering why there's no buttercream
我在想为什么没有奶油
or anything to hold your fondant down.
或者任何东西来固定你的糖。
But here's the deal. I'm glad it's off
但事情是这样的。我很高兴取消了
because that's really super thick fondant,
因为那是超级厚的软糖，
not really something I want to bite into.
不是我想咬的东西。
Mm.
毫米。
That's a really crunchy cookie.
这饼干真脆。
It's chewy and crunchy.
它有嚼劲又脆。
Kaniyah, I think your dough got a little overworked.
卡尼亚，我觉得你的面团有点过度劳累了。
And that's why they're crunchy and chewy at the same time.
这就是为什么它们同时又脆又有嚼劲。
They got a little tough.
他们变得有点强硬。
Just like you, they're a little tough.
和你一样，他们也有点强硬。
You know what I mean?
你懂我的意思吗?
What did you use for your citrus twist?
你做柑橘皮的时候用了什么?
-Orange. -I do taste some orange.
橙色。我确实尝出了一点橘子味。
So that's a good sign.
这是个好迹象。
There's something missing, though. What is that?
不过，还是少了点什么。那是什么?
Kind of, you know what it tastes like is a, like,
有点，你知道它尝起来就像，
a fortune cookie. -What?
幸运饼干。-什么?
You know, there's just kind of no flavor.
你知道的，就是没有味道。
All right, Kaniyah. Thank you. -Thank you, Kaniyah.
好的，Kaniyah。谢谢你！-谢谢你，Kaniyah。
-You're welcome. -Just got really worked.
你是受欢迎的。-我真的很忙。
Okay.
好吧。
-How's it going, Aidan? -Good.
-怎么样，艾登?改善情况。
Tell us about your cookies and what your apps were.
告诉我们你的cookie和你的应用程序是什么。
The Cheesecake Chess
芝士蛋糕象棋
is strawberries versus blueberries
是草莓还是蓝莓
battling it out in chess
在国际象棋中一决雌雄
so that they can be on the cheesecake.
这样就可以放在芝士蛋糕上了。
That sounds like a fun game.
听起来是个有趣的游戏。
Okay.
好吧。
That's a really thick fondant
那是很厚的软糖
that's bigger than your cookie.
那比你的饼干还大。
Sorry.
对不起。
What's the next app?
下一个应用是什么?
Fruitcake Ninja is about the Emperor
水果蛋糕忍者是关于天皇的
banished the fruitcakes down below in a deep dungeon.
把水果蛋糕放逐到地下的地牢里。
But now the fruitcakes are escaping.
但现在水果蛋糕正在逃离。
And he's sending his lead ninja
他派出了他的领头忍者
to save the whole country from fruitcakes.
把整个国家从水果蛋糕中拯救出来。
The ninja, I know that's a guy
忍者，我知道是个男的
because the guy on there doing something.
因为那家伙在做什么。
Uh, maybe it's a dog-walking app.
也许是个遛狗软件。
I don't know.
我不知道。
And this one is...
这个是……
Pieterest is the ultimate pie network for grandmothers.
Pieterest是祖母们的终极派网。
And they share pie ideas.
他们分享派的想法。
And they have pie conversations, pie charts.
他们有饼式对话，饼状图。
-Love your stories. -The stories are really good.
-喜欢你的故事。-故事真的很好。
Thanks.
谢谢。
But, you know, I got to say with your decorations,
但是，你知道，我不得不说你的装饰，
I really expected more from you.
我对你有更高的期望。
Yeah, not my best day.
是啊，不是我最好的一天。
I'm a little concerned with the doneness
我有点担心它的熟度
of your cookie, too.
还有你的饼干。
They seem really, really blond.
他们看起来真的是金发碧眼。
What?
怎么啦？
I do like chewy sugar cookies.
我喜欢有嚼劲的糖饼干。
Okay. Good to know.
好吧。很高兴知道。
I would rather have a chewy one than a crispy one.
我宁愿要有嚼劲的，也不要脆的。
Tell me what flavors your cookies are.
告诉我你的饼干是什么口味的。
They are lime-flavored cookies.
它们是酸橙味的饼干。
And then I just have a big layer of vanilla buttercream.
然后我就有了一层香草奶油。
Mm. I taste lime.
嗯，我尝到酸橙的味道。
Aidan, you got to bake these longer.
艾登，你得烤久一点。
This isn't chewy. This is underbaked.
这个不耐嚼。这是欠考虑的。
I can still taste the flour. -Aw, disappointing.
我还能尝出面粉的味道。哦,失望。
-Yeah. -Don't be shy, man.
-是的。-别害羞，伙计。
Color is flavor.
颜色就是味道。
But your stories -- out of this world.
但你的故事，来自这个世界。
-Thanks, Aidan. -Thanks. Bye.
-谢谢,艾丹。-谢谢。再见。
-Good job. -Bye.
改善工作。再见。
I just expected more.
我只是期待更多。
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package
会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包吗
that includes a future story in "Food Network Magazine"...
包括《美食网络杂志》的未来故事…
Hallelujah!
阿利路亚!
-And... -$25,000.
——……——25000美元。
[ All cheering ]
[众人欢呼]
Winner is coming.
赢家来了。
Mobile App Cookie Challenge.
手机应用Cookie挑战。
So this is, uh, a decorating challenge...
所以这是一个装修挑战…
-Mm-hmm. -...a taste challenge...
-嗯。-…味觉挑战……
and a storytelling challenge.
还有讲故事的挑战。
Yeah, I think some of our app developers did pretty good.
是的，我认为我们的一些应用程序开发人员做得很好。
You know, like Justice.
你知道，就像正义。
He did great.
他做得很好。
Now, for me today,
今天，对我来说，
Cole made some beautiful cookies.
科尔做了一些漂亮的饼干。
Cole's got to figure out how to make his flavors
科尔得弄清楚怎么做他的口味
match his decorating.
搭配他的装饰。
Conversely, Justice needs to bring
相反，正义需要带来
his decorating up to match his flavors.
他的装饰要符合他的口味。
And we know he can. We've seen him decorate.
我们知道他可以。我们见过他装修。
Let's talk about a few mobile app cookies
让我们来谈谈一些手机应用cookie
that, um, I would probably delete.
我可能会删掉的
What was going on with Aidan today?
艾登今天怎么了?
I've had better days.
我也有过好日子。
I mean, that fondant was, like, half-an-inch thick.
我是说，那块软糖大概有半英寸厚。
And the cookie was way underbaked.
饼干烤得太烂了。
But the thing that really disappointed me today --
但今天真正让我失望的是
Audra's decorating.
Audra装饰。
No. I'm not gonna finish.
不。我说不完了。
Really sloppy design.
真是草率的设计。
By the time she had to get them decorated,
等她把房子装饰好了，
it was just a rush of mess.
只是一团乱。
Yeah.
是的。
What happened to Jason today?
杰森今天怎么了?
Dude, I do not know, man.
伙计，我不知道。
I don't even know what that is.
我都不知道那是什么。
It's just sloppy.
这太草率了。
You know, the thing that really disappointed me today
今天最让我失望的事
the most was his stories.
最重要的是他的故事。
He had no stories.
他没有故事。
I haven't really come up with it.
我还没想出来。
It's still in the beta version.
它还在测试阶段。
Of all these guys, Jason loves to talk.
在这些人中，杰森最爱说话了。
-Yeah. -You finally give him a chance,
-是的。-你终于给他机会了
and he's like, "Eh."
他说，“嗯。”
All right, Val. Mobile App Cookies.
好了，瓦尔，手机应用cookie。
We are going to push send and send somebody home.
我们要按下发送键，然后送人回家。
You ready to make that decision?
你准备好做决定了吗?
Delete.
删除。
Swipe left.
刷卡离开。
Oh, it's a rough one.
哦，这是一个艰难的过程。
Bakers, two of you gave us cookies
面包师，你们俩给了我们饼干
with good-looking designs
有好看的设计
and great explanations of how your apps worked.
以及对你的应用程序如何工作的出色解释。
Justice...
正义……
...and Cole.
…和科尔。
Yes, thank God.
是的，感谢上帝。
Justice, we liked the subtle orange
正义，我们喜欢淡淡的橙色
in your cookies and frosting.
在你的饼干和糖霜里。
Your designs were clever.
你的设计很聪明。
And your app stories were hilarious.
你的应用故事很搞笑。
Hilarious.
搞笑。
Cole, your designs were colorful
科尔，你的设计很丰富多彩
and really eye-catching.
而且非常引人注目。
Your cookie had a nice crunch.
你的饼干嘎吱作响。
And your app stories were right on.
你的应用故事很正确。
[ Deep voice ] Thank you.
[低沉的声音]谢谢。
But only one baker's cookies
但只有一个面包师的饼干
topped our list of favorite apps.
在我们最喜欢的应用程序列表中名列前茅。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
...Justice.
…正义。
-Dang it. -Good job.
讨厌它。改善工作。
Congratulations, Justice.
祝贺你,正义。
Again, this is two times in a row, man.
再说一次，这是连续两次了。
You're so lucky.
你真幸运。
This is not what I was expecting.
这不是我想要的。
Only one other person has won twice --
只有另外一个人赢过两次——
Aidan and then me.
艾登和我。
That's crazy.
这太疯狂了。
I hope that I'll be able to ride this straight to the finale.
我希望我能直接骑到最后。
Don't be so surprised, man. You're awesome.
别这么惊讶，伙计。你太棒了。
Now, there were a few other bakers
还有一些其他的面包师
whose mobile app cookies had bugs that needed fixing
谁的移动应用cookie存在需要修复的漏洞
but were good enough to keep you in the running.
但我们的实力足以让你继续参选。
Those bakers are...
那些面包师……
...Aidan...
艾丹…
Thank God.
感谢上帝。
And the other baker is...
另一个面包师是……
I really hope I'm safe.
我真的希望我很安全。
...Kaniyah.
……Kaniyah。
Hallelujah!
阿利路亚!
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
Was not expecting that.
我没想到会这样。
That was amazing.
太神奇了。
That's gonna be a meme.
这将是一个表情包。
Whoo, okay. Bakers, unfortunately,
喔,好吧。面包师,不幸的是,
that leaves Jason and Audra.
那就剩下杰森和奥德拉了。
Please, step forward. -Fourth time.
请往前走。第五次时间。
It really stinks being here again.
再次来到这里真的很糟糕。
Fourth time.
第四次。
You both came up with some really fun concepts.
你们都想出了一些很有趣的概念。
But there were error messages in your execution.
但是在执行过程中出现了错误信息。
Jason, we didn't get any citrus twist in your cookie.
杰森，你的饼干里没有柑橘皮。
Your app stories, which we all thought
你的应用故事，我们都觉得
were gonna be your strong suit,
我们会成为你的强项
were really disappointing.
我们真的很失望。
Audra, your cookies were inconsistent.
奥德拉，你的饼干不稳定。
And they needed more lemon.
他们还需要更多的柠檬。
And your decorating,
还有你的装饰，
let's face it, was really messy.
让我们面对现实吧，真的很乱。
-I agree. -I'm sorry.
我同意。我很抱歉。
But the baker who will be leaving us today is...
但是今天要离开我们的面包师是…
...Jason.
杰森。
Sorry, man.
对不起,男人。
You're totally awesome.
你太棒了。
You made it really, really far.
你走得非常非常远。
Don't be hard on yourself.
不要对自己太苛刻。
VALERIE: Don't stop baking.
瓦莱丽:不要停止烘焙。
Please say your goodbyes and exit the kitchen.
请说再见，然后离开厨房。
-Bye, Jason. -Hey, dude.
再见,杰森。-嘿,伙计。
Go get that crepe truck.
去叫那辆可丽饼车。
I'm feeling a little sad.
我觉得有点难过。
But I'm still thankful that I made it this far.
但我仍然很感激我能走到这一步。
AUDRA: Gonna miss you, Jason.
我会想你的，杰森。
And it was awesome to be able to meet Duff
能见到达夫真是太棒了
and Valerie in person.
和瓦莱丽本人
-See ya, homey. -Chocolate!
-再见，兄弟。巧克力!
-Yes. Yes. -Oh, yes.
-是的。是的。-哦,是的。
VALERIE: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
瓦莱丽:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
One dozen sugar cookies
一打甜饼干
with the perfect icons for three of these apps.
有三个应用程序的完美图标。
Oh, I'm not gonna finish.
我说不完了。
DUFF: You've said all along
达夫:你一直都说
that decorating is not your strong suit.
装修不是你的强项。
-Yeah. -I believe you.
-是的。-我相信你。
Ugh.
啊。
There's something missing, though. What is that?
不过，还是少了点什么。那是什么?
You know what it tastes like is, uh, like a fortune cookie.
你知道它尝起来就像，像幸运饼干。
-What? -There's just kind of no flavor.
-什么?-没什么味道。
-Justice. -Your designs were clever.
正义。-你的设计很聪明。
And your app stories were hilarious.
你的应用故事很搞笑。
Baker who will be leaving us today is Jason.
贝克今天要离开我们的是杰森。
Sorry, man.
对不起,男人。
**
**
[ Gasps ]
[喘息]
Chicken!
鸡!
Oh, bunnies!
[喘气]哦，兔子!
Pig! Oh, my God!
猪!我的天啊!
That is the most adorable thing I've ever seen.
这是我见过的最可爱的东西。
Five little animals. They're so adorable.
五只小动物。他们太可爱了。
It's a mini pig.
这是一只迷你猪。
Turtles!
海龟!
What?
怎么啦？
I think the challenge might be petting-zoo snacks.
我觉得挑战可能是宠物动物园的零食。
I don't know.
我不知道。
-TOGETHER: Hi. -Hi.
同一个:嗨。-你好。
Welcome back, bakers.
欢迎回来，面包师们。
You are the formidable five.
你们是强大的五人组。
And because you've come so far,
因为你已经走了这么远，
we thought we'd celebrate
我们想庆祝一下
with a "Kids Baking Championship" pet project.
“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的宠物项目
-Yay. -What is this?
耶。-这是什么?
One of these critters
这些小动物之一
is going to inspire what you bake today.
会给你今天的烘焙带来灵感。
If you do the math, each of you has a 20% chance
如果你算一下，你们每个人都有20%的机会
of becoming Kids Baking Champion.
成为儿童烘焙冠军
-Yeah.
-是的。-是的。
And you have a 20% chance
你有20%的机会
of getting paired up
配对的感觉
with this crazy-looking Silky chicken.
这只看起来很疯狂的丝滑鸡
[ Laughs ] [ Chicken crowing ]
[笑][鸡叫]
It's not even morning.
还没到早上呢。
Dude, that chicken's got a lot to say,
老兄，那只鸡有很多话要说，
well, for a chicken.
对一只鸡来说。
Okay. You're gonna pick a card
好吧。你要选一张牌
to find out which animal will inspire your pet project.
找出哪种动物会激发你的宠物计划。
-It's a random pick. -No.
-是随机挑选的。-不。
This one.
这一个。
[ Gasps ] I got Silky chicken.
我买了丝滑鸡。
I'll pick, uh, that arm.
我挑那条胳膊。
I hope that I might get the turtle.
我希望我能抓到乌龟。
Guinea pig.
几内亚猪。
I got the rabbit.
我抓到兔子了。
I got a turtle. Yes!
我有一只乌龟。是的!
And I got mini pig.
我得到了迷你猪。
Let's kick off this Pet Project Challenge.
让我们开始这个宠物项目挑战。
You have 90 minutes
你有90分钟的时间
to make a dessert inspired by your animal.
以你的动物为灵感做一道甜点。
What?
怎么啦？
Pet Project dessert can look like your animal.
宠物计划的甜点可以看起来像你的动物。
It can be something they'd love to eat,
可以是他们喜欢吃的东西，
whatever, as long as you can tell us the connection.
随你便，只要你能告诉我们其中的联系。
I've got this.
我来搞定。
90 minutes, Pet Project Desserts.
90分钟，宠物计划甜点。
And your time starts...
你的时间开始了……
BOTH: Now.
两种:现在。
Whee.
哟。
Yeast.
酵母。
Shoot. I need the cake flour.
开枪。我需要蛋糕粉。
We have 90 minutes to make an animal-inspired dessert.
我们有90分钟的时间来做一个动物甜品。
I get the turtle. Yay.
我得到了乌龟。耶。
I have a really cool idea for this.
我有个很酷的主意。
And it connects with my life.
它与我的生活息息相关。
At the end of our street,
在这条街的尽头，
there is a big pond full of turtles.
有一个满是乌龟的大池塘。
I'm gonna make a dessert that looks like a turtle.
我要做一个看起来像乌龟的甜点。
So my dessert will have a chocolate shell
所以我的甜点会有一个巧克力外壳
with a bit of yellow cake and buttercream inside.
里面有一点黄蛋糕和奶油。
To make my yellow cake, I mix sugar, flour,
为了做我的黄蛋糕，我把糖，面粉，
leavening agent, salt, buttermilk,
发酵剂、盐、酪乳、
just regular yellow cake ingredients.
就是普通的黄色蛋糕原料。
To get those pesky little bits.
得到那些讨厌的小块。
I make this yellow cake a lot.
我经常做这个黄色的蛋糕。
It's pretty much been everywhere in this championship.
在这个冠军赛中，它几乎无处不在。
Perfect cake batter into the oven.
把完美的蛋糕糊放进烤箱。
This is such a creative challenge.
这是一个创造性的挑战。
I want to squeeze that bunny. It looks so soft.
我想挤那只兔子。它看起来很软。
KANIYAH: My animal is a bunny rabbit.
我的动物是一只小兔子。
Yay 'cause bunnies eat fruit.
耶，因为兔子吃水果。
Hi, Kaniyah. Hello.
嗨,Kaniyah。你好。
So, tell me what you're making for us.
告诉我你要给我们做什么。
I'm making a pineapple upside-down cake.
我在做菠萝倒立蛋糕。
You're making a pineapple upside-down cake for a rabbit?
你要给兔子做菠萝倒立蛋糕?
Yeah because I saw rabbits eating pineapple.
是的，因为我看到兔子吃菠萝。
You saw rabbits
你看到兔子吃菠萝。
-Yes. -Okay.
-是的。-好的。
Don't you doubt me.
别怀疑我。
All right.
好吧。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Pineapple, pineapple, pineapple, and cherries.
菠萝，菠萝，菠萝和樱桃。
I'm making a pineapple upside-down cake
我在做菠萝倒立蛋糕
with pineapple ice cream.
配菠萝冰淇淋。
The first thing I need to do is to get my butter
我要做的第一件事是拿出黄油
and brown sugar melted.
红糖融化了。
Melt.
融化。
This is gonna be the top layer of the cake
这是蛋糕的最上面一层
once I flip it over.
一旦我把它翻过来。
There we go.
好了。
Now I'll get started on my cake batter.
现在我要开始做蛋糕面糊了。
First, I sift together all my dry ingredients.
首先，我把所有干食材筛在一起。
And I add butter, milk, and oil and eggs.
然后加入黄油、牛奶、油和鸡蛋。
Once that is smooth, I use the pineapple juice...
一旦光滑了，我就用菠萝汁……
Ah, crushed pineapple.
啊，菠萝碎。
...and a little bit of the pineapple chunks
…再加一点菠萝块
to give it a more pineapple flavor.
让它更有菠萝味。
I pour on my butter-and-brown-sugar mixture,
倒上黄油和红糖的混合物，
pineapple slices.
菠萝切片。
And I add pineapples and cherries.
我加入菠萝和樱桃。
All right.
好吧。
And then I pour in my cake batter.
然后倒入蛋糕面糊。
Then I put it in the oven.
然后我把它放进烤箱。
And it starts to leak.
它开始泄漏。
The pans that I'm using are removable like cheesecake pans.
我用的锅是可拆卸的，就像奶酪蛋糕锅一样。
Because of that, it has cracks at the bottom.
正因为如此，它的底部有裂缝。
So I'm gonna put 'em on a sheet tray
所以我要把它们放在托盘上
so it won't leak onto the bottom
这样就不会漏到锅底了
'cause then it will smell burned.
因为那样会有烧焦的味道。
Okay.
好吧。
JUSTICE: I want to show Duff and Valerie
法官:我想让达夫和瓦莱丽看看
that I'm one of the best pie makers.
我是最棒的糕点师之一
I got a guinea pig.
我有一只豚鼠。
And I am going to make mini peach pies.
我要做迷你桃派。
So I just have to connect a pie with a guinea pig.
所以我只需要把派和豚鼠联系起来。
I do not know how I'm going to do that.
我不知道该怎么做。
But I really want to make a pie.
但是我真的很想做一个派。
My dad has a peach tree at his work.
我爸爸工作的地方有一棵桃树。
So I make a lot of peach pies.
所以我做了很多桃子派。
To start my pie dough,
要做派面团，
I pulse sugar, flour, and salt, butter, and my shortening
我把糖、面粉、盐、黄油和起酥油搅匀
until it forms a nice, crumbly mixture.
直到它形成一个漂亮的，易碎的混合物。
I add a little bit of vinegar
加一点醋
because vinegar always makes your pie crust even flakier.
因为醋会让你的派皮更脆。
Hi, Justice. Hi.
嗨,正义。嗨。
I'm very excited about a pie
我对派很感兴趣
because in this entire competition,
因为在整个比赛中，
we have not had a pie yet.
我们还没吃馅饼呢。
I've been wanting to do a pie so badly.
我一直很想做个派。
I've just been waiting for the right opportunity.
我只是在等合适的机会。
And how are you gonna tie together
你们要怎么团结在一起
your guinea pig to a peach pie?
你的豚鼠要吃桃子派吗?
You'll see why.
你会明白的。
Oh, you want me to be surprised?
你想给我惊喜吗?
Mm-hmm. All right.
嗯哼。好吧。
Have at it, buddy.
来吧，伙计。
I think I'm really good at making up stories.
我觉得我很擅长编故事。
So...yeah.
所以…是的。
My dough is done.
我的面团做好了。
So I wrap it in plastic wrap.
所以我用保鲜膜把它包起来。
And I put it in the blast chiller to cool down
我把它放进冷却机里冷却
and for the butter to harden.
让黄油变硬。
I got the mini pig.
我有一只迷你猪。
So I have to use bacon
所以我必须用培根
because obviously, it's a pig.
因为很明显，它是一头猪。
I love bacon.
我喜欢培根。
It's my favorite part of the pig.
这是猪身上我最喜欢的部分。
[ Squeals ]
[尖叫]
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Today, I'm gonna bake maple-bacon doughnuts.
今天，我要烤枫糖培根甜甜圈。
[ Snorts ]
[哼一声]
I'm gonna make a baked doughnut instead of a fried doughnut.
我要做一个烤甜甜圈，而不是油炸甜甜圈。
I'm making a coconut cake base by adding sugar,
我要加糖做椰子蛋糕底，
butter, flour, eggs.
黄油，面粉，鸡蛋。
And then I'm adding coconut milk
然后加入椰奶
and a little bit of coconut cream.
再加一点椰子奶油。
I'm piping these three-quarters full
我把这些灌满四分之三
because I don't want these to be super thin
因为我不想让它们太薄
and turn into crackers.
然后变成饼干。
So I need to make sure they're filled.
所以我要确保它们都被填满了。
These doughnuts take 15 minutes to bake at 350 degrees.
这些甜甜圈需要在350度的温度下烤15分钟。
And they should be perfect.
它们应该是完美的。
Audra, make a chicken sound.
奥德拉，发出小鸡的声音。
[ Crows ]
[乌鸦]
I sound funny.
我听起来很有趣。
The animal I get is the Silky chicken,
我买的是丝滑鸡，
whose name is Einstein
他的名字叫爱因斯坦
because he has a really big, fluffy head.
因为他有一个毛茸茸的大脑袋。
No, please. I need four.
不,请。我需要四个。
I'm making a banana cake with vanilla frosting.
我在做香草糖霜香蕉蛋糕。
Okay. I have to do well in this round.
好吧。这一轮我必须好好表现。
My cake will represent my animal
我的蛋糕将代表我的动物
because on top of my cake will be two fondant chickens.
因为在我的蛋糕上面会放两只糖鸡。
I've never made a pet-inspired cake.
我从来没做过宠物蛋糕。
But we have a cat named Rory.
但是我们有一只叫罗里的猫。
She's turning 2 this year.
她今年2岁了。
A quarter.
四分之一。
To make my banana cake,
为了做香蕉蛋糕，
I combine butter, sugar, and some eggs.
我把黄油、糖和一些鸡蛋混合在一起。
That has to get creamed.
必须要加奶油。
In a measuring cup, I add my whole milk.
在量杯中加入全脂牛奶。
And then I add some banana flavor.
然后加入一些香蕉味。
I put about 1 1/2 teaspoons in, maybe a little more.
我放了大约1 1/2茶匙，也许再多一点。
I pour that into my butter mixture
我把它倒入黄油混合物中
and alternately with my flour mixture.
交替加入面粉混合物。
You always want to start and end on the flour
你总是想要开始和结束在面粉上
or else the consistency won't be right.
否则稠度就不对了。
Perfect yellow cake.
完美的黄色蛋糕。
I pour my batter into my floured cake pan.
我把面糊倒进撒了面粉的蛋糕锅里。
And...
和…
[ Crows ]
[乌鸦]
...Einstein is cheering me on.
…爱因斯坦在为我加油。
Yeah. You say it, Silky chicken.
是的。你说得对，丝鸡。
That'd be really hard to sleep with.
跟她上床真的很难。
One hour left. Pet Project Desserts.
还有一个小时。宠物项目甜点。
Now that my doughnuts are in the oven,
现在我的甜甜圈已经放进烤箱了，
I need to start on my glaze.
我得开始上釉了。
I'm taking my vanilla glaze and adding maple syrup,
我要用香草糖浆，加入枫糖浆，
whisking it together, and a little brown food coloring
搅拌均匀，再加一点棕色食用色素
so you know it's maple.
所以你知道它是枫木的。
Time to check the doughnuts.
是时候检查甜甜圈了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Puffed up a lot.
膨胀了很多。
They do not look like doughnuts.
它们看起来不像甜甜圈。
They look like muffins.
它们看起来像松饼。
I'm gonna try to poke a hole through them
我要试着在它们中间戳个洞
'cause they're really puffy.
因为它们真的很肿。
And I really hope this works
我真的希望这能奏效
'cause if it doesn't,
因为如果没有
then I'm gonna go home.
然后我就回家。
They're really messy. I'm so stressed right now.
它们真的很乱。我现在压力很大。
Attention, bakers.
注意,面包师。
No.
不。不。
Kids get to have pets.
孩子们可以养宠物。
But why don't pets get to have pets?
但是为什么宠物不能养宠物呢?
I don't have enough time for their shenanigans.
我没有足够的时间听他们胡闹。
So each of you has to make a mini pet
所以你们每个人都要做一个迷你宠物
for your Pet Project animal.
为你的宠物项目的动物。
What?
怎么啦？
COLE: I'm freaking out.
科尔:我吓坏了。
I have to worry about making these doughnuts perfect.
我得担心怎么把这些甜甜圈做得完美。
And I don't need another thing to do.
我不需要再做别的事了。
I'm not gonna have enough time to finish.
我没有足够的时间来完成。
DUFF: We're looking for an animal-inspired dessert
达夫:我们在寻找一种动物灵感的甜点
and one mini pet treat.
还有一份迷你宠物大餐。
Oh, gosh.
哦,天哪。
A mini pet for your Pet Project animal.
一个迷你宠物为您的宠物项目动物。
COLE: My doughnuts don't look like doughnuts.
科尔:我的甜甜圈看起来不像甜甜圈。
And now we have to make another thing.
现在我们要做另一个东西。
How's everybody doing?
大家都好吗?
COLE: Horrible.
科尔:可怕。
VALERIE: Cole, what's going on?
瓦莱丽:科尔，怎么了?
They're not doughnuts.
它们不是甜甜圈。
They're beautiful. They look beautiful.
他们是美丽的。它们看起来很漂亮。
And I'm seeing bacon, which screams "pig" to me.
我看到的是培根，对我来说就是猪。
So now you just have to make another little addition
现在你只需要再加一点
like -- what kind of pet would you like --
你喜欢什么样的宠物
What do you think your little pig would like as a pet?
你认为你的小猪作为宠物会喜欢什么?
-Hmm. -You can figure this out.
嗯。-你能搞定的。
It doesn't affect this dessert.
这不会影响这道甜点。
This is all looking good. -Okay.
这一切看起来都很好。-好的。
All right? Okay. [ Sniffles ]
好吧?好吧。[流鼻涕]
So just come up with a pet for your pet pig.
所以为你的宠物猪想一个宠物吧。
Okay.
好吧。
After talking with Valerie,
和瓦莱丽谈过之后，
I feel like I can manage
我觉得我能应付
to get something else in here.
把别的东西放进去。
But I just have to make these things simple.
但我必须把这些事情简单化。
I'm just gonna make little itty-bitty spiders
我要做一些小蜘蛛
because in "Charlotte's Web,"
因为在《夏洛特的网》里
the pig was best friends with a spider.
猪和蜘蛛是最好的朋友。
I want to resemble that on a plate.
我想把它放在盘子上。
I make a big ball, a little ball, and six legs,
我做了一个大球，一个小球和六条腿，
and stick it all together by using water.
然后用水把它们粘在一起。
I still have to finish these doughnuts.
我还得把这些甜甜圈吃完。
I do not have a lot of time.
我的时间不多了。
How's it going, bakers?
最近怎么样，面包师们?
Good.
好。
Now that I have my pie crust in the blast chiller,
现在我把派皮放进了冷冻机，
I'm gonna start on making my filling.
我要开始做馅料了。
I peel the skin off the peaches 'cause it's not the best to eat.
我把桃子的皮剥了，因为它不好吃。
You want the peaches to shine
你想要桃子发光
because they're the main part of this dish.
因为它们是这道菜的主要部分。
I do not want it to be that sweet.
我可不想过得那么甜蜜。
So I add some lemon juice and nutmeg
加一些柠檬汁和肉豆蔻
because I want a little bit of spice in there as well.
因为我想在里面放一点香料。
45 minutes left, bakers.
还有45分钟，面包师们。
DUFF: Justice better get those in the oven.
达夫:法官最好把它们放进烤箱里。
If not, we're gonna get raw fruit and raw dough.
如果没有，我们就吃生水果和生面团。
Oh, I don't like raw dough in my pie. No.
哦，我不喜欢生面团做派。不。
I roll my dough out.
我把面团擀出来。
And I plop that into the pie tin.
然后把它放进烤盘里。
And I strain out the peaches.
我把桃子滤出来。
I don't want too much liquid in there
我不希望里面有太多液体
or else it'll turn into peach soup.
否则就会变成桃子汤。
Next, I cut some nice straight lattices
接下来，我切一些漂亮的直格
and weave it on top of the pie.
把它织在派上。
It'll make your pie look super good.
它会让你的派看起来超级好吃。
And it's an area so that air gets out.
这是一个让空气流出的区域。
Doesn't it look good?
看起来不错吧?
There's under 40 minutes left.
还剩不到40分钟。
I finally get my pies in the oven.
我终于把派放进烤箱了。
Ooh.
哦。
I hope that they'll bake in time.
我希望它们能及时烤熟。
I'm gonna work on my chocolate shells.
我要去做巧克力壳了。
The way I'm going to make my cake
我要做蛋糕的方法
look more like a turtle
看起来更像一只乌龟
is I'm going to create a chocolate shell
我要做一个巧克力壳吗
that will hold my cake and buttercream.
可以装下我的蛋糕和奶油。
So I melt some brown candy melts in the microwave,
所以我在微波炉里融化了一些棕色的糖果，
pour it over my sphere molds kind of thick.
把它倒在我的球形模具上，稍微厚一点。
This is a bit of a messy process,
这个过程有点混乱，
and you have to work fast.
而且你必须动作快。
Come on.
来吧。
I just want all that excess chocolate to drip off.
我只想让多余的巧克力都掉下来。
I left that to cool upside-down. I hope that it turns out good.
我让它倒着凉了。我希望结果会很好。
Cool.
酷。
KANIYAH: Hoo!
KANIYAH:呼! !
I pull my cakes out the oven and let them rest on my rack.
我把蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来，放在架子上。
Ice cream.
冰淇淋。
Time to make some ice cream.
是时候做冰淇淋了。
Crème anglaise.
英式奶油。
We'll get started on my crème anglaise/ice-cream base,
我们开始做奶油蛋糕/冰淇淋底，
crème anglaise/ice-cream base.
奶油蛋糕/冰淇淋底。
I add a lot of pineapple juice,
我会加很多菠萝汁，
get that going over the stove.
把它放到炉子上烤。
And while that's going,
在这个过程中，
I mix egg yolks and sugar
我把蛋黄和糖混合在一起
till it becomes slightly pale.
直到它变得有点苍白。
Pour a little bit of my cream mixture over my yolks
在蛋黄上倒一点奶油混合物
and start whisking so it won't cook my eggs.
开始搅拌，这样鸡蛋就不会煮熟了。
I don't want curdled ice cream.
我不想要凝固的冰淇淋。
Then I pour it into the rest
然后把它倒进去
and get my ice-cream base going in the ice-cream maker.
把我的冰淇淋底放进冰淇淋机。
Making ice cream is fun.
做冰淇淋很有趣。
So what are you gonna do for your chicken cake?
你准备怎么做你的鸡肉蛋糕?
I'm going to shape some fondant
我要捏一些软糖
to make them look like chickens.
让他们看起来像鸡。
Oh.
哦。
Okay. Let's start on my chickens.
好吧。让我们从我的鸡开始。
AUDRA: For my decoration,
为了我的装饰，
I get a big chunk of fondant.
我得到一大块软糖。
And I form it into the chicken body...
我把它做成鸡的身体……
Let's cut out some wings.
我们剪一些翅膀吧。
...and then some wings and then a head.
…然后是翅膀，然后是头。
Head for you.
朝你那边去。
One of them is a little Einstein.
其中一个是小爱因斯坦。
And then one is Einstein's soul mate, Bella.
还有一个是爱因斯坦的灵魂伴侣，贝拉。
Such cute little chickens.
这么可爱的小鸡。
Bella and Einstein.
贝拉和爱因斯坦。
30 minutes left, bakers. You got 30 minutes.
还有30分钟，面包师们。你有30分钟。
30 minutes.
30分钟。
It feels like they're taking forever.
感觉他们花了很长时间。
Oh, no. Their heads are falling off.
哦,不。他们的头都掉下来了。
And I'm supposed to make a mini pet.
我要做一个迷你宠物。
I totally brain fart.
我完全用脑子放屁。
I don't know what to do for my mini pet at all.
我根本不知道该为我的小宠物做些什么。
This twist is horrible.
这个转折太可怕了。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝。
I have to get my stuff done.
我得把我的东西做完。
JUSTICE: Time is counting down.
法官:时间不多了。
Luckily, I have some leftover ingredients
幸运的是，我还有一些剩余的食材
that I can just make a little animal out of.
我可以用它做个小动物
I'm making little guinea pig babies
我在做豚鼠宝宝
out of pie crust and some peaches.
没有派皮和桃子了。
I'm fitting as much as I can inside the little dough pocket
我尽量往面团口袋里塞东西
and then rolling it up into a ball.
然后把它卷成一个球。
And then I deep-fry that.
然后我油炸它。
Justice is at the fryer.
正义在炸锅旁。
-Hmm. -What's he up to?
嗯。他在干什么?
He's frying something, getting creative.
他在炒菜，很有创意。
It's basically just a doughnut hole
基本上就是一个甜甜圈洞
that I'm going to decorate as a little baby guinea pig.
我要把它装饰成一只小豚鼠。
I smell bacon.
我闻到了培根的味道。
[ Squeals ]
[尖叫]
Oh, come on, Cole.
得了吧，科尔。
-Not the little piggy. -He is angry.
-不是那只小猪。-他生气了。
Oh, poor piggy.
哦，可怜的小猪。
Sorry, piggy. I want to win.
对不起,小猪。我想赢。
I want me some bacon.
我想要一些熏肉。
This bacon is thick.
这培根很厚。
So I need to make sure that it's cooked
所以我要确保它已经煮熟了
because last time I made it,
因为上次我做的时候
Duff said it was raw.
达夫说那是生的。
I do not want to be eliminated from raw bacon
我可不想被生培根淘汰
'cause that's embarrassing.
因为那太尴尬了。
Duff, when are you gonna get the waffle tattoo?
达夫，你打算什么时候纹华夫饼?
If you guys bring home the gold,
如果你们能拿回金牌，
I will get a waffle tattoo.
我要纹个华夫饼纹身。
-Don't you worry. -Are you bluffing?
-别担心。-你在虚张声势吗?
Hold on.
等一等。
[ Line ringing ]
[线路振铃]
Hey. Is this celebrity chef Michael Voltaggio?
嘿。这是名厨Michael Voltaggio吗?
-Yes. -Listen.
-是的。着。
These kids are giving me a hard time.
这些孩子让我很难受。
I have to go get a waffle tattoo.
我得去纹个华夫饼。
I promised them last week I'd get it done.
我上周答应过他们会完成的。
They are not letting me off the hook with this thing.
他们不会放过我这件事的。
MICHAEL: I'm gonna book you an appointment right now.
迈克尔:我现在就给你预约。
So after the show, I'll meet you there?
演出结束后，我们在那见?
Absolutely. I'll be there. I'll be waiting for you.
绝对的。我会去的。我会等你的。
I'm going to get my waffle.
我去拿我的华夫饼。
Sure thing, Duff.
当然，达夫。
I'm gonna start on pineapple-ring cookies.
我要开始做菠萝圈饼干了。
For the twist,
为了扭转，
I've just incorporated sugar-cookie kitty cat
我刚刚加入了糖饼干小猫
because it's like a little friend for the bunny.
因为它就像是兔子的小朋友。
Kitty cat and a bunny, they're both fluffy.
小猫和兔子，它们都是毛茸茸的。
I just need to make a cookie.
我只需要做块饼干。
I'm making sugar cookies again
我又在做糖饼干了
because last week,
因为上周，
I had some "issues" with my cookie.
我的饼干出了点问题。
This time, I'm adding pineapple
这次，我要加菠萝
to add a little bit more flavor.
为了增加一点味道。
Duff said my cookie tasted like a fortune cookie.
达夫说我的饼干尝起来像幸运饼干。
So I'm trying to remake that cookie
所以我试着重做那块饼干
and make it taste better.
让它的味道更好。
Kaniyah's making sugar cookies again.
Kaniyah又在做糖饼干了。
Hmm.
嗯。
She wants to prove her point, like, "I can do this."
她想证明自己的观点，比如"我能行"
-Yeah. -"And let me show you."
-是的。-"让我示范给你看。"
Yeah.
是的。
I want victory from last week's cookies.
我要从上周的饼干中获得胜利。
20 minutes, bakers.
二十分钟，面包师们。
Oh, God, 20 minutes.
天啊，20分钟。
I have no idea what I'm going to do for my mini pet.
我不知道该为我的小宠物做些什么。
Okay. They look good.
好吧。它们看起来不错。
I get my cakes out of the oven.
我把蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来。
They smell so banana-y.
它们闻起来有股香蕉味。
I want them to be cool so my icing
我想让它们变凉，这样我的糖霜
doesn't get all melty, melty and go pbbt!
不会变成一团乱麻，一团乱麻!
Oh.
哦。
So I throw them in the blast chiller
所以我把它们扔进了冷冻机
and start my buttercream.
开始我的奶油。
I'm going to make my vanilla frosting green
我要把香草糖霜做成绿色
to look like grass for the chickens
看起来像鸡吃的草
to be laying in.
躺在家里。
Oh, God. What did I do?
哦,上帝。我做了什么?
My buttercream looks a little broken.
我的奶油看起来有点坏了。
Ooh, it's not looking the best.
哦，看起来不太好。
I definitely do not have enough time
我绝对没有足够的时间
to make another buttercream.
做另一种奶油。
I'll just have to go with it.
我只能跟着它走了。
15 minutes, bakers.
15分钟，面包师们。
[ Timer rings ] -Ooh, my cake's done.
(计时器响了)-哦，我的蛋糕做好了。
I get my cake out of the oven.
我把蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来。
Ah, it came out perfectly.
啊，结果很完美。
And it looks perfect.
看起来很完美。
I go to check on my chocolate shells.
我去检查我的巧克力壳。
Is this cool? Yeah. That's cool.
这酷吗?是的。那很酷。
Ah.
啊。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天哪。
They're just falling apart.
它们正在分崩离析。
Oh, gosh. I messed that up.
哦,天哪。我搞砸了。
Ah. This is the sole foundation
啊。这是唯一的基础
of what I'm making today.
我今天所做的
Ew.
电子战。
Come on.
来吧。
I've got to figure this out.
我得想个办法。
I've got to serve something to the judges.
我得给评委们上点东西。
This is a disaster.
这是一场灾难。
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary cake and ice cream turn into
解说员:普通的蛋糕和冰淇淋变成
adorable kitten treats right after this.
可爱的小猫在这之后。
How to make ice cream kittens --
如何制作冰淇淋小猫
Gather together pound cake,
聚在一起捣饼，
round cookie cutter,
圆形饼干切割机，
parchment cups,
羊皮纸杯,
ice cream and scoop,
冰淇淋和勺子，
butterscotch chips,
奶油糖果的芯片,
chocolate sprinkles,
巧克力屑,
and black decorating icing.
还有黑色的装饰糖霜。
Slice your pound cake.
切你的磅蛋糕。
Cut out mini cake rounds.
切出小蛋糕。
Put cake in the parchment.
把蛋糕放在羊皮纸上。
Scoop ice cream to top the cake.
用勺子把冰淇淋放在蛋糕上。
Use butterscotch, frosting, and sprinkles
使用奶油糖、糖霜和糖屑
to decorate the kitten.
装饰小猫。
And make a whole litter of desserts.
然后做一大堆甜点。
For more treats like this,
想要更多这样的美食，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
15 minutes left, bakers.
还有15分钟，面包师们。
DUFF: Pet Project Desserts.
DUFF:宠物项目甜点。
Link that dessert to your animal however you like.
把甜点和你喜欢的动物联系起来。
AIDAN: No, my little turtle shells.
艾丹:不，我的小龟壳。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
No.
不。
Aidan is pulling out his chocolate turtle shells.
艾登正在拿出他的巧克力龟壳。
And they are breaking.
它们正在断裂。
Chocolate is one of the most difficult things to work with.
巧克力是最难处理的东西之一。
Oh, poor Aidan.
可怜的艾登。
I don't think I let this cool long enough.
我觉得我还没冷静多久。
I definitely should've blast chilled my chocolate.
我真该把巧克力冰镇一下。
I'm really worried about this.
我真的很担心。
I'm just gonna have to do that again.
我只能再来一次了。
I didn't let it cool long enough.
我没让它冷却太久。
I just need to restart them.
我只需要重新启动它们。
So I have to melt some more candy melts.
所以我得再融化一些糖果。
All right. This one better turn out right.
好吧。这个最好是正确的。
I'm gonna take extra care when making these.
我做的时候会格外小心的。
And this time,
这一次，
I'm going to put them straight in the blast chiller
我要把它们直接放进冷风机里
so they're just nice and hard.
所以它们又好又硬。
And they won't crumble
它们不会碎
as I take them out of the molds.
当我把它们从模具里拿出来的时候
If these chocolate shells don't come out,
如果这些巧克力壳不出来，
I'm in serious trouble.
我有大麻烦了。
JUSTICE: I run to check on my pies.
法官:我跑去检查我的馅饼。
And they're not done yet.
他们还没有完成。
This is bad.
这很糟糕。
I can't serve this to Duff and Valerie.
我不能把这个端给达夫和瓦莱丽。
So I just have to wait to the last minute to take them out.
所以我只能等到最后一刻才把它们取出来。
It's a little bit scary.
这有点吓人。
But I need to now decorate my little peach balls
现在我要装饰一下我的小蜜桃球了
and make them look like guinea pigs.
让他们看起来像小白鼠。
I found these little googly eyes.
我发现了这些小眼睛。
So I'm just gonna use those and stick them on with butter.
我要用这些，然后涂上黄油。
KANIYAH: It's time for me to turn
是时候该轮到我了
my pineapple upside-down cake upside down.
我的菠萝倒置蛋糕。
I flip them onto the plate.
我把它们翻转到盘子里。
Beautiful! They're all beautiful.
漂亮!他们都很漂亮。
Whoa.
哇。
I might just eat one.
我可能只吃一个。
Now I just need to get my cookies done.
现在我只需要把饼干做好。
Are these done?
这些都做好了吗?
Please tell me that they're done.
请告诉我他们结束了。
Take them out the oven.
把它们从烤箱里拿出来。
And they're just the way I like them.
它们就是我喜欢的样子。
I go grab some candy eyeballs
我去拿些眼球糖
and little chocolate chips to put for the mouth.
还有一点巧克力片放进嘴里。
These cookies are way better than last week's.
这些饼干比上周的好吃多了。
AIDAN: I'm going to put cake and buttercream
艾丹:我要放蛋糕和奶油
inside my chocolate shell.
在我的巧克力壳里。
Buttercream.
奶油乳酪。
I'm making my tried-and-true Swiss meringue buttercream.
我要做久经考验的瑞士蛋白派奶油。
I heat up my egg whites and sugar.
我把蛋白和糖加热。
And I whip that into a meringue.
然后搅拌成蛋白派。
Mm, yummy.
嗯,好吃。
Then you add a whole pound of butter.
然后加入一整磅黄油。
Whole pound, that's what makes it yummy.
一整磅，这才是美味所在。
I'm adding green to decorate the turtles.
我在用绿色装饰海龟。
I don't have time to color this any deeper.
我没有时间给它涂更深的颜色了。
And for this twist,
为了这个转折，
I want to make a fish out of orange-colored buttercream
我想用橙色的奶油做一条鱼
to go with my turtle.
和我的乌龟一起去。
It's gonna be tight.
会很紧的。
5 minutes, bakers.
5分钟，面包师们。
COLE: My doughnuts are cooled.
科尔:我的甜甜圈已经凉了。
And I dunk them in the maple glaze
我把它们浸在枫糖浆里
and sprinkle some good bacon on there.
再在上面撒点培根。
These doughnuts look really, really good.
这些甜甜圈看起来真的很好吃。
But I don't have time to eat any.
但是我没有时间吃。
I'm grabbing my pies out of the oven.
我要把派从烤箱里拿出来。
Please let them be done.
请让他们完成吧。
Yes! They have a nice, crispy top shell
是的!它们的顶壳很漂亮，很脆
that does not seem gushy.
这似乎并不矫情。
I just had enough time.
我只是有足够的时间。
But now it's a mad rush to get everything on the plate.
但现在，人们疯狂地把所有的东西都放在盘子里。
So, on my cake, I'm going to include this egg
所以，在我的蛋糕上，我要加入这个鸡蛋
next to these little love birds
在这些小情侣旁边
because, well, she laid an egg.
因为她下了个蛋。
I'm just running out of time.
我快没时间了。
So I choose fondant for my mini pet egg
所以我为我的迷你宠物蛋选择了软糖
because I really can't think of anything else.
因为我真的想不出别的了。
And I'll just see how it works out.
我来看看结果如何。
AIDAN: I take my shells out of the blast chiller.
艾丹:我把炮弹从冷冻机里拿出来。
If these don't turn out, that's it.
如果这些结果不出来，那就完了。
I loosen out the sides.
我把两边弄松。
I pull it out very delicately.
我小心翼翼地把它拔了出来。
Yes!
是的!
Your chocolate looks really good.
你的巧克力看起来真好吃。
I know. I'm so glad it came out.
我知道。我很高兴它出来了。
I was really worried about time.
我真的很担心时间。
I need to hurry and get these turtles assembled.
我得赶紧把这些乌龟组装起来。
Turtles, assemble.
海龟、组装。
I will make it to the semifinals.
我会进入半决赛的。
I fill up my chocolate shell with cake and buttercream
我在巧克力壳里塞满了蛋糕和奶油
and then pipe out little arms
然后伸出小胳膊
and his head and his tail.
还有他的头和尾巴。
To make my fish, I pipe a little head,
为了做我的鱼，我用管子管一个小脑袋，
tail and put on some googly eyes.
尾巴，戴上一双大眼睛。
30 seconds, bakers.
30秒，面包师们。
I don't know if I can finish.
我不知道我能不能完成。
You can, Aidan. You can do it.
你可以的，艾登。你能做到的。
My fish look a little weird.
我的鱼看起来有点怪。
Some of them are kind of guh.
有些是废话。
They're swimming in a little pond.
他们在一个小池塘里游泳。
BOTH: 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
都是，5,4,3,2,1。
DUFF: Hands up.
达夫:举起手来。
-Whoo! -All right.
-哇!-好的。
Good job, guys.
干得好，伙计们。
AIDAN: My finished plates are a little sloppy.
艾丹:我的成品盘子有点粗糙。
So I hope it tastes good.
所以我希望它尝起来不错。
All right, Duff, are you ready for Pet Project Desserts?
好了，达夫，准备好《宠物甜点计划》了吗?
[ Crows ]
[乌鸦]
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I'll take that as a yes.
我就当你同意了。
Yes.
是的。
Justice.
正义。
[ Crows ]
[乌鸦]
Exactly.
完全正确。
Justice, tell us what animal you got
法官，告诉我们你有什么动物
and what you made for us.
还有你为我们做的一切。
I got a guinea pig. And I made for you a peach pie
我有一只豚鼠。我给你做了个桃子派
with a guinea pig with a tiny little peach inside,
一只豚鼠，里面有一个小桃子，
kind of like a doughnut hole
有点像甜甜圈洞
but just like a fried-peach-goodness ball.
但就像一个油炸的桃子球。
-But this is your pet. -Yeah.
-但这是你的宠物。-是的。
-And it's a... -Baby guinea pig.
-这是一个…-小豚鼠。
Baby guinea pig.
小豚鼠。
How do you relate a peach pie to a guinea pig?
你怎么把桃子派和豚鼠联系起来?
So, once upon a time,
所以，从前，
a mean hawk came and took the guinea pig into the air.
一只卑鄙的鹰飞来，把豚鼠带到空中。
But then it dropped it. And it fell into a tree.
但后来它放弃了。它掉到一棵树上了。
And it told all the other little guinea pigs.
它告诉了所有其他的小豚鼠。
And they all climbed up in the tree
他们都爬上了树
and ate all the peaches.
吃光了所有的桃子。
Ever since then, they love peaches.
从那时起，他们就爱上了桃子。
Please, please, please say they'll like it.
拜托，拜托，拜托说他们会喜欢的。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I buy it.
我买了。
That -- Beautiful story.
那——美丽的故事。
Beautiful. All right.
美丽。好吧。
Thank God.
感谢上帝。
-Ooh. -Nice.
-哦。-。
I'm afraid to eat the mini pet.
我害怕吃这个迷你宠物。
I'm not.
我不是。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Huh.
嗯。
Okay. Um, it's a good doughnut.
好吧。嗯，这是一个很好的甜甜圈。
But it's a little gummy.
但是有点黏。
And it got a little oily.
有点油了。
Duff's right. The oil could have been a little bit hotter.
达夫是对的。油可以再热一点。
And that way, the oil doesn't soak all the way into it.
这样，油就不会完全浸透进去。
But I love the little surprise of peach.
但我喜欢桃子的小惊喜。
Your mini pet is very, very tasty.
你的迷你宠物非常非常好吃。
I'm excited about this pie. I can't wait.
我对这个派很兴奋。我都等不及了。
I love that you made a pie 'cause we haven't had a pie
我喜欢你做的派，因为我们还没吃过派
since this whole competition started.
自从这场比赛开始。
You're a pioneer.
你是先锋。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
That's right. I am a pioneer.
这是正确的。我是一个先锋。
And I'm looking at it.
我看着它。
And I was, like, you know, "I hope the bottom's baked."
然后我就说"我希望锅底烤好了"
And it totally is, man. That looks awesome.
确实是这样，伙计。看起来棒极了。
Ah, you even gave us latticework.
啊，你甚至给了我们格子作业。
But this lattice is a little -- it's a little messy.
但是这个晶格有点，有点乱。
I actually think this is really beautiful latticework.
我觉得这个格子真的很漂亮。
It's better than my latticework. I got to tell you.
比我的格子画好多了。我得告诉你。
This is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
I love it.
我喜欢它。
This crust is just so buttery and so flaky.
这饼皮太软太脆了。
-Thank you. -A lot of times, I think,
-谢谢。-很多时候，我想，
with peaches, people have a tendency
对于桃子，人们有一种倾向
to over-sugar them. And you didn't.
不要加太多的糖。但你没有。
And you really got a nice peach flavor.
桃子的味道真的很不错。
You know, this is a good peach pie.
你知道吗，这桃子派很好吃。
You're really stepping it up. You want to win this?
你真的进步了。你想赢吗?
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Great job, Justice.
干得好，法官。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
I'm so impressed with this peach pie.
我对这个桃子派印象深刻。
What?
怎么啦？
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Cole, what animal did you get?
科尔，你买了什么动物?
I got the mini pig.
我有一只迷你猪。
The first thing I thought of was bacon.
我首先想到的是培根。
And then I thought doughnuts.
然后我想到了甜甜圈。
And why not put some maple in there?
为什么不放点枫糖进去呢?
And maple bacon works.
还有枫糖培根。
Then for my mini pet,
然后是我的小宠物，
I made little baby spiders out of gum paste
我用口香糖糊做了小蜘蛛
'cause in "Charlotte's Web,"
因为在《夏洛特的网》里
the pig and the spider were, like, best friends.
猪和蜘蛛是最好的朋友。
Perfect.
完美的。
Your inspiration was this adorable little mini pig.
你的灵感来自这只可爱的迷你小猪。
And you decided to make bacon.
你决定做培根。
Yes.
是的。
Respect. Good choice.
尊重。不错的选择。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
-Like a true chef. -Mm-hmm.
就像一个真正的厨师。-嗯。
But this is, like, the third time you've made bacon.
但这都是你第三次做培根了。
And I think this might be the first time
我想这可能是第一次
you've done it right.
你做得对。
Nothing congealed. It looks like you rendered
没有凝固的。看起来像是渲染过的
all that bacon fat out.
所有的熏肉都长胖了。
Good job. -Thank you.
好工作。-谢谢。
And I would've liked to --
我本想——
for the spider to have been more edible.
因为蜘蛛更容易食用。
-Yeah. -But what's wrong
-是的。-怎么了?
with a doughnut covered in bacon?
还有一个裹着培根的甜甜圈?
Absolutely nothing.
绝对没有。
Let's give it a whirl.
让我们试一试。
They're about to taste my bacon doughnut.
他们要尝尝我的培根甜甜圈了。
And I just really hope it's not too sweet
我只希望这不会太甜蜜
'cause I haven't tried it yet.
因为我还没试过。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
-Great sweet and salty. -Mm-hmm.
-甜咸俱佳。-嗯。
You know, real nice.
你知道，真的很好。
Yes! [ Laughs ]
是的![笑]
I love the bacon and the maple together.
我喜欢培根和枫树一起吃。
I love the glaze. It's delicious.
我喜欢这种釉。它是美味的。
It is -- it is very dense, though.
不过，它的密度非常大。
I don't know that I'd call it a doughnut.
我不知道我会叫它甜甜圈。
More like pound cake.
更像是磅蛋糕。
This is, like, 14 pounds.
这大概有14磅重。
It doesn't scream doughnut to me.
我不觉得这是甜甜圈。
But you didn't have to make a doughnut.
但你没必要做甜甜圈。
You just made something really yummy
你刚刚做了很好吃的东西
and sweet and bacon-y.
甜甜的，培根味的。
Good job. -Thank you.
好工作。-谢谢。
Now I'm gonna pick all the bacon off.
现在我要把培根都摘下来。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
-How's it going, Aidan? -Good.
-怎么样，艾登?改善情况。
What animal did you get?
你买了什么动物?
I got the turtle.
我抓到乌龟了。
Hopefully, you can tell.
希望你能分辨出来。
Well, at the end of our street,
在这条街的尽头，
there is a big pond.
有一个大池塘。
And when you start to throw bread in,
当你开始往里面扔面包时，
tons and tons of turtles just come.
一吨又一吨的乌龟来了。
And sometimes even fish come.
有时甚至鱼也会来。
They're playing, happy turtle buddies.
他们在玩耍，快乐的海龟伙伴。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I made a vanilla cake with a vanilla buttercream
我用香草奶油做了一个香草蛋糕
inside of a chocolate shell.
在巧克力壳里。
And there's a little buttercream fish.
还有一条奶油鱼。
It looks like a turtle and a goldfish friend.
它看起来像一只乌龟和一只金鱼朋友。
I like that you have his four legs,
我喜欢你有他四条腿，
his tail, and his head.
他的尾巴，还有他的头。
You have all of the blue here.
所有的蓝色都在这里。
So it shows that it's water.
这表明它是水。
Yours looks a little different.
你的看起来有点不同。
Aidan, I'm gonna be honest.
艾登，我实话实说。
I think your turtle got a little messy.
我觉得你的乌龟有点脏。
On your chocolate shell,
在你的巧克力外壳上，
I got a lot of green buttercream
我有很多绿色的奶油
that I don't think you meant to be there.
我觉得你不是故意去的
This foot isn't even attached.
这只脚甚至都没有固定。
Looks like you were really in a hurry.
看起来你真的很着急。
-I was. -Right? You were.
我是。-对吗?你是。
You were, and I can tell.
是的，我看得出来。
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
It's not my best work.
这不是我最好的作品。
But it's very, very far from being my worst.
但这远不是我最糟糕的。
Let's cut into this gorgeous little turtle. Yeah.
我们切开这只漂亮的小乌龟。是的。
Okay.
好吧。
No! You killed the turtle.
不!你杀了乌龟。
That's really fun.
那真的很有趣。
Look at that inside.
看看里面。
I love the taste of your buttercream,
我喜欢你的奶油的味道，
not too sweet.
不太甜。
It doesn't overpower the cake.
它不会盖过蛋糕。
My favorite recipe.
我最喜欢的食谱。
Very moist cake.
非常湿润的蛋糕。
And the chocolate with it, it's really --
还有配巧克力的，真的
it's a really great little dessert.
这是一道很棒的小甜点。
There's nothing negative to say about what you made.
你的作品没有什么不好的。
You made an awesome buttercream. You made awesome cake.
你做的奶油太棒了。你做的蛋糕棒极了。
And you got a beautiful shell.
你得到了一个漂亮的外壳。
But you got vanilla, vanilla, and chocolate.
但你有香草，香草和巧克力。
I wish you would dig a little deeper
我希望你能再深入一点
and, like, do some cooler flavors
再来点更酷的口味
just to make it a little more exciting.
只是为了让它更刺激一点。
You know, Val loves lemon.
你知道，瓦尔喜欢柠檬。
Put some lemon in there.
放一些柠檬进去。
You're in the final five.
你进入最后五名了。
You have to really step it up not just a notch,
你必须真正提高，不仅仅是一个档次，
but a bunch of notches. We know now.
而是一堆缺口。我们现在知道了。
You can make a perfect vanilla cake
你可以做一个完美的香草蛋糕
and a perfect buttercream.
还有完美的奶油。
Now what else can you do?
现在你还能做什么?
I'm really worried because I don't know
我真的很担心，因为我不知道
where I stand with my turtle cake.
我和我的海龟蛋糕站在一起。
Bye. -See you.
再见。你查查。
And I want to get to the semifinal so badly.
我非常想进入半决赛。
I do not want to end my journey here.
我不想在这里结束我的旅程。
Pet Project Desserts, Duff.
宠物项目甜点，达夫。
[ Barks ]
[吠叫]
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
[ Meows ]
[喵喵][喵喵]
You ready for Kaniyah?
你准备好见卡尼亚了吗?
[ Purring ] Aw.
(呼噜声)啊。
Kaniyah?
Kaniyah吗?
Here she comes.
她来了。
You are too funny.
你太有趣了。
Tell us what animal you got
告诉我们你养了什么动物
and how it inspired your dessert.
还有它是如何启发你做甜点的。
I got a rabbit.
我有一只兔子。
And I made a pineapple upside-down cake
我还做了个菠萝倒立蛋糕
because I went to a petting zoo.
因为我去了宠物动物园。
And I saw rabbits eating pineapples.
我还看到兔子吃菠萝。
Rabbits eat pineapple?
兔子吃菠萝?
Look it up.
查一下。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
You know what? I'm gonna.
你知道吗?我要。
Good because they do.
很好，因为他们知道。
And who's his little pet?
谁是他的小宠物?
Little playful baby kitten.
顽皮的小猫。
Okay.
好吧。
[ Meows ]
[喵喵叫]
I think that is one gorgeous pineapple upside-down cake.
我觉得这是一个漂亮的菠萝倒立蛋糕。
I agree with you.
我同意你的看法。
Your pineapple got nice and caramelized.
你的菠萝变焦糖了。
This dark color looks so good.
这个深色看起来很不错。
You did a really nice job on this.
你做得很好。
Uh, what's going on in this -- What is this nonsense here?
这是怎么回事这是什么鬼东西?
-Pineapple ice cream. -Pineapple ice cream?
菠萝冰淇淋。菠萝冰淇淋?
Yes. You made us a cake
是的。你给我们做了个蛋糕
and a cookie and ice cream
还有饼干和冰淇淋
in just 90 minutes?
仅仅90分钟?
That's impressive. -Yes, it is.
这是令人印象深刻。-是的。
And I'm tired of talking about it.
我不想再提了。
I want to eat it. -Okay.
我想吃它。-好的。
All right.
好吧。
Mmm.
嗯。
Eat it.
吃它。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
This is -- this is bad. You made a big mistake.
这太糟糕了。你犯了个大错误。
What'd I do?
我做了什么?
You made a pineapple upside-down cake
你做了个菠萝倒立蛋糕
that's better than mine.
这比我的好。
It's so good.
太好吃了。
This is really good.
这真的很好。
It's out of this world.
这真是太棒了。
It's delicious.
它是美味的。
It is so moist.
天气太潮湿了。
Crust is so good.
面包皮太好吃了。
The caramelization all around the edges,
边缘的焦糖化，
it's crazy how good it is.
太好吃了。
This is the best pineapple upside-down cake I've ever had.
这是我吃过的最好吃的菠萝倒立蛋糕。
I got to tell you, though. You know what I have to say
不过我得告诉你。你知道我要说什么
about that cookie?
那块饼干呢?
[ Hisses ]
[嘶嘶声]
It is not baked all the way.
它不是一直烤的。
-Yeah. -You can really taste the flour.
-是的。你真的能尝到面粉的味道。
It just needed a good five more minutes in the oven.
在烤箱里再烤五分钟就好了。
Okay.
好吧。
Okay, ice cream.
好的，冰淇淋。
I'm not tasting the pineapple in the ice cream.
我才不要尝冰淇淋里的菠萝。
-It's very subtle. -But it's real good.
-非常微妙。-但真的很好吃。
But I don't care. It's extra credit.
但我不在乎。这是额外的学分。
All I want to do is put my face
我只想把我的脸
into that pineapple upside-down cake.
倒进菠萝蛋糕里。
Hope that cake is good enough to keep me in this competition.
希望蛋糕足够好，能让我继续参加比赛。
-Yeah. I hope so too. -I hope so too.
-是的。我也希望如此。-我也希望如此。
Thanks.
谢谢。
You're welcome.
不客气
-I don't want to stop eating it. -I know. I'm not gonna.
我不想停止吃它。-我知道。我不会的。
Audra?
Audra吗?
-Hello.
-你好。-你好。
-How's it going, Audra? -Good.
-最近怎么样，奥德拉?改善情况。
That's good. Okay.
这很好。好吧。
What animal did you get?
你买了什么动物?
I got the Silky chicken.
我买了丝滑鸡。
Did you hear him cheering me on?
你听到他为我加油了吗?
[ Crows ]
[乌鸦]
Yeah. You say it, Silky chicken.
是的。你说得对，丝鸡。
Do you have a Silky chicken impersonation?
你们有模仿丝滑鸡的节目吗?
Cluck, cluck.
咯咯叫,咯咯叫。咯咯叫,咯咯叫。
Cluck. [ Laughter ]
咯咯叫。[笑声]
What dessert did you make?
你做了什么甜点?
I made a banana cake that has a vanilla frosting.
我做了一个香草糖霜的香蕉蛋糕。
And it's topped with fondant chickies.
上面还放了一层糖饼干。
So how does this relate to the Silky chicken?
那么这和丝滑鸡有什么关系呢?
Once upon a time, there was the Silky chicken.
很久很久以前，有一只丝鸡。
And he had met his soul mate.
他遇到了他的灵魂伴侣。
But he was captured and put in a farm.
但他被抓了起来，关进了一个农场。
All of the other animals
所有其他的动物
at the farm helped break the little chicken out
在农场帮忙把小鸡弄出来
so that he could find his soul mate.
这样他就能找到他的灵魂伴侣。
And that is them together.
这是它们在一起。
And then they have an egg next to them.
然后它们旁边有一个蛋。
Is the egg their little pet?
蛋是他们的小宠物吗?
It's also their child.
这也是他们的孩子。
It's their mini pet and their child.
这是他们的迷你宠物，也是他们的孩子。
Yes. At the same time? A twofer.
是的。同时?一个活动双管齐下。
-Yes. -Okay.
-是的。-好的。
I'd be amazed
我会很惊讶的
if that egg came out of that chicken.
如果鸡蛋是从鸡里出来的。
-[ Laughs ] -Yeah.
-[笑]-是的。
The egg is as big as the chicken.
鸡蛋和鸡一样大。
Right?
对吧?
The cake looks really well done.
蛋糕看起来做得很好。
I love the color of the grass. I love that you chose
我喜欢草的颜色。我喜欢你的选择
a tip that made it look like it's a really comfy nest.
这个小窍门让它看起来像一个非常舒适的巢穴。
The chickens are cute.
小鸡很可爱。
But, you know, I just -- I wish there was
但是，你知道，我只是，我希望有
a little more detail on here, maybe some beaks or eyes.
这里有更多的细节，可能是一些喙或眼睛。
-Yeah. -And let's see how it tastes.
-是的。-让我们看看味道如何。
Yeah.
是的。
Something is not right.
有点不对劲。
So, uh, what's in your cake here?
那么，你的蛋糕里有什么?
Well, I put banana flavor in it.
我放了香蕉味的。
Okay. And it was a lot of alcohol.
好吧。而且喝了很多酒。
So it's extract. -Gotcha.
所以它是提取物。明白了。
I think I put a teaspoon in there.
我想我放了一茶匙进去。
You sure you just put a teaspoon in there?
你确定你刚放了茶匙进去吗?
I'm pretty sure.
我很确定。
Now, thinking about it, I think I added a tablespoon.
现在，想想看，我想我加了一汤匙。
Whoo!
哇!
Well, you certainly used it.
嗯，你确实用过。
Yes. You did, darlin'.
是的。是你，亲爱的。
I love fake banana flavor.
我喜欢假香蕉味的。
But there's a lot of it in here, though.
但这里有很多东西。
I mean, it's pretty strong.
我是说，味道很浓。
But it's nice and moist.
但是它很好，很湿润。
The frosting is really delicious.
糖霜真的很好吃。
This is probably the best cake
这可能是最好的蛋糕了
you've made the whole time you've been here.
你在这里待了这么久。
-Mm-hmm. -There's just a lot of banana.
-嗯。-香蕉太多了。
I know you think it's the best cake I've made so far.
我知道你认为这是我做过的最好吃的蛋糕。
Thanks, Audra.
谢谢,Audra。
But I hope it's the best cake you've had today.
但我希望这是你今天吃过的最好吃的蛋糕。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
I do not want to go home.
我不想回家。
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package... DUFF: Yeah!
将会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包…达夫:是啊!
...that includes a feature story in Food Network Magazine...
…包括《美食网络杂志》的一篇专题报道……
Hallelujah! ...and...
阿利路亚!…和…
$25,000.
25000美元。
[ Cheering ]
[欢呼]
Winner is coming.
赢家来了。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
All right, Valerie.
好吧，瓦莱丽。
Pet Project Desserts and mini pet treats.
宠物项目甜点和迷你宠物零食。
Okay, I have three words for you, Duff --
好吧，我给你三个词，达夫
Justice, peach pie.
正义，桃子派。
Mmm.
嗯。
Mama, give me some more of that peach pie.
妈妈，再给我来点桃子派。
That crust was buttery and flaky and perfectly done.
饼皮酥脆酥脆，做得很完美。
I really dug his peaches, too. They were juicy.
我也很喜欢他的桃子。它们多汁。
They weren't too sweet.
他们不太甜。
I happily could've eaten that entire pie.
我真想把整个派都吃掉。
The only thing that Justice had an issue with today
法官今天唯一有意见的事
was that little peach popper.
就是那个小蜜桃。
You're right. It was way too oily.
你是对的。太油了。
Okay. Cole, I think,
好吧。科尔，我想，
is a chef after my own heart
厨师合我的心意吗
'cause Cole got the mini pig as his animal
因为科尔得到了迷你猪作为他的动物
and so included bacon in his dessert.
所以在他的甜点中加入了培根。
Cole's maple-bacon doughnut was sweet, salty,
科尔的枫糖培根甜甜圈又甜又咸，
had all that great flavor.
味道都很好。
One thing I was really happy with Cole
有一点我对科尔很满意
is that he rendered his bacon correctly today, finally.
他今天终于把培根做好了。
Everything's crispy. -Okay.
一切都脆。-好的。
But the spider... -Yeah.
但是蜘蛛……-是的。
-Great story to it. -Mm-hmm.
-很棒的故事。-嗯。
-You know, "Charlotte's Web." -Sure.
-你知道，《夏洛特的网》。-当然。
But I don't think it's edible.
但我觉得它不能吃。
It's just a big thing of fondant.
只是一大块软糖。
Yeah. It looked like a tick.
是的。它看起来像一只扁虱。
It did!
它了!
What about Kaniyah today?
今天Kaniyah怎么样?
Oh, my God with that pineapple upside-down cake.
天啊，还有那个菠萝倒立蛋糕。
The texture and the flavor of that buttery ring,
黄油圈的口感和味道，
that's like somebody's grandma made that cake.
那蛋糕就像是某人的奶奶做的。
It was perfect. -Yeah.
这是完美的。-是的。
And I really liked her story.
我真的很喜欢她的故事。
Bunnies eating pineapples, you know, who knew? Who knew?
兔子吃菠萝，谁知道呢?谁知道呢?
The one thing that fell short on
唯一没做到的事
that plate was the underbaked cookie.
那盘子是没烤熟的饼干。
It really did.
确实如此。
Kaniyah said that that was her cookie redemption.
Kaniyah说那是她的饼干救赎。
I think she remains unredeemed.
我认为她还没有得到救赎。
Mm.
毫米。
We had a few stumbles today.
我们今天遇到了一些麻烦。
Audra's banana cake.
奥德拉的香蕉蛋糕。
It was very banana.
它很香蕉。
It wasn't banana.
那不是香蕉。
It was banana-flavoring banana.
那是香蕉味的香蕉。
I think her decorations were kind of weak.
我觉得她的装饰有点弱。
Everything was white. It was just, like,
一切都是白色的。就像，
white chickens, white egg, green buttercream.
白鸡，白蛋，绿奶油。
And that's it. -Yeah.
就是这样。-是的。
What in the world was going on with Aidan today?
艾登今天到底怎么了?
I was kind of surprised by what he put on the plate.
他在盘子里放的东西让我有点惊讶。
I think he was creative. And he thought about it.
我觉得他很有创意。他想了想。
And he made a turtle.
他做了一只乌龟。
It was just so sloppy.
太草率了。
It tasted great, though, really delicious cake.
尝起来很棒，蛋糕真的很好吃。
The buttercream was perfect, nice, crispy shell.
奶油很完美，外壳很脆。
Valerie, it did taste great.
瓦莱丽，味道确实很好。
But at the same time, it was boring.
但与此同时，它也很无聊。
It was just vanilla cake,
只是个香草蛋糕
vanilla frosting, a chocolate shell.
香草糖霜，巧克力壳。
And look. For his pet's pet,
看看。为了他宠物的宠物，
he had a glob of buttercream,
他吃了一团奶油，
put some eyes on it, and called it a fish.
给它长上眼睛，叫它鱼。
Okay. But the buttercream is edible.
好吧。但是奶油是可以吃的。
Cole's spider was not edible.
科尔的蜘蛛不能吃。
Do you really want to just eat a blob of buttercream?
你真的想只吃一团奶油吗?
-Over fondant? Yes. -Fair enough.
起方旦糖吗?是的。不够公平。
I feel like I'm nitpicking.
我觉得我在吹毛求疵。
But we're gonna decide who's gonna be in the final four
但我们将决定谁能进入四强
for this competition. -Mm.
为了这次比赛。毫米。
So we have to just pick apart each dessert
所以我们必须把每一道甜点分开
more than we ever would before.
比以往任何时候都要多。
-Yep. -This is huge.
是的。-这是件大事。
You ready to make that decision, Valerie?
你准备好做决定了吗，瓦莱丽?
I'm pretty sure I know who's going home today.
我很确定我知道今天谁要回家。
I do, too.
我也是。
I really hope I make it.
我真的希望我能成功。
Bakers, we're not sure which was more memorable,
面包师们，我们不确定哪个更令人难忘，
your faces when you walked in and saw the animals
你们走进来看到动物时的表情
or tasting your incredibly creative Pet Project Desserts.
或者品尝你令人难以置信的创意宠物项目甜点。
Two bakers in particular gave us desserts
有两个面包师特别给我们做了甜点
that made us want to beg for more.
这让我们想乞求更多。
[ Laughs ] Duff.
(笑)达夫。
Justice, your peach pie
正义，你的桃子派
with the latticework crust was ridiculously delicious.
加上格子状的面包皮，真是好吃极了。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
-Kaniyah. -Oh, yeah.
-Kaniyah。-哦,是的。
You made a gorgeous pineapple upside-down cake
你做了一个漂亮的菠萝倒立蛋糕
and creamy, delicious ice cream.
还有香甜可口的冰淇淋。
Oh, yeah.
哦,是的。
We looked it up, and your story of bunnies
我们查了一下，还有你的兔子故事
eating pineapples was legit and charming.
吃菠萝既合法又迷人。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
You have both earned a spot
你们都赢得了一席之地
in next week's semifinals.
在下周的半决赛中。
Yeah!
是啊!
But one baker's creations were the best in show.
但有一位面包师的作品在展览中是最好的。
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
Kaniyah.
Kaniyah。
Yes!
是的!
Again, again, again.
一遍又一遍。
I did it.
我做到了。我做到了。
I'm in the final four, ooh, ooh.
我进四强了，哦哦。
Congratulations, Kaniyah.
祝贺你,Kaniyah。
Now, there was one other baker
现在，还有一个面包师
whose dessert was good enough
谁的甜点够好
to earn a spot in the final four.
争取进入四强的机会。
Please be me.
请做我吧。请做我吧。
Cole, we will see you in the semifinals.
科尔，我们半决赛见。
Thank you. Phew.
谢谢你！唷。
That means Aidan and Audra, you're in the bottom.
也就是说艾登和奥德拉，你们在最底层了。
Please step forward.
请往前走。
Aidan, your chocolate turtle with yellow cake
艾登，你的黄蛋糕巧克力龟
and vanilla buttercream made us crave
香草奶油让我们欲罢不能
more exciting flavors.
更刺激的口味。
And your mini pet fish really was just a blob with eyes.
你的迷你宠物鱼其实只是一团有眼睛的东西。
Audra, your banana cake
Audra，你的香蕉蛋糕
with vanilla frosting had way too much banana.
香草糖霜加了太多香蕉。
Your chickens didn't really look like chickens.
你的鸡长得不像鸡。
And the mini pet egg you made was way too big.
你做的迷你宠物蛋太大了。
The baker who will be leaving us today is...
今天要离开我们的面包师是……
Audra.
Audra。
Sorry, Audra. -We are so gonna miss you.
对不起,Audra。我们会很想你的。
You have been such a pleasure to have around.
有你在身边是我的荣幸。
You are an awesome, awesome baker.
你是一个非常棒的面包师。
AUDRA: Even though I didn't win,
虽然我没有赢，
I've shown the whole world that I can bake well.
我已经向全世界证明了我烤得很好。
-I'm gonna miss you so much. -I'm gonna miss you more.
我会很想你的。我会更想你的。
Everyone here is just so nice. And I'm really gonna miss them.
这里的每个人都很好。我真的会想念他们的。
Bye. -See you, girl.
再见。-再见，姑娘。
But as soon as I get home, I'm going to hug my cat.
但是我一到家，我就要去拥抱我的猫。
I'm excited to see her.
我很高兴见到她。
DUFF: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
DUFF:《儿童烘焙锦标赛》前情提要……
-Chicken! -Oh, bunnies!
鸡!-哦,兔子!
One of these critters is going to inspire what you bake.
其中一种动物会给你的烘焙带来灵感。
When are you gonna get the waffle tattoo?
你打算什么时候纹华夫饼?
MICHAEL: I'm gonna book you an appointment right now.
迈克尔:我现在就给你预约。
I'm going to get my waffle.
我去拿我的华夫饼。
This is the best pineapple upside-down cake I've ever had.
这是我吃过的最好吃的菠萝倒立蛋糕。
Best in show --
最佳表演——
Kaniyah. -Yes!
Kaniyah。-是的!
Looks like you were really in a hurry.
看起来你真的很着急。
-I was. -I can tell.
我是。-我看得出来。
You have to really step it up.
你必须要加大力度。
Audra, your banana cake had way too much banana.
奥德拉，你的香蕉蛋糕里香蕉太多了。
The baker leaving us today is...
今天离开我们的面包师是…
Audra.
Audra。
**
**
-Oh, no. -Ah.
-哦,不。——啊。
They've gone mad.
他们疯了。
Oh, Duff. He looks evil.
哦,达夫。他看起来很邪恶。
[ Cackles ] -Good gracious.
[咯咯笑]-天哪。
I don't know what's going on.
我不知道发生了什么。
But Duff and Valerie are wearing lab coats.
但达夫和瓦莱丽穿着实验室工作服。
And I just know we're doing something science-y.
我只知道我们在做一些科学的事情。
And I don't like that.
我不喜欢那样。
Science is my least favorite subject.
科学是我最不喜欢的科目。
Ah, bakers, welcome.
啊，面包师们，欢迎你们。
Valerie, turn up the power to 1.21 gigawatts.
瓦莱丽，把功率调到1亿2千兆瓦。
-Are you sure, Doctor Duff? -Yes. Hurry!
-你确定吗，达夫医生?-是的。快点!
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
[ Coughing ]
[咳嗽]
I think you should turn that off.
我觉得你应该把它关掉。
Sorry.
对不起。
Bakers, now that we're down to the final four
面包师们，现在我们进入了四强
and on the verge of the finale
就在决赛的边缘
with $25,000 at stake,
25000美元岌岌可危，
we're inviting you into the inner sanctum
我们邀请你进入内室
to reveal the miraculous fusion of science and baking --
揭示科学与烘焙的神奇融合
molecular gastronomy.
分子烹饪。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
What?
怎么啦？
Molecular gastronomy
分子烹饪
physically transforms ingredients using science.
利用科学对原料进行物理转化。
For example,
例如,
you can use spherification chemicals
你可以使用球面化化学品
to turn liquid into little pearls of flavor.
把液体变成美味的小珍珠。
Behold, fresh raspberry-juice caviar.
看，新鲜的覆盆子汁鱼子酱。
It looks like fish eggs.
它看起来像鱼卵。
-Yum. [ Laughter ]
百胜。[笑声]
An immersion circulator
一种浸入式循环器制造技术
quickly infuses flavor into things.
能迅速给事物注入味道。
Right here, nectarines are soaking up
就在这里，油桃被吸收了
the flavor of fresh basil
新鲜罗勒的味道
and the sweetness of lime simple syrup.
还有柠檬糖浆的甜味。
Tapioca maltodextrin turns fat into molecular snow.
木薯淀粉麦芽糊精把脂肪变成分子雪。
Believe it or not, this is powdered butter.
信不信由你，这是黄油粉。
And it is delicious.
而且很好吃。
This is, like, freaky, honestly.
说实话，这太诡异了。
And to top it all off,
最重要的是，
a smoking gun adds smoke flavor to anything.
确凿的证据给任何东西都增加了烟味。
Voilà, smoked berries and cream cheese.
瞧，烟熏浆果和奶油奶酪。
Mmm. It smells so good.
嗯。闻起来真香。
Smells like ribs.
闻起来像排骨。
-[ Laughs ] -It smells like ribs?
-[笑]-闻起来像排骨?
-Yes. -Smells like ribs.
-是的。-闻起来像排骨。
Yes.
是的。
In this semifinal big bake,
在这场半决赛中，
each of you must use at least two
每个人至少要用两个
of these advanced techniques
这些先进的技术
to make a molecular-gastronomy dessert.
做一道分子美食甜点。
Give it everything you've got because, guys,
尽你所能，因为，伙计们，
this challenge will decide
这次挑战将决定
who is going on to the finale
谁将进入决赛
and who is going home.
谁要回家了。
-Not me.
不是我。不是我。
Nope.
不。
You have 90 minutes
你有90分钟的时间
to make your molecular kid-stronomy dessert.
来做你的分子儿童天文学甜点。
And your time starts...
你的时间开始了……
Now.Now.
Now.Now。
COLE: Go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go.
科尔:快，快，快，快。走，走，走，走。走，走，走，走。
No. I need the tapioca stuff.
不。我需要木薯粉。
-There's more than one. -Ugh.
-不止一个。啊。
Today's big bake,
今天的大烘焙，
we have 90 minutes to make a dessert
我们有90分钟做甜点
out of two molecular gastronomic --
从两个分子美食中——
Is that a word? -Yes.
这是一个词吗?-是的。
Okay.
好吧。
Molecular gastronomy.
分子烹饪。
KANIYAH: Ah!
KANIYAH:啊!
What have we created?
我们创造了什么?
Okay.
好吧。
Does anyone have the smoker gun?
有人有吸烟枪吗?
These techniques are pretty advanced.
这些技术相当先进。
Justice, do you mind if I borrow your smoker?
Justice，介意我借用一下你的烟机吗?
-Oh, yeah. You can. -Thank you.
-哦,是的。你可以。-谢谢。
Apparently, it's legal for a child
显然，这对孩子来说是合法的
to use a smoker gun.
用吸烟枪。
So...
所以…
-Hi, Aidan. -Hi.
-你好,艾丹。-你好。
Whatcha making, buddy?
你在做什么，伙计?
I'm making a s'mores-inspired tart
我在做一个受s'mores启发的蛋挞
with a graham-cracker crust.
用全麦饼干做皮。
And I'm gonna have smoked chocolate ganache.
我要烟熏巧克力甘纳许。
So you're gonna use the smoking gun.
所以你要用确凿的证据。
And which other method are you gonna use?
你还会用哪种方法?
I'm gonna make peanut butter powder using the tapioca.
我要用木薯粉做花生酱粉。
Yum. That sounds delicious.
好吃。听起来很好吃。
What would you do if you won $25,000?
如果你赢了两万五千美元，你会怎么做?
I might just set $1,000 aside to have to spend.
我可能会存下1000美元等着花。
I have two dogs at home.
我家里有两条狗。
And I hope sometime to buy a cat maybe.
我希望有一天能买只猫。
My dad is allergic.
我爸爸过敏。
So I don't know if it'll work out or not.
所以我不知道能不能成功。
But in the future, I want a cat.
但是将来，我想要一只猫。
I love cats so much.
我非常喜欢猫。
I might call it Cookie.
我可以叫它琦琦。
I don't want to hold you up.
我不想耽误你的时间。
This looks like a really exciting dessert.
这看起来真是一道令人兴奋的甜点。
-Bye. -Buh-bye.
再见。-Buh-bye。
I put my chocolate in the bowl,
我把巧克力放进碗里，
cover it with Saran Wrap.
用保鲜膜盖好。
I put wood chips in the smoker, turn the fan on.
我把木屑放进烟里，打开风扇。
And then I light the wood chips on fire.
然后我把木屑点着。
And all of a sudden, the smoke starts to fill up the bowl.
突然间，烟开始充满了碗。
Wow.
哇。
After there is smoke in it,
里面有烟之后，
you just seal off the plastic wrap
你只要把保鲜膜封起来
and let the smoke sort of flavor the chocolate.
让烟味给巧克力调味。
The smoking gun, when I first smelled it,
确凿的证据，当我第一次闻到的时候，
it really made me think of camping.
这让我想起了露营。
It smelled just like a campfire.
闻起来就像篝火。
And that's why I wanted to make a s'more tart.
所以我才想做个s'more蛋挞。
But I don't want to oversmoke my chocolate.
但我不想把巧克力抽得太多。
Okay. There's a lot of smoke.
好吧。有很多烟。
If the smoke alarm goes off,
如果烟雾报警器响了
I don't want to get eliminated.
我可不想被淘汰。
It tastes like it's burnt.
尝起来像烧焦了。
Smoky all right.
烟雾缭绕。
Hmm.
嗯。
I heat up my cream in the microwave,
我用微波炉加热奶油，
pour it over the chocolate
把它倒在巧克力上
and let that sit for the chocolate to melt.
静置以待巧克力融化。
Smoky. It's good.
烟熏。很好。
I would have loved a mad science room.
我想要个疯狂的科学室。
I had a chemistry set.
我有一套化学设备。
-Did you? -Uh-huh.
-你吗?-嗯。
Almost burned the house down.
差点把房子烧了。
Not surprised.
并不感到意外。
Today, I'm making a cinnamon- and nutmeg-infused apple pie
今天，我要做一个肉桂和肉豆蔻苹果派
with a ice cream- and raspberry-caviar.
还有冰淇淋和覆盆子鱼子酱。
I love apple pie.
我喜欢苹果派。
I make apple pie all the time.
我经常做苹果派。
It's a favorite of my family.
这是我家人的最爱。
First things first, my apples are chopped.
重要的是，我的苹果切碎了。
So I'm gonna put them in a plastic bag
所以我要把它们放在塑料袋里
with simple syrup, cinnamon sticks, and nutmeg
用糖浆，肉桂棒和肉豆蔻
so I can get them in the immersion circulator.
这样我就可以把它们放进浸入式循环器了。
It takes almost half an hour
差不多要半个小时
to fully suck in the flavors.
充分地吸收味道。
These flavors are gonna infuse in the apples.
这些味道会渗透到苹果里。
And it's gonna taste just like apple pie.
尝起来就像苹果派。
Last week was really difficult.
上周真的很难熬。
So this week, I'm going to manage my time
所以这周，我要管理好我的时间
and make everything perfect.
让一切都变得完美。
My biggest competition is probably Aidan.
我最大的竞争对手可能是艾登。
He's very creative, just like me.
他很有创造力，就像我一样。
So I need to step up my game a little bit.
所以我需要提高我的水平。
15 minutes gone, bakers.
15分钟过去了，面包师们。
15 minutes, bakers.
15分钟，面包师们。
How's everyone doing? Why so serious?
大家都好吗?为什么这么严肃?
The competition is getting super intense.
竞争变得超级激烈。
And I want to win so bad.
我太想赢了。
So my dessert has to be really good.
所以我的甜点必须非常好吃。
Where are the apple corers? -Oh, what are you doing?
苹果皮在哪里?-你在干什么?
Are you doing, like, an apple crumble?
你是在做苹果酥吗?
Cobbler.
补鞋匠。
I wish I could make a pie.
我希望我能做一个派。
But I did make one last week.
但我上周做了一个。
So instead, I think I will make a cobbler.
所以，我想我要做一个补鞋匠。
Normally I make them out of, like, berries.
通常我是用浆果做的。
But today I think I'm gonna do apple
但今天我想做苹果
and a smoked-apple ice cream.
还有一份烟熏苹果冰淇淋。
Are you done with the corer?
你盖好封面了吗?
-Yeah. -Thank you.
-是的。-谢谢。
I'm borrowing the corer from Cole.
我向科尔借了封面。
And I'm realizing he's also making an apple pie.
我发现他还在做苹果派。
Hooray.
万岁。
Why?
为什么?
Do you have the ground nutmeg? -Yeah.
你有肉豆蔻粉吗?-是的。
I borrow the nutmeg from Cole.
我向科尔借了肉豆蔻。
And I realize he's only using nutmeg and cinnamon.
我发现他只用了肉豆蔻和肉桂。
So I'm using cinnamon, nutmeg, and mace.
所以我要用肉桂，肉豆蔻和肉豆蔻。
Mace is like a spice you can use to help make it taste
梅斯就像一种香料，你可以用它来增加味道
even more like apple pie
更像是苹果派
and warm coziness.
还有温暖舒适。
I cut a lemon and I squeeze some juice into a teaspoon
我切了一个柠檬，在一个茶匙里挤了一些柠檬汁
'cause it's nice to have some tartness.
因为有点酸味是很好的。
I'll put the apple spices
我要放些苹果香料
and all my other spices
还有我所有的香料
into the immersion circulator
进入浸入式循环器
so it can become all nice and blended together.
这样就可以很好地混合在一起。
What's up, Justice?
怎么了，法官?
So you're using the immersion circulator
所以你要用浸入式循环器
and what else? -The smoker.
还有什么?——吸烟者。
Chemistry, you got it.
化学，你懂的。
Yeah. How badly do you want to be in this finale?
是的。你有多想进入决赛?
Well, on a scale of one to 10, I would want it infinity.
在1到10的范围内，我希望它是无穷大。
I think if I got into the finale,
我想如果我能进入决赛，
I would be able to just win the whole thing
我就能赢得整场比赛
and be, like... -Smooth sailing.
然后他……顺利航行。
"I did it. Yay."
“我做到了。耶。”
-Good luck. -Thank you.
好的运气。-谢谢。
Go get them.
去找他们。
How are you boys doing?
你们最近怎么样?
-Good. -Mm-hmm.
改善情况。-嗯。
I may be the only girl left,
我可能是唯一剩下的女孩，
but those boys better watch out.
但那些男孩最好小心点。
I'm bringing it, no doubt.
毫无疑问，我会带来的。
I'm gonna make a smoked-berry pie
我要做一个烟熏浆果派
with hazelnut-chocolate snow
榛子巧克力雪花
with a raspberry-caviar ice cream.
还有覆盆子鱼子酱冰淇淋。
I want to get started on my pie crust
我要开始做派皮了
because it's going to take a long time to get it perfect.
因为要做到完美需要很长时间。
So I add flour, a little bit of sugar,
加入面粉，少许糖，
salt, butter, vegetable shortening.
盐，黄油，蔬菜起酥油。
And then I add my ice-cold water.
然后加入冰水。
You always want to use cold butter
你总是想用冷黄油
and cold water to make it flaky.
再加冷水，让它变薄。
I'm the only girl.
我是唯一的女孩。
But that's okay 'cause I'm gonna win some money.
不过没关系，因为我要赢钱了。
When I win the $25,000,
等我赢了两万五千美元
I'm going to expand my business
我要扩大我的生意
and get more customers
获得更多的客户
and buy a lifetime supply
买一辈子用的
of expensive, good sneakers
昂贵的好运动鞋
'cause I love sneakers.
因为我喜欢运动鞋。
Moola, cha-ching.
金钱,唰唰。
Hey, bakers. Can we have your attention?
嘿,面包师。请大家注意一下好吗?
-Yep. -What is that?
是的。-那是什么?
We are about to take molecular gastronomy
我们要讲分子烹饪
back in time.
回到过去。
I don't mean to scare you guys.
我不是想吓到你们。
But this could be really "whisk-y."
但这可能真的是“搅拌”。
-What? -Y'all are evil.
-什么?-你们都是恶魔。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
We are about to take molecular gastronomy back in time.
我们将带着分子美食回到过去。
What is that?
那是什么?
In addition to your two modern tools,
除了你的两个现代工具，
you must use an old-school whisk.
你必须使用老式的打蛋器。
For what? Make some whipped cream for your dessert.
为了什么?做些鲜奶油做甜点。
-By hand? -Y'all are evil.
——手吗?-你们都是恶魔。
That's right.
这是正确的。
You got to use old-fashioned elbow grease.
你得用老式的体力。
-That's mean. -Come on.
——的意思。头里。
Come up and get your whisk.
上来拿你的打蛋器。
-Come up and get your -- whoa. -Sorry.
-上来拿你的——哇。对不起。
-That's okay. -We're so sorry.
——没问题。-我们很抱歉。
That's fine.
这很好。
-Ooh, I like this one. -I got the good one.
-哦，我喜欢这个。-我得到了一个好的。
AIDAN: This is mean.
艾丹:这太刻薄了。
There's a weird, tennis-racket-shaped whisk.
有一个奇怪的网球拍形状的搅拌器。
I grab it.
我抓住它。
It's whipped cream unplugged.
这是不插电的生奶油。
My whisk looks like something you mash potatoes with.
我的打蛋器看起来像捣碎土豆的东西。
It doesn't even look like a real whisk.
它看起来都不像真正的打蛋器。
Heavy cream. I'm gonna make a plain whipped cream
奶油。我要做一个普通的生奶油
and just, like, keep it as simple as I can.
尽可能地让它变得简单
I put the cream into the bowl.
我把奶油放进碗里。
And I start to whisk.
我开始搅拌。
And then I add some sugar.
然后我加一些糖。
If you overwhisk it, it'll turn into butter.
如果你过度搅拌，它就会变成黄油。
And you do not want that.
你不希望那样。
Where's my whisk?
我的打蛋器呢?
Not all whisks are created equal.
并非所有的打蛋器都是一样的。
When you're hand-whipping whipped cream,
当你用手搅拌鲜奶油时，
you really want a half-moon whisk
你真的需要一个半月打蛋器
'cause you can just really shake it.
因为你真的可以摇晃它。
And it just whips in front of your eyes.
就在你眼前晃来晃去。
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
快点，快点，快点。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
DUFF: Use your brains.
达夫:动动脑筋。
And your brawn.
还有你的肌肉。
Look at this.
看看这个。
I'm gonna get my pie done first.
我要先把派做好。
I should have plenty of time to make my whipped cream.
我应该有足够的时间做鲜奶油。
AIDAN: Ooh, gosh.
艾丹:哦，天哪。
I wanted to be so clean today.
我今天真想打扫干净。
But no.
但是没有。
"Aidan, you can't be clean today
“艾登，你今天不可能干净
'cause you have to whip cream by hand."
因为你必须用手搅打奶油。”
Ooh, Aidan is not happy about that twist.
艾登对这个转折很不高兴。
This is stupid.
这太愚蠢了。
Oh, Aidan. I'm sorry.
哦,艾丹。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry for the twist.
我很抱歉搞砸了。
A little bit of powdered sugar for sweetness.
加一点糖粉来增加甜味。
And now I'm gonna chill this until it's ready.
现在我要把它冷却，直到它准备好。
Twist down.
拧下来。
It would take me the entire 90 minutes
这要花我整整90分钟
to whip up whipped cream with my hand.
用手搅拌鲜奶油。
You know, you and I are gonna whip cream by hand.
你和我要用手打发奶油。
Ugh, I don't want to.
呃，我不想。
I mean, it takes about three minutes.
我是说，大概需要三分钟。
Uh, not -- No.
不，不。
For you, it takes three minutes. For me, it takes three hours.
对你来说，只需要三分钟。对我来说，需要三个小时。
Whoo.
喔!
Being a bit messy today, like I always am.
今天有点乱，我一直都是这样。
To make my graham-cracker crust,
为了做我的全麦饼干脆皮，
I get graham-cracker crumbs,
我有全麦饼干屑，
butter, and a little bit of sugar.
黄油，还有一点糖。
And I just mix those with my hands.
然后用手搅拌。
I'm just gonna try to take some softened butter,
我要试着用一些软化的黄油，
brush it around.
刷一下。
I just don't want it to stick.
我只是不想让它粘住。
I don't want there to be any chance of a crumbly tart.
我可不想蛋挞有任何碎的可能。
Why is everyone doing pies?
为什么每个人都在做馅饼?
My dessert is gonna stand out
我的甜点会脱颖而出的
because I'm the only one
因为我是唯一一个
who's not making a pie or a cobbler
谁不做派或馅饼呢
'cause pie and cobbler are basically the same thing.
因为馅饼和馅饼基本上是一样的。
My little tarts.
我的小宝贝们。
Good. All right. I'm gonna bake these.
好。好吧。我要烤这些。
And I bake them off for five minutes.
然后烤五分钟。
And it'll be nice and hard.
它会变得又好又硬。
Yay.
耶。
I have to have something that's baked.
我得吃点烤好的。
This is the baking championship.
这是烘焙锦标赛。
45 minutes left, bakers.
还有45分钟，面包师们。
My pie crust has to be in the oven
我的派皮必须在烤箱里烤
for at least 20 minutes.
至少20分钟。
And I need to hurry up.
我得快点了。
Okay.
好吧。
I combine butter and flour first
我先把黄油和面粉混合
and then add water gradually until it forms a dough.
然后慢慢加水，直到揉成面团。
-Hi, Cole. -Hi.
-你好,科尔。-你好。
Whatcha making?
到了以后在做什么?
I'm making an infused apple pie.
我在做苹果派。
Ooh. And ice cream with raspberry caviar.
哦。还有覆盆子鱼子酱冰淇淋。
So you're using the spherification chemicals?
所以你在用球面化化学品?
-Yes. -And the immersion circulator?
-是的。那浸入式循环器呢?
Yes. This is gonna get you into the finale?
是的。这样你就能进决赛了吗?
Or not? -Yeah. It's gonna get me to win.
或不呢?-是的。这会让我赢的。
Good attitude.
良好的态度。
I'm in this competition to prove
我要在这场比赛中证明
that I can do this and that boys can bake.
我能做这个，男孩能烤面包。
And I'm starting to work on my cobbler dough.
我开始做馅饼面团了。
For this, I use self-rising flour
我用的是自发面粉
because it already has a leavening agent in it.
因为里面已经有发酵剂了。
So it'll just puff up automatically.
所以它会自动膨胀。
And you don't have to put baking powder in there.
你不需要在里面放发酵粉。
The first thing I do is I measure my butter and flour.
我要做的第一件事是量一下黄油和面粉。
And I just smoosh it together.
我只是把它们挤在一起。
I just want to get it all crumbled up.
我只想把它弄碎。
Then I start to add my buttermilk,
然后加入酪乳，
nutmeg, cinnamon, and salt.
肉豆蔻，肉桂和盐。
I add some mace and my sugar.
我加了一些肉豆蔻和糖。
Mm. It's super good.
嗯，超级好吃。
Next, I need to start and assemble everything.
接下来，我需要开始组装所有东西。
And I add all the nice filling that I had.
我把所有的馅料都加进去。
Then I crumble my dough on top.
然后我把面团碎在上面。
You want just, like, clumps of it all over.
你想要的是一团一团的。
And I'm ready to put them in the oven.
我准备把它们放进烤箱。
It's gonna taste super good, I hope.
我希望味道会非常好。
Right now, I think the top two are Cole and Aidan
现在，我觉得前两名是科尔和艾登
because they're really good bakers.
因为他们是很棒的面包师。
And they can also do really good decorations.
他们也可以做很好的装饰。
But I'm not really intimidated because I think that my cobbler
但我并不害怕，因为我觉得我的鞋匠
will probably be able to keep me in the competition.
也许能让我继续参加比赛。
Isn't it so great to be on the "Kids Baking Championship"?
能参加"儿童烘焙大赛"真是太棒了?
-Sometimes. -Yes.
——有时。-是的。
-No. -[ Laughs ]
-不。——(笑)
I start on my berries.
我开始吃浆果。
I'm gonna use the smoking gun for my fruit.
我要用确凿的证据来证明我的水果。
You use the lighter, which is really dangerous
你用打火机，这很危险
'cause I'm dangerous like that.
因为我很危险。
Now I need to smoke my berries.
现在我要抽我的浆果。
[ Coughs ]
[咳嗽]
I taste my berry.
我品尝我的浆果。
It's not smoky.
它不冒烟。
I want a smoked-berry pie, not a berry pie.
我要烟熏浆果派，不是浆果派。
So I smoke it again.
所以我又抽了一遍。
Then I let it sit for a long time.
然后我把它放了很长时间。
I keep plastic wrap on top to keep all the smoke in.
我用保鲜膜把烟挡在外面。
These berries have got to be smoked by now.
这些浆果现在该熏制了。
And then I mix it with the sugar to make it like a filling,
然后我把它和糖混合，做成馅料，
to make it gooey.
使它粘稠。
And then I put it in my pie crust.
然后我把它放在派皮上。
And I cover the top.
我把上面盖上。
Then I put it in the oven.
然后我把它放进烤箱。
Where is he? Oh. [ Laughs ]
他在哪里?哦。[笑]
Duff's about to hurt himself is what he's doing.
达夫这是在伤害自己。
I'm fast like Bruce Lee.
我像李小龙一样快。
He's got catlike reflexes.
他有猫一样的反应能力。
This thing's gonna chop my arm off.
这东西会把我的胳膊砍下来的。
[ Warning siren blaring ]
[警笛鸣响]
COLE: It's time to get this built.
科尔:是时候把它建成了。
For my pies, I want a lattice on top.
做馅饼的时候，我要在上面放一个格子。
They look really nice.
它们看起来很漂亮。
And I'm ready to make my ice cream base.
我准备好做冰淇淋底了。
You can't have apple pie without vanilla ice cream.
苹果派不能没有香草冰淇淋。
It just doesn't work.
这根本行不通。
I make classic vanilla ice cream
我做经典的香草冰淇淋
by heating up cream and milk.
通过加热奶油和牛奶。
And I'm whisking the egg yolks and sugars.
搅拌蛋黄和糖。
And then it gets light in color.
然后颜色变浅。
You don't have to use egg yolks with your ice cream.
你不需要用蛋黄做冰淇淋。
I love it because it makes your ice cream
我喜欢它，因为它可以做成你的冰淇淋
super silky and so good.
超级丝滑，非常好吃。
Who's doing caviar pearls or --
谁在做鱼子酱珍珠还是
Me.
我。
Just seeing. I was just curious.
刚刚看到。我只是好奇。
-Are you? -No.
是你吗?-不。
I'm using the smoker gun.
我用的是吸烟枪。
And I'm making peanut butter snow.
我在做花生酱雪。
I've never made
我从来没做过花生酱雪。
But it's not that hard.
但这并不难。
You just whisk together peanut butter and the powder.
你只要把花生酱和面粉搅拌在一起。
And then you puree it in the food processor.
然后在食品加工机里打成泥。
And it comes out to be a nice peanut butter-flavored snow.
最后变成了花生酱味的雪。
The most difficult part of this dessert
这道甜点最难的部分
is probably the raspberry caviar
可能是覆盆子鱼子酱
because I've never made raspberry caviar.
因为我从来没做过覆盆子鱼子酱。
I need to get started.
我得开始了。
So I blend the sodium alginate into my raspberries.
所以我把海藻酸钠混合到覆盆子里。
And while that's blending,
在混合的过程中，
I put calcium chloride into my water
我把氯化钙放进水里
so that when the puree drops in there,
这样当果泥掉进去的时候，
it forms a skin.
它形成了一层皮肤。
It's not working.
这行不通。
It's not forming a skin.
它没有形成表皮。
And when I pick it up with the spoon,
当我用勺子把它捡起来的时候，
it just breaks and falls through.
它就这样破掉了。
I'm just gonna try using a syringe
我要试试用注射器
and individually dropping them.
然后一个个地放下它们。
It's just way too thick.
它太厚了。
And it just falls apart in the bowl.
它在碗里就散了。
I messed up again.
我又搞砸了。
I don't know what to do with this.
我不知道该怎么办。
I can't do this.
我做不到。
30 minutes, bakers.
30分钟，面包师们。
30 minutes left.
还有30分钟。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
ANNOUNCER: An ordinary mug of hot chocolate
一杯普通的热巧克力
radiates into hot chocolate cake in a mug
辐射到杯子里的热巧克力蛋糕里
right after this.
就在这之后。
ANNOUNCER: How to make quick and easy hot chocolate mug cakes.
解说员:如何快速简便地制作热巧克力马克杯蛋糕。
Gather together chocolate cake batter,
将巧克力蛋糕面糊，
microwave-safe mugs, cinnamon sticks,
微波炉安全杯，肉桂棒，
and a little whipped cream.
再加一点生奶油。
Parcel out your batter,
把面糊散开，
about 1:30 in the microwave to bake.
大约1:30在微波炉里烤。
[ Ding! ] Top with a whole cinnamon stick
(叮!在上面放一根肉桂棒
and a dollop of whipped cream.
再来一团生奶油。
Gooey, tender, chocolate cake in a mug.
杯子里的巧克力蛋糕又软又粘。
For more treats like this,
想要更多这样的美食，
visit foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com/kidsbaking。
25 minutes left.
还剩25分钟。
Give us a molecular-gastronomy dessert.
给我们一份分子美食甜点。
Use that mad science to make those flavors come alive.
用疯狂的科学让这些味道变得鲜活起来。
Alive!Alive!
活着,活着!
This is not working for me.
这对我没用。
So I'm not really sure what I'm gonna do.
所以我不确定我该怎么做。
I'm so stressed right now.
我现在压力很大。
This raspberry caviar looks terrible.
这个覆盆子鱼子酱看起来很糟糕。
Cole, figure it out.
科尔，想办法。
I can't do this. I'm doing something else.
我做不到。我在做别的事。
I think he's scrapping it.
我想他要放弃了。
Oh, I wanted to taste it.
哦，我想尝尝。
I don't know what I did wrong.
我不知道我做错了什么。
But I need to start something else.
但我得开始做点别的。
I can't go home.
我不能回家。
Kaniyah, do you have any peanut butter? No.
卡尼亚，你有花生酱吗?不。
Aidan, do you have peanut butter?
艾登，你有花生酱吗?
Yeah. I have peanut butter.
是的。我有花生酱。
I decided to make peanut butter snow.
我决定做花生酱雪。
Why did I not think of this first?
为什么我没有先想到这一点?
I spent so much time thinking about raspberry caviar.
我花了很多时间想覆盆子鱼子酱。
It didn't even work.
它根本没用。
And raspberry does not go with apples.
覆盆子和苹果不搭。
Can I use some?
我可以用一些吗?
-Yeah. I'm all done with it. -I grab the peanut butter.
-是的。我受够了。-我拿起花生酱。
And there's not a lot in the jar.
罐子里也没多少了。
There's just enough
足够了
that I could still make some peanut butter snow.
我还能做花生酱雪
17 minutes.
17分钟。
Got to make the snow.
得造雪了。
I mix peanut butter and tapioca maltodextrin
我把花生酱和木薯淀粉糊精混合在一起
and put it in a food processor.
然后放到食品加工机里。
And it'll turn from white to, like, a light tan.
然后它就会从白色变成浅棕色。
And it's kind of weird, so weird.
这有点奇怪，太奇怪了。
AIDAN: I notice that Cole is making peanut butter snow just like me.
艾丹:我注意到科尔和我一样在做花生酱雪。
Hmm.
嗯。
Crap.
废话。
Okay.
好吧。
We're gonna find out who is better
我们会找出谁更好
and who goes home.
谁回家了。
Okay. Don't get nervous, Aidan. You have tons of time.
好吧。别紧张，艾登。你有很多时间。
It's time to assemble my s'mores.
是时候组装我的巧克力夹心饼了。
I start to delicately take out my shells.
我开始小心翼翼地取出蛋壳。
And they're crumbling.
他们正在崩溃。
No, no, no, no, no.
不不不不不不。
[ Gasps ] Aidan's tart shells are breaking.
艾丹的蛋挞壳碎了。
What's he gonna do?
他会怎么做?
I'll tell you what he's not gonna do --
我来告诉你他不会做什么
make a tart.
做一个蛋挞。
I don't know why they're crumbling.
我不知道他们为什么会崩溃。
Maybe they're not hard enough.
也许他们不够努力。
That's kind of falling apart.
这有点崩溃了。
Next time, he's gonna put some more butter
下次，他会多放点黄油
and sugar in there.
还有糖。
I can't use this.
我不能用这个。
I am freaking out because it's the main point of my dish.
我吓坏了，因为这是我这道菜的重点。
I should've never ever done this.
我就不该这么做。
10 minutes, bakers. You got 10 minutes.
10分钟，面包师们。给你10分钟。
I just need to turn them into deconstructed tarts.
我只需要把它们变成解构的馅饼。
I'm gonna have to plate the crumbs
我要把面包屑装盘
inside a little glass
在一个小玻璃杯里
because when all else fails, deconstruct.
因为当一切都失败时，解构。
Okay.
好吧。
And I put ganache on
我放了甘纳许
and put a nice dollop of whipped cream on top.
在上面放一团鲜奶油。
And I think that's good.
我认为这很好。
-Ah! [ Electricity buzzing ]
——啊![电嗡嗡声]
Ah! [ Laughs ]
啊![笑]
-You startled me. -I'm alive!
-你吓到我了。-我活着!
I seriously thought you just --
我真的以为你只是
You got me for a second.
你说到我了。
I'm scared.
我很害怕。
JUSTICE: Now that my cobblers are in the oven,
法官:现在我的补鞋匠在烤箱里，
I am gonna start working on my smoked-apple ice cream.
我要开始做烟熏苹果冰淇淋了。
I light the wood chips.
我点燃了木屑。
And it's starting to glow. And that's what you want.
它开始发光了。这就是你想要的。
It looks super cool.
看起来超级酷。
The apples are basically marinating in the smoke.
苹果基本上是泡在烟里了。
So I'm ready to start my crème anglaise.
我准备好开始我的法式英语了。
And I put some milk, cream, and vanilla bean
我放了一些牛奶，奶油和香草豆
in a saucepan until it's nice and warm.
放入平底锅中加热。
And then I add my sugar,
然后加入糖，
egg yolks, and some spices until it's pale in color
蛋黄，加一些香料，直到颜色变淡
and put that in the ice cream machine.
把它放进冰淇淋机。
So I get my apples out of the bowl.
我把苹果从碗里拿出来。
And I start to incorporate those
我开始把它们结合起来
so that it gets that nice, smoky flavor.
这样就有了烟熏味。
-Can I use this, please? -Yeah. I'm all done.
-我可以用这个吗?-是的。我都做完了。
You still haven't made your powder?
你还没做粉?
-No. -Hurry, hurry, hurry.
-不。-快点，快点，快点。
Got a lot to do during this bake.
烤面包的时候有很多事要做。
It's time to start on my ice cream.
是时候开始吃我的冰淇淋了。
I use milk, heavy cream,
我用牛奶，多脂奶油，
raspberry puree, and raspberries.
树莓泥和树莓。
And I bring it to a low boil.
然后小火煮。
And then I get my ice cream into the ice cream maker...
然后我把冰淇淋放进冰淇淋机……
Put it in the blast chiller to make it harder.
把它放进冷冻机里，让它变硬。
I get the pies out of the oven
我把派从烤箱里拿出来
and place them on a cooling rack.
然后把它们放在冷却架上。
And then I get started on my snow.
然后我开始做我的雪。
How you doing, Kaniyah?
你好吗，Kaniyah?
Good.
好。
I just need hazelnut spread.
我只需要榛子酱。
Anybody have the hazelnut spread?
有人有榛子酱吗?
I never touched it.
我从来没碰过它。
I go run over and get a food processor.
我跑过去拿了个食品加工机。
My chocolate-hazelnut snow is gonna be on point.
我的巧克力榛子雪会是最佳选择。
And, like, what's not to love about chocolate and berries?
还有，有什么理由不喜欢巧克力和浆果呢?
That's a classic.
这是经典之作。
8 minutes, bakers.
8分钟，面包师。
Ah, 8 minutes.
啊，8分钟。
[ Gasps ] Oh, my God.
(喘息)哦，我的上帝。
I realized that my whipped cream wasn't whipped.
我意识到我的鲜奶油不是鲜奶油。
And that takes a long time.
这需要很长时间。
[ Crying ]
[哭泣]
Make some whipped cream quickly.
快做些生奶油。
Make sure it's cold.
确保它是冷的。
What is Kaniyah doing? She's sobbing.
Kaniyah在做什么?她在哭泣。
VALERIE: What's going on, babe?
瓦莱丽:怎么了，宝贝?
You putting a little bit of your tears in there for us?
你是在为我们流泪吗?
I don't have my whipped cream.
我没带鲜奶油。
Kaniyah, what's wrong?
Kaniyah，怎么了?
why do you want this?
卡尼亚，你为什么想要这个?
I have to make my powder.
我得做粉了。
You have to make your powder? Okay. Make your powder.
你得自己做爽身粉?好吧。做你的粉。
You got this.
你能行的。
I never want to do this again.
我再也不想这么做了。
Kaniyah, I'm coming.
Kaniyah，我来了。
8 minutes, bakers.
8分钟，面包师。
Ah, 8 minutes.
啊，8分钟。
[ Crying ]
[哭泣]
Kaniyah, I'm coming.
Kaniyah，我来了。
Kaniyah, what do you need done?
Kaniyah，你需要做什么?
Can you whip my whipped cream please?
你能打一下我的鲜奶油吗?
-Sure. Where is it? -It's right there.
-当然。它在哪里?-就在那儿。
Whip this cream.
打发这奶油。
-Her knight in shining armor. -Knight in shining armor.
-她穿着闪亮盔甲的骑士。-穿着闪亮盔甲的骑士。
Work those arm muscles.
锻炼手臂肌肉。
Ah.
啊。
Is this all you need left?
剩下的就这些了吗?
-Yes. -Okay.
-是的。-好的。
I promise you I will get this cream whipped in time.
我向你保证我会及时把奶油打好。
Thank you, Aidan.
谢谢你，艾登。
I -- I'm telling you,
我告诉你
I can't take this show anymore.
我再也看不下去了。
I just can't take it. I can't do this anymore.
我受不了了。我不能再这样下去了。
All right. It's all whipped.
好吧。都搅过了。
Use the measuring scoop to scoop it.
用量勺舀一下。
That's what I did. And it worked great.
我就是这么做的。效果很好。
-I love you, Aidan. -Thanks.
-我爱你，艾登。-谢谢。
Thank you, Aidan.
谢谢你，艾登。
All right. Everyone should be plating now.
好吧。现在每个人都该镀了。
Make them look cool.
让他们看起来很酷。
COLE: Oh, my God.
科尔:哦，天哪。
I still need to churn my ice cream.
我还需要搅拌我的冰淇淋。
My pies are still baking.
我的派还在烤。
I don't know if I have enough time.
我不知道我是否有足够的时间。
All right. 5 minutes, guys.
好吧。5分钟，伙计们。
We got 5 minutes. -Oh, my God.
我们还有5分钟。-我的天啊。
I churn the ice cream a little longer
我把冰淇淋搅得更久一些
so that I don't have to put it in the blast chiller
这样我就不用把它放进冷风机里了
'cause I don't have time to do that.
因为我没时间做那个。
And now I can just serve it right away.
现在我可以马上上菜了。
Cole, is everything else plated?
科尔，其他的都准备好了吗?
The ice cream's the only thing you're waiting on?
冰淇淋是你唯一在等的东西?
-My pies. -Okay.
我的馅饼。-好的。
My ice cream's finally made.
我的冰淇淋终于做好了。
But I still have to get my pies out of the oven.
但我还得把派从烤箱里拿出来。
I'm really concerned about Cole.
我真的很担心科尔。
We're running out of time.
我们没时间了。
Get plated.
被镀。
AIDAN: I'm almost ready to plate.
艾丹:我快准备好装盘了。
My meringue is mixing.
我的蛋白霜在搅拌。
It's just egg whites and sugar.
它只是蛋清和糖。
It looks perfect.
看起来很完美。
That's stiff.
这是僵硬的。
It's just like llama fur.
就像羊驼毛一样。
Blow torch works fast.
喷灯工作快。
My meringue is done.
我的蛋白霜做好了。
My peanut butter snow and my tarts went on the plate.
我的花生酱雪和蛋挞上了盘子。
And I'm almost finished plating.
我差不多完成了。
They look like slightly creepy smiley faces.
它们看起来有点吓人的笑脸。
My ice cream tastes really, really good.
我的冰淇淋非常非常好吃。
And my cobbler is out of the oven
我的馅饼出炉了
and put onto my plate.
然后放到我的盘子里。
And I need to start making my ganache.
我要开始做巧克力酱了。
The cream looks nice and warm. I pour that out.
奶油看起来又好又暖和。我倒出来。
And I dump that over my chocolate.
我把它倒在巧克力上。
And I start to mix that up.
我开始把它们混在一起。
No, no, no, no, no. My ganache is super watery.
不不不不不不。我的甘那许水特别多。
Ganache usually looks like thick, chocolaty fudge.
甘纳许通常看起来像厚厚的巧克力软糖。
But this looks like water.
但这看起来像水。
And I do not know what's happening to it.
我不知道它发生了什么。
I put it back in the microwave to heat it up
我把它放回微波炉加热
because I think I'm just gonna put some more chocolate in there
因为我想我要在里面再放些巧克力
so it's not as, like, watery.
所以它不像水一样。
Whatcha doing, Justice?
你在干什么，法官?
Justice, what are you doing?
法官，你在干什么?
Uh, it was -- Keep going. Keep going. Don't stop.
呃，那是继续说。继续。不要停止。
We only have two minutes left.
我们只剩下两分钟了。
[ Groans ]
[呻吟]
Get something on the plate, everyone.
大家吃点东西。
Everything is done.
一切都完成了。
My smoked-berry pie
我的烟熏浆果派
and raspberry ice cream are made.
还有覆盆子冰淇淋。
My chocolate-hazelnut snow looks fine.
我的巧克力榛子雪看起来不错。
But my plate is a little messy.
但我的盘子有点乱。
But I hope it tastes good.
但我希望它尝起来不错。
-Aidan. -90 seconds.
艾丹。-90秒。
COLE: I finally got my pies out of the oven.
科尔:我终于把派从烤箱里拿出来了。
And I don't have time to check it or taste it.
我没有时间去检查或品尝。
I just have to get them on the plate.
我只需要把它们放到盘子里。
Hurry, guys. Hurry.
快点,伙计们。快点。
No.
不。
I wanted the ganache on the plate
我想把甘纳许放在盘子里
for decorations and, like, swirl on the plate.
用来装饰，比如在盘子上旋转。
But that didn't work.
但这行不通。
I'm just angry at that ganache.
我只是对那巧克力酱很生气。
10...
十……
Both: 9...8...7...6...
两种:9……八……七……6…
Go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走。走，走，走，走，走。
...5...4...3...2...1.
5…4 3…2…1。
-Hands up.
手了。手了。
Okay, you guys. Don't ever do that to me again.
好了，伙计们。别再这样对我了。
DUFF: Down to the wire.
达夫:最后一刻。
-Whoo-hoo. -Whoo.
-Whoo-hoo。-哇。
Wow. Good job.
哇。好工作。
"Molacular" -- "molucular" -- molecular --
Molacular——分子的——分子的——
molecular "kid-stromony" --
分子的“孩子的和谐”——
"Kid-stromony."
“Kid-stromony。”
Molecular kid-stronomy desserts.
分子儿童天文学甜点。
Are we mad?
我们疯了吗?
Oh, my God. Somebody help us.
我的天啊。谁来帮帮我们。
-Want to bring in Aidan? -Let's.
-想把艾登带来吗?小的。
Aidan.
艾丹。
-Hi.
-你好。-你好。
AIDAN: The last week, I was in the bottom.
艾丹:上周，我在垫底。
And I nearly got sent home.
我差点被送回家。
This is the last time
这是最后一次
a person's gonna go home before the finale.
一个人要在大结局之前回家。
And I do not want to be that person.
我不想成为那样的人。
So, I got a surprise for you.
我给你准备了个惊喜。
A couple weeks ago I promised that if the waffle side won,
几周前我承诺如果华夫饼那边赢了，
I would get a waffle tattoo.
我会纹个华夫饼纹身。
You should get
你应该纹个华夫饼纹身。
-[ Laughs ] -I should get a waffle tattoo.
-[笑]-我应该纹个华夫饼纹身
-Don't forget your tattoo. -Waffle.
-别忘了你的纹身。华夫饼干。
I -- Believe me. I will not forget my tattoo.
我——相信我。我不会忘记我的纹身。
Uh-huh. And your tattoo artist has been "booked."
啊哈。你的纹身师被预约了
He was booked. And so you won the best waffle cake.
他被预约了。所以你赢得了最佳华夫饼奖。
So I think you should be the first one to see my waffle.
所以我觉得你应该第一个看到我的华夫饼。
All right, here. Yeah.
好了，给你。是的。
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[戏剧音乐播放]
Help me get this off. -Yeah.
帮我把这个脱下来。-是的。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天啊。
So, a couple weeks ago I promised that
所以，几周前我答应过
I would get a waffle tattoo.
我会纹个华夫饼纹身。
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[戏剧音乐播放]
-Oh, my gosh. -There it is.
-哦，我的天哪。-在这儿。
-You actually got the waffle. -You want to come up and see?
-你真的得到了华夫饼。-你想上去看看吗?
Come on up and see it.
上来看看吧。
-It's so cute. -Oh, my God. It's amazing.
-太可爱了。-我的天啊。这是惊人的。
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
It looks so cool. -Right?
看起来很酷。-对吗?
It looks like a waffle, right?
看起来像华夫饼，对吧?
You could still see the redness
你仍然可以看到红色
because he just got it done yesterday.
因为他昨天才做完。
And it looks super cool.
它看起来超级酷。
Team Waffle.
团队华夫饼干。
Every time I see that waffle,
每次我看到华夫饼，
I'll think of you... -Thanks.
我会想你的……-谢谢。
...and my big mouth.
…还有我的大嘴巴。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
So, Aidan, tell us what you made for us today.
艾登，告诉我们你今天为我们做了什么。
You might want to turn the plate around
你最好把盘子转过来
because the powder's supposed to be a smile.
因为粉末应该是微笑的。
-Ohh. -Ohh. Look at that.
-哦。-哦。看那个。
The powder's supposed to be a smile.
粉末应该是微笑的。
-I see it. -It's a mad scientist.
-我看到了。-是个疯狂的科学家。
[ Laughs ] I love it.
(笑)我喜欢。
One eye's kind of...
一只眼睛有点…
He's going mad.
他要疯了。
He's going mad, I tell you.
我告诉你，他快疯了。
Certainly has.
当然有。
I made a deconstructed s'mores tart.
我做了一个解构的s'mores挞。
There is a baked graham-cracker crust.
有一个烤全麦饼干外壳。
I have a smoky chocolate ganache.
我有烟熏巧克力甘纳许。
There is whipped cream on top.
上面有鲜奶油。
And I have a toasty meringue
我还有烤蛋白霜
on the side with peanut butter powder.
配上花生酱粉。
-Wow. -Huh.
-哇。嗯。
-Go for it. -How's that for a bite?
-去吧。-吃一口怎么样?
Do it.
这样做。
Wow.
哇。
I taste the smoke right at the very end.
我在最后一刻尝到了烟味。
I know. It's perfect.
我知道。它是完美的。
It really does taste like
它真的尝起来像
I'm eating s'mores at a campfire.
我在篝火旁吃玉米片。
-Mm-hmm. -Really good.
-嗯。-真的很好。
Your peanut butter powder is awesome.
你的花生酱粉太棒了。
It's nice and peanut buttery.
很好吃，还有花生酱。
This is good, man.
这很好，伙计。
I'm so glad they like it.
我很高兴他们喜欢。
Now, was it intended to be deconstructed?
那么，它是要被解构的吗?
[ Sighs ]
[叹气]
No. It came out a bit crumbly.
不。它出来的时候有点脆。
But if you need to reconstruct it,
但如果你需要重建它，
just deconstruct it.
只要解构它。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Good words to live by.
生活的良言。
Here's the thing, though. I really wish this was a tart
但事情是这样的。我真希望这是个蛋挞
because I feel like I have to work for it.
因为我觉得我必须为之努力。
It's a little work to get to the joy of the flavors.
要体会到味道的乐趣还需要一点功夫。
We're down to the final four. We got to put three through.
我们进入了四强。我们得打通三个。
And we have to look at every single piece of this
我们必须仔细研究每一个细节
and pick it apart.
然后把它拆开。
There's a lot of schmutz.
有很多乱七八糟的东西。
You got, like, chocolate here.
这里有巧克力。
When you're plating, make sure you plate
当你装盘子的时候，一定要装盘子
everything really neat and really clean
一切都非常整洁干净
'cause if you were at a restaurant
因为如果你在餐厅
and that came out, you'd be like,
结果出来了，你会说，
"What? Come on."
“什么?来吧。”
But the flavors are all really there.
但是所有的味道都在那里。
That whipped cream, really well-executed.
鲜奶油，做得很好。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
All right, Aidan. Great job today.
好吧，艾登。今天干得好。
-Thanks. -Great job.
-谢谢。——工作。
-Bye. -Thank you.
再见。-谢谢。
Hey, you want to go out later and get tattoos?
你想待会出去纹个纹身吗?
-Yeah. -All right.
-是的。-好的。
S'more tattoos.
年代' more纹身。
You might want to ask his parents first.
你最好先问问他父母。
-So, you want to talk to Cole? -I would love to talk to Cole.
-你想和科尔谈谈吗?-我想和科尔谈谈。
Hey, Cole.
嘿,科尔。
COLE: This challenge was so stressful.
科尔:这个挑战压力太大了。
I don't like science.
我不喜欢科学。
Okay. So, tell us what you made for us.
好吧。那么，告诉我们你为我们做了什么。
I made a apple pie
我做了一个苹果派
with a classic vanilla ice cream
配上经典的香草冰淇淋
and a peanut butter snow.
还有花生酱雪。
Cole, I got to tell you, man, this is a beautiful plate.
科尔，我得告诉你，这盘子真漂亮。
I like how your pie is very kind of laissez-faire.
我喜欢你的派的自由风格。
It has a very kind of, like, just whimsical feel to it.
它有一种异想天开的感觉。
Yeah. Let's taste it.
是的。让我们尝一尝。
All right. Here's a good bite.
好吧。这里有一口好吃的。
I got ice cream and whipped cream...
我有冰淇淋和生奶油……
-Mm-hmm. -...an apple and the snow.
-嗯。-…一个苹果和雪。
The apples are really infused with a lot of flavor.
这些苹果真的很有味道。
I taste the cinnamon. I taste the nutmeg.
我尝到了肉桂的味道。我尝了尝肉豆蔻。
I taste the simple syrup.
我尝了尝简单的糖浆。
I am missing a little bit more of an apple pie filling.
我还缺一点苹果派馅。
It seems all dry. -You got to have some goo.
看起来都是干的。-你得吃点东西。
Pie needs goo, right?
馅饼需要黏液，对吧?
There's got to be goo, right? You sous vide the apples.
肯定有好的，对吧?你把苹果煮熟了。
You cooked them in a simple syrup.
你用简单的糖浆煮了它们。
You take that simple syrup out,
把简单的糖浆拿出来，
make a slurry with some cornstarch.
用一些玉米淀粉做成浆料。
Thicken it up, add it to your apples.
把它调稠，加到苹果里。
You would've had a pie filling.
你会有一个馅饼馅。
But your ice cream on the other hand, whoa.
但另一方面，你的冰淇淋，哇。
That is a perfect vanilla ice cream.
这是一个完美的香草冰淇淋。
And it's so good with the peanut butter snow on it.
涂上花生酱的雪真是太好吃了。
I love the two flavors together. -Thank you.
我喜欢这两种味道混合在一起。-谢谢。
Cole, I shouldn't be able to do this.
科尔，我不该这么做的。
That's dough.
这是面团。
Wait, what?
等等,什么?
I'm sorry, man.
对不起，伙计。
This is raw pie dough.
这是生派面团。
-I know. Shoot. -Raw pie dough.
-我知道。开枪。-生馅饼面团。
What is happening right now?
现在发生了什么?
This guy should've been in the oven right away.
这家伙现在就该进烤箱了。
You could've baked this thing
你可以烤这个东西
till it was nice and golden-brown.
直到它变成漂亮的金棕色。
You could've baked a separate lattice by itself
你可以单独烤一个晶格
till it was nice and golden-brown,
直到它变成金黄色，
then taken those apples, put them in here.
然后把苹果拿出来，放在这里。
Okay. But, man, this ice cream is fantastic.
好吧。但是，伙计，这冰淇淋太棒了。
I'll dip the crust in the vanilla ice cream
我要把面包皮浸在香草冰淇淋里
'cause it's so good.
因为它太棒了。
Thank you, Cole.
谢谢你，科尔。
-Thanks, Cole. -Thank you.
-谢谢,科尔。-谢谢。
They said a few positive things.
他们说了一些积极的事情。
So I just really,
所以我真的，
really hope it's enough to get me to the finale.
真希望这足以让我进入决赛。
Let's see who else is coming.
让我们看看还有谁来。
Justice.
正义。
How was your day today?
你今天过得怎么样?
-Good, really good. -Really good?
-很好，非常好。-真的好吗?
Yeah. I think we'll be the judge of that.
是的。我想我们自己来判断吧。
-What did you make today? -Apple cobbler.
你今天做了什么?-苹果鞋匠。
So I used an immersion circulator.
所以我用了浸入式循环器。
And so all those flavors would be, like,
所以所有的口味都像是，
in there and taste super good.
在里面，味道超级好。
And a whipped cream.
再来一杯鲜奶油。
And then the smoker seems really fun.
然后吸烟者看起来很有趣。
So I used the smoker for the leftover apples I had
所以我用烟熏我剩下的苹果
in a smoked-apple ice cream.
在烟熏苹果冰淇淋里。
That's the best whipped cream I've seen today.
这是我今天见过的最好的生奶油。
Well, he's a beast. Look at him. Let me see that thing.
他是只野兽。看看他。让我看看那个东西。
That is insane. Look at that whipped cream.
这太疯狂了。看那鲜奶油。
Yeah. Look at him. He's a beast.
是的。看看他。他是一头野兽。
[ Both laugh ]
[两人笑]
Let's taste it.
让我们尝一尝。
Mmm. It's got a lot of nice flavor.
嗯。它的味道很好。
Tell me the spices you used in your cobbler.
告诉我你做皮匠用了什么香料。
Cinnamon, nutmeg, and ground mace.
肉桂，肉豆蔻和肉豆蔻粉。
-Ground mace? -Yeah.
背景锏?-是的。
Well, it's seasoned very well.
嗯，调味得很好。
I could eat just these apples alone
我一个人就能吃下这些苹果
without anything else on them.
上面没有任何其他东西。
I knew they would like my apples.
我知道他们会喜欢我的苹果。
I was eating them during the whole bake.
我在整个烘焙过程中都在吃。
I knew they were amazing.
我知道他们很了不起。
Now, you make a biscuit-style cobbler.
现在，你要做饼干式的馅饼。
It's more of, like, a scone batter, I think,
我觉得它更像是烤饼面糊，
'cause it has sugar in it.
因为里面有糖。
And normally biscuits don't have sugar in them.
通常饼干是不含糖的。
When I do a cobbler,
当我做补鞋匠的时候，
I almost do like a cake batter on top. Ooh.
我喜欢在上面放蛋糕面糊。哦。
So you have two schools of thought here.
这里有两种思想流派。
Sure. I mean, some people do biscuits on top.
确定。我是说，有些人会在上面放饼干。
It's cool.
天气凉爽。
Trust me. It tastes really good.
相信我。味道真的很好。
The ice cream is cute with the little piece of apple.
有一小块苹果的冰淇淋很可爱。
It's gone a little brown.
有点发黄了。
So I don't know that I would've put it on top.
所以我不知道我会不会把它放在最上面。
Used the smoker on the ice cream?
用烟熏冰淇淋吗?
I don't taste a lot of smoke.
我尝不出烟味。
It's, like, barely there at the end.
就像，最后几乎没有。
What's this little guy?
这个小家伙是什么?
Oh. I was trying to make a ganache.
哦。我在做巧克力酱。
And it turned to soupy water.
它变成了浑浊的水。
I think I was kind of angry at the ganache.
我想我是对巧克力酱有点生气。
So I just decided,
所以我决定，
"I'm just gonna use a little chocolate."
“我要用一点巧克力。”
I get angry at my food all the time.
我总是对我的食物生气。
"Stop. Stop calling my name.
“停止。别叫我的名字。
Leave me alone."
别烦我。”
This thing, we don't need that.
这个东西，我们不需要。
-Yeah. No. -We're good.
-是的。不。我们很好。
Thank you, Justice.
谢谢你，法官。
Thanks, Justice.
谢谢,正义。
Let's bring in Kaniyah.
让我们把Kaniyah请进来。
Someone is sassy.
有人很时髦。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
So, Kaniyah, what did you make today?
那么，Kaniyah，你今天做了什么?
I made a smoked-berry pie
我做了一个烟熏浆果派
with a chocolate-hazelnut spread snow
用巧克力榛子涂抹雪
with a raspberry
还有覆盆子
and a little bit of blackberry ice cream
再来点黑莓冰淇淋
and whipped cream.
还有鲜奶油。
All right. I'd say we dig into this pie.
好吧。要我说，我们得好好研究这个派。
Let's dig in.
让我们开始吧。
I like pie and ice cream together.
我喜欢派和冰淇淋一起吃。
Pie à la mode.
馅饼:la模式。
Is it done?
完成了吗?
Well, let me get it in my mouth.
好吧，让我把它放进嘴里。
And I'll tell you. -Well, eat it fast.
我来告诉你。-快吃吧。
Stop giving me that look.
别那样看着我。
Say you like it and move on with your life.
说你喜欢它，然后继续你的生活。
ANNOUNCER: The winner of the "Kids Baking Championship"
播音员:“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军
will receive a sweet prize package... DUFF: Yeah!
将会收到一个甜蜜的奖品包…达夫:是啊!
...that includes a feature story in Food Network Magazine...
…包括《美食网络杂志》的一篇专题报道……
Hallelujah.
哈利路亚。
-...and... -$25,000.
-……——25000美元。
[ Cheering ]
[欢呼]
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Winner is coming.
赢家来了。
Stop giving me that look.
别那样看着我。
I just can barely detect the smoking.
我几乎察觉不到烟味。
Maybe it could have been hiked up just a tiny bit.
也许它可以再高一点。
-Okay. -But I love the ice cream.
-好的。-但我喜欢冰淇淋。
I see you trying to whip the cream.
我看到你在搅奶油。
Aidan came over and helped you.
艾登过来帮了你
-Yeah. -How about that?
-是的。-怎么样?
That was pretty nice. -Yeah. He's a good dude.
那很不错。-是的。他是个好人。
And I really like your hazelnut-chocolate snow.
我很喜欢你的榛子巧克力雪。
How did you make the snow?
你是怎么造雪的?
Um, tapioca maltrodesh.
嗯，木薯粉。
Maltodextrin.
麦芽糊精。
-Tapioca.
木薯。木薯。
-"Malodextrin." -Maltodextrin.
——“Malodextrin”。麦芽糊精。
-Malto.
-Malto。麦芽糊精。
-Well done. -Good job.
-嗯。改善工作。
I did it.
我做到了。
Kaniyah, I like the chocolate-hazelnut
Kaniyah，我喜欢榛子巧克力
with the berries.
还有浆果。
You know, chocolate and berries always goes really good.
你知道，巧克力和浆果总是很好吃的。
That's what I said.
我就是这么说的。
Your pie crust is very tender.
你的派皮很软。
You didn't knead it too much.
你揉得不多。
So it didn't get really tough.
所以事情并没有变得很艰难。
That being said, there's no seasoning in there.
也就是说，里面没有调味料。
I think a little bit of cinnamon
我想加一点肉桂
and just something in there
里面有东西
to make it a little more interesting.
让它更有趣一点。
It makes your pie just a little more complicated,
这会让你的派更复杂，
which is a lot like you, complicated.
这很像你，很复杂。
You're complicated.
你是复杂的。
Sometimes sweet, sometimes not.
有时甜蜜，有时不甜蜜。
Always intense.
总是紧张。
-Thanks, Kaniyah. -Thank you so much, Kaniyah.
-谢谢,Kaniyah。-非常感谢，Kaniyah。
You're welcome.
不客气
That is one of a kind.
那是独一无二的。
Love her.
爱她。
Whatcha think?
到了以后觉得怎么样?
Well, you know, this is a really important decision, you know,
你知道，这是一个非常重要的决定，
because we're gonna decide
因为我们要做出决定
who's going into the finale.
谁将进入决赛。
So let's talk about whose experiment succeeded today.
那么我们来谈谈今天谁的实验成功了。
Justice.
正义。
I loved that apple cobbler.
我喜欢那个苹果馅饼。
There was so much flavor in the apples.
苹果的味道很好。
Mmm. It's super good.
嗯。超级好吃。
However, I don't know that I tasted
然而，我不知道我尝过
a lot of smoke in the ice cream.
冰淇淋里有很多烟。
You don't want it to taste like charred wood.
你肯定不希望它尝起来像烧焦的木头。
You almost couldn't taste it though,
你几乎尝不出它的味道，
unlike Aidan's dessert,
不像艾登的甜点
where you tasted the chocolate. It was delicious.
你品尝巧克力的地方。味道很好。
And then at the very end, you got that smoke.
然后在最后，你会看到烟雾。
It's smoky. It's good.
这是烟雾缭绕。很好。
It's really smart because you make s'mores at a campfire.
这很聪明，因为你会在篝火上做s'mores。
-Right. -I tell you what, though.
-对。-我告诉你吧。
Kaniyah had a pretty bad day.
Kaniyah今天过得很糟糕。
-Oh, poor Kaniyah. -You know, listen.
-哦，可怜的Kaniyah。-你知道，听着。
For me, Kaniyah's pie just wasn't successful.
对我来说，Kaniyah的派并不成功。
The challenge was she had to get whipped cream on the plate.
挑战是她必须把鲜奶油放到盘子里。
And she did.
她照做了。
But we both know that Aidan came over and had to help her out.
但我们都知道艾登过来帮了她。
Well, he whipped the cream. But she flavored it.
嗯，他打了奶油。但她给它加了调味。
I know. I'm -- I'm reaching.
我知道。我——我在伸手。
I mean, there's $25,000 at stake.
这可是两万五千美元的赌注。
Got to be perfect. -It wasn't real successful.
一定要完美。-不是很成功。
Let's discuss Cole.
我们来谈谈科尔吧。
Right.
正确的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Cole gave us a raw crust.
科尔给了我们一块生皮。
And in week one, that's okay.
在第一周，这是可以的。
In the semis, that is not okay.
在半决赛中，这是不行的。
Yeah. I'm surprised.
是的。我感到惊讶。
But the apples were really, really delicious.
但是苹果真的非常非常好吃。
Listen, apple pie needs goo.
听着，苹果派需要黏液。
Apple pie filling is more than just apples.
苹果派的馅料不仅仅是苹果。
Well, you can't get everything you like in life, Duff.
你不可能得到你想要的一切，达夫。
You know, you can't always get what you want.
你知道，你不可能总是得到你想要的。
Yeah.
是的。
All right, Val.
好吧，瓦尔。
This is not a decision we can make lightly.
这不是我们可以轻易做出的决定。
Someone should have a talk with these kids
应该有人跟这些孩子谈谈
and tell them to make it a little easier on us.
告诉他们让我们好受点。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
**
**
Today we asked you, the final four,
今天我们问你们，四强，
to create something that even many professional bakers
创造出许多专业的面包师
have a tough time with,
遇到困难
a molecular-gastronomy dessert.
分子美食甜点。
Not easy.
不容易的。
Today, one baker's dessert was delicious enough
今天，一个面包师的甜点已经足够美味了
to be considered a gastronomic grade "A."
被认为是a级美食
And that baker is...
那个面包师是……
Aidan.
艾丹。
-Yes! -Congratulations.
-是的!祝贺你。
You have secured your spot in the finale.
你已经确定了进入决赛的机会。
Whew! I thought I did really well.
唷!我认为我做得很好。
Your modernist take on s'mores was really awesome.
你对s'mores的现代主义诠释太棒了。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
How you feeling?
你感觉怎么样?
Pretty great.
好极了。
Justice, Cole, and Kaniyah, please step forward.
Justice, Cole和Kaniyah，请上前。
Each and every one of you are very talented bakers.
你们每个人都是非常有天赋的面包师。
But today, the three of you,
但今天，你们三个，
well, you had a few mistakes.
你犯了一些错误。
DUFF: Justice, there wasn't a lot of smoke
达夫:法官，没有很多烟
in the smoked-apple ice cream.
在烟熏苹果冰淇淋里。
But the immersion circulator helped to infuse
但是浸入式循环器帮助注入
a nice level of spice right into your apples.
苹果的香料恰到好处。
That spice and your perfect whipped cream
香料和你完美的鲜奶油
were enough to keep you in the competition.
足以让你继续竞争。
[ Gasps ] Thank you so much.
(喘息)非常感谢。
You're in the finale, dude.
你进入决赛了，伙计。
Yes!
是的!
So now it comes down to Cole and Kaniyah.
现在轮到科尔和卡尼亚了。
This is my worst moment at the "Kids Baking Championship."
这是我在"儿童烘焙锦标赛"上最糟糕的时刻
I can't go home.
我不能回家。
Kaniyah, your raspberry ice cream was tasty.
卡尼亚，你的覆盆子冰淇淋很好吃。
And we liked your chocolate-hazelnut snow.
我们喜欢你的巧克力榛子雪。
But we could barely detect smoke in your smoked-berry pie.
但我们几乎没在你的烟熏浆果派里发现烟味。
Cole, you presented a beautiful plate.
科尔，你的盘子很漂亮。
And the apple pie had very nice flavor.
苹果派味道很好。
But your dough was underbaked
但你的面团没烤好
and raw in some spots.
有些地方还是生的。
Unfortunately, only one of you
不幸的是，只有一个人
can move on to next week's finale.
可以进入下周的决赛了。
**
**
Please.
请。
Kaniyah...
Kaniyah……
you're safe.
你是安全的。
Cole, I'm sorry. You'll be leaving us.
科尔，我很抱歉。你要离开我们了。
Cole, you are an awesome baker.
科尔，你是个很棒的面包师。
You just had a bad day today.
你今天过得很糟糕。
I'm shocked.
我很震惊。
I didn't think I would be going home
我以为我回不了家了
till I had a check in my hands.
直到我拿到支票
-You're awesome, man. -You're amazing.
-你太棒了。你真了不起。
I'm proud of myself for making it this far.
我为自己能走到这一步感到骄傲。
I'm gonna keep baking and lots of glitter.
我要继续烤，加很多亮片。
Wow. That was tough.
哇。这很艰难。
I think that was probably the hardest one we've ever done.
我想这可能是我们做过的最难的一个。
That was -- that was tough.
那是，那是艰难的。
It's really hard to say goodbye.
说再见真的很难。
And you guys should feel really good right now
你们现在应该感觉很好
'cause that dude was good.
因为那家伙很棒。
AIDAN: It is shocking to see Cole leave.
艾丹:科尔的离开让我很震惊。
He is super talented.
他超级有天赋。
Bakers, you made it to the finale.
贝克斯，你们进入了决赛。
-Yay! -Yes!
耶!-是的!
We made it to the finale!
我们进入了决赛!
Now one of you will become Kids Baking Champion
现在你们中的一个将成为儿童烘焙冠军
and take home $25,000.
然后拿25000美元回家。
Now skedaddle. We'll see you next week.
现在逃走。我们下周见。
-Bye.
再见。再见。
* We made it, we made it *
我们成功了，我们成功了
ANNOUNCER: Previously on "Kids Baking Championship"...
“儿童烘焙锦标赛”前情提要……
They've gone mad! DUFF: Each of you must make
他们疯了!达夫:你们每个人都必须做出决定
a molecular gastronomy dessert.
分子美食甜点。
What?
怎么啦？
Oh, my God! What's wrong?
我的天啊!怎么了?
I ruined my whipped cream!
我毁了我的鲜奶油!
Kaniyah, I'm coming!
Kaniyah，我来了!
VALERIE: Wow! I taste the smoke.
瓦莱丽:哇!我闻到了烟味。
DUFF: It really does taste like
达夫:它确实尝起来像
I'm eating a s'mores at a campfire.
我在篝火旁吃果仁饼干。
Best in show, Aidan. Yes.
最好的表演，艾登。是的。
DUFF: Cole, I'm sorry, man. This is raw.
达夫:科尔，我很抱歉，伙计。这是生的。
Cole, you'll be leaving us.
科尔，你要离开我们了。
Are you ready for this? Yes.
你准备好了吗?是的。
I'm about to break through this Styrofoam brick wall
我要冲破这堵泡沫塑料砖墙了
to make a huge entrance on "Kid Baking Championship."
在"儿童烘焙锦标赛"上大放异彩
I was a nose tackle in high school,
我高中时是铲鼻子队员，
but that's the last time I had to really
但那是我最后一次真的
bust through anything, so I'll see what happens.
冲破任何障碍，所以我看看会发生什么。
Are you scared? I'm a little scared.
你害怕吗?我有点害怕。
But I'm excited. But I'm nervous.
但我很兴奋。但是我很紧张。
Just do me a favor. Uh-huh.
帮我个忙。啊哈。
Please make sure you're not standing in front of this thing.
请确保你没有站在这东西前面。
Oh, please. You won't hurt me.
哦,请。你不会伤害我的。
I have three brothers. You can't hurt me.
我有三个兄弟。你伤害不了我。
All right. That's a battle of physics
好吧。这是一场物理之战
that you're not going to win, Valerie.
你赢不了的，瓦莱丽
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
All right, here it goes.
好了，开始吧。
Whoa. What...
哇。什么……
What is this madness?
这是什么疯狂?
Welcome back, Justice, Kaniyah, and Aidan.
欢迎回来，Justice, Kaniyah和Aidan。
Yay!
耶!
You are the final three.
你们是最后三名。
* Wag waga waga waga *
*哇哇哇哇哇哇
* I made it to the finale *
我进入了决赛
* And I'm going to take home some money *
我要带些钱回家
I know how to bake.
我知道怎么烤。
VALERIE: One of you will be leaving here
瓦莱丽:你们中的一个要离开这里
with $25,000 and the title
25000美元和冠军头衔
of Kids Baking Champion.
儿童烘焙冠军。
Yes!
是的!是的!
Because you are all baking superheroes, like me.
因为你们都是超级英雄，就像我一样。
I am secretly Valerie Cake Crusader.
我其实是瓦莱丽·蛋糕十字军。
Crusader?
十字军?
That's one of the most cheesiest names
这是最俗气的名字之一
I've ever heard.
我听过的最好的。
I shoot doughnuts and other cake-y treats.
我拍甜甜圈和其他蛋糕。
And if my doughnut touches you,
如果我的甜甜圈碰到你
you have magical powers for only 10 seconds.
你的魔力只有10秒。
[ Kids screaming ]
[孩子们尖叫]
Oh, snap! How's it going, bakers?
哦,提前!最近怎么样，面包师们?
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my God.
哦，天哪!我的天啊。
Okay, bakers, today is all about superheroes.
好了，面包师们，今天的主题是超级英雄。
You have overcome nine weeks of intense challenges
你们已经克服了九个星期的严峻挑战
and revealed a level of energy
显示出一种能量
and determination that is almost superhuman.
这几乎是超人的决心。
And I should know, because my alter ego
我应该知道，因为我的另一个自我
is Dessert Man!
是甜点男!
So what's your superpowers?
你有什么超能力?
Did you not see me just bust through that wall?
你没看见我刚冲过那堵墙吗?
Oh, yeah. He busts through walls
哦,是的。他能穿墙而过
and eats cookies all day!
整天吃饼干!
Desserts fuel my superhuman strength.
甜点给了我超人的力量。
[ Grunts ]
[咕噜声]
We're giving you five hours.
我们给你五个小时。
[ Gasps ] Five hours.
[喘气]五个小时。
Hours? VALERIE: Five hours
小时?瓦莱丽:五个小时
to create an original superhero cake.
做一个原创的超级英雄蛋糕。
What?
怎么啦？怎么啦？
AIDAN: I'm less into superheroes and more into baking,
艾丹:我不太喜欢超级英雄，我更喜欢烘焙，
so I'm really nervous about this challenge
所以我对这个挑战很紧张
because I have no clue what I'm going to do.
因为我不知道我要做什么。
And your baking time starts...
你的烘焙时间开始了…
Now! Aaaah!
现在!啊!
I have no clue what my superhero's going to be,
我不知道我的超级英雄会是谁，
but I do know I want to make a lemon rosemary olive oil cake.
但我知道我想做一个柠檬迷迭香橄榄油蛋糕。
We have to create a unique superhero
我们得创造一个独一无二的超级英雄
on our cake in some way.
在我们的蛋糕上。
I'm going to make a mascarpone frosting.
我要做马斯卡彭奶酪糖霜。
Sound yummy?
听起来美味吗?
I want to do lemon, rosemary, olive oil
我想加入柠檬，迷迭香，橄榄油
because I want something bold and different for the finale.
因为我想要一个大胆而与众不同的结局。
I mix flour, sugar, eggs,
我把面粉，糖，鸡蛋，
salt, buttermilk, baking powder,
盐，酪乳，发酵粉，
replace the butter with olive oil,
用橄榄油代替黄油，
and then a little bit of rosemary.
再放一点迷迭香。
Ah, rosemary.
啊,迷迭香。
I'm just going to cut up a little bit.
我要把它切成一小块。
Don't want to overpower it.
我不想压制它。
I just take a couple teaspoons of rosemary,
我只需要几茶匙迷迭香，
because a little bit goes a long way.
因为一点点就能走很长的路。
Delicious lemon zest.
美味的柠檬皮。
I'm adding a bunch of lemon zest,
我要加一些柠檬皮，
and, to have a really strong lemon flavor,
要想有浓郁的柠檬味，
I'm going to add some lemon juice,
我要加点柠檬汁，
'cause Valerie loves lemons.
因为瓦莱丽喜欢柠檬。
My inspiration behind this cake
这是我的灵感来源
is how Valerie loves lemons.
就是瓦莱丽喜欢柠檬的原因
If I can execute this cake perfectly,
如果我能完美地制作这个蛋糕，
it will stand out and I'll win.
它会脱颖而出，我会赢。
Mm, mm, mm.
嗯，嗯，嗯。
Aidan's making lemon rosemary olive oil cake.
艾登在做柠檬迷迭香橄榄油蛋糕。
That makes me very happy.
这让我很高兴。
You know, olive oil cakes have such a nice texture.
你知道，橄榄油蛋糕的口感很好。
And they're so moist if you make them right.
如果你做对了，它们会非常湿润。
If you make them right.
如果你做对了。
AIDAN: Into the oven.
艾丹:放进烤箱。
Okay.
好吧。
All the big bakes have been important,
所有的大蛋糕都很重要，
but right now, this is the only one that matters.
但现在，这是唯一重要的。
I'm making a lemon blueberry infused with rosemary cake
我在做柠檬蓝莓迷迭香蛋糕
with a lemon icing.
加上柠檬糖霜。
I'm doing lemon.
我要做柠檬汁。
What?
怎么啦？
I'm actually doing lemon, olive oil, rosemary.
我用的是柠檬，橄榄油，迷迭香。
Ah. Aidan, sorry.
啊。艾丹,对不起。
My cake is going to wow the judges.
我的蛋糕会让评委们大吃一惊的。
I put rosemary, lemon, and blueberries
我放了迷迭香、柠檬和蓝莓
in a bag together
放在一个袋子里
and I put it in the immersion circulator.
我把它放进浸入式循环器里。
That thing is really cool.
那东西真的很酷。
It infuses blueberries with a flavor in no time.
它很快就给蓝莓注入了一种味道。
VALERIE: Look what Kaniyah's doing!
瓦莱丽:看凯妮雅在做什么!
So she had so much fun last week
所以她上周玩得很开心
with the immersion circulator
带浸入式循环器
that she is using it again this week.
她这周又用了。
I'm really excited that --
我真的很兴奋——
that they're thinking about flavor.
他们考虑的是味道。
My superhero is Catastrophe Girl.
我的超级英雄是灾难女孩。
It goes through town,
它穿过城镇，
trying to save the catastrophe from happening.
试图阻止灾难的发生。
Hopefully there will be no catastrophes
希望不会发生灾难
for my Catastrophe Girl cake.
我的大灾难女孩蛋糕
Ah!
啊!
I get my batter in a pan
我把面糊放在平底锅里
and I plop my blueberries on top.
然后把蓝莓放在上面。
There's no system to putting these blueberries in my cake.
没有办法把蓝莓放进我的蛋糕里。
Put 'em in and you push them down!
把它们放进去，然后把它们压下去!
How's it going, Kaniyah? Need to put your timer on?
最近怎么样，Kaniyah?需要设置计时器吗?
Mm...
毫米…
I freehand mine.
我是徒手的。
Really? Well, so who's your superhero?
真的吗?那么谁是你的超级英雄?
Catastrophe Girl. Catastrophe Girl?
灾难的女孩。灾难的女孩吗?
Yep. She comes around and fixes catastrophes.
是的。她来解决灾难。
Oh, okay.
哦,好的。
Has she been in your station? It looks like it.
她到过你的岗位吗?看起来是这样。
Yes.
是的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
Okay. Yep.
好吧。是的。
What does Catastrophe Girl do?
灾难女孩是做什么的?
She helps the world with catastrophes.
她帮助世界应对灾难。
So, like, if there was, like, a fire,
所以，如果发生了火灾，
she would go help the people where the fire was?
她会去帮助火灾现场的人们吗?
Yes. Oh, cool.
是的。哦,很酷。
My superhero is Weather Man.
我的超级英雄是天气预报员。
Weather Man.
天气预报员。
My inspiration behind this cake
这是我的灵感来源
is my passion for weather.
是我对天气的热爱。
I literally, every single day that I have free time,
我每天只要有空闲时间，
just read about weather,
看看天气，
look up stuff about weather, look outside at the weather.
查阅有关天气的资料，看看外面的天气。
I really love weather.
我真的很喜欢天气。
Justice, what kind of cake are you making?
正义先生，你在做什么样的蛋糕?
Rose cake. I'm just going to see how that goes.
玫瑰蛋糕。我只是想看看结果如何。
Ooh, rose, yeah, that's a sophisticated flavor.
玫瑰色，是啊，很高级的味道。
I will be making a three-tiered rose cake.
我要做一个三层玫瑰蛋糕。
I quadrupled the cake recipe.
我把蛋糕的配方改了四倍。
I feel like this cake is going to be huge!
我觉得这个蛋糕会很大!
And that's exactly what I want.
这正是我想要的。
I'm using rose flavoring
我用的是玫瑰香精
because I think it's a nice, elegant flavor,
因为我觉得味道很好，很优雅，
and rose also represents hope, love, and balance.
玫瑰也代表着希望、爱和平衡。
That's the doing of the Weather Man.
这是天气预报员的功劳。
It's so important to taste while you're baking,
烘焙的时候尝味道很重要，
because if you say, "It's a rose cake,"
因为如果你说"这是玫瑰蛋糕"
and they're like, "I don't taste any rose"...
他们说，“我没有玫瑰的味道”……
You have to make sure it tastes like what you're saying.
你得确保它尝起来像你说的那样。
Hello, Justice. Hello.
你好,正义。你好。
So I'm wondering, how badly do you really want to win this?
所以我在想，你到底有多想赢得这场比赛?
I really infinity really want to win this.
我真的很想赢。
Why? I want to be the first boy to win.
为什么?我想成为第一个获胜的男孩。
I want to buy my goat.
我想买我的山羊。
Do your parents know
你父母知道吗?
that your farm will be expanding?
你的农场要扩张了?
Maybe. I don't know. You haven't talked to 'em yet?
也许吧。我不知道。你还没跟他们谈过吗?
Not really. Okay.
不是真的。好吧。
Well, we'll -- we'll start with the first thing,
好吧，我们从第一件事开始，
and first you've got to win it.
首先你得赢得比赛。
Yep. So I'll leave you alone.
是的。所以我不打扰你了。
Okay.
好吧。
So are you really going to get a goat if you win?
如果你赢了，你真的会得到一只山羊吗?
Yeah.
是的。
What would you get if you won?
如果你赢了，你会得到什么?
I don't know. Hey.
我不知道。嘿。
If you don't know, maybe you can just buy me a goat if you win.
如果你不知道，如果你赢了，也许你可以给我买只山羊。
What would you do with $25,000 at 12 years old?
你12岁的时候会拿25000美元做什么?
Okay, besides put it away
好吧，还有，把它收起来
and save for college or, you know...
存点钱上大学，或者…
No, 'cause I'm thinking that's what I did.
不，因为我觉得我就是这么做的。
Donate it to the... 'Cause I was working.
把它捐给……因为我在工作。
I was doing commercials when I was 12 years old.
我12岁的时候就开始拍广告了。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
So I was already working.
所以我已经开始工作了。
Oh, my God. I'm so tired.
我的天啊。我太累了。
I need to stop working already!
我得停止工作了!
Four hours left, bakers!
还有四个小时，面包师们!
Original superhero cakes!
原创的超级英雄蛋糕!
JUSTICE: Four hours left and I'm just getting my cakes in the oven,
法官:还有四个小时，我正要把蛋糕放进烤箱，
'cause I had to make a lot of cake batter.
因为我要做很多蛋糕糊。
Who's a baking superhero?
谁是烘焙超级英雄?
-I am!
我是!我是!
-Me! -Everything's in the oven
加!-所有东西都在烤箱里
and I need to get started on my frosting.
我得开始做糖霜了
I'm thinking of mascarpone
我在想马斯卡彭奶酪
because I've seen mascarpone and lemon used a lot,
因为我见过马斯卡彭奶酪和柠檬用得很多，
so I want this to be really fancy.
所以我想让它很别致。
Aidan. What's going on, man? Hi.
艾丹。怎么了，伙计?嗨。
Um, 'bout to start my frosting.
我要开始做糖霜了
Okay. And I'm going to make a mascarpone frosting.
好吧。我要做马斯卡彭奶酪糖霜。
Wow. Yum.
哇。好吃。
That's elevated.
这是升高的。
I'm going to put that on my menu.
我要把它放在我的菜单上。
I'm excited about this cake.
我对这个蛋糕很兴奋。
I'm very excited Thanks.
我对这个蛋糕很兴奋。谢谢。
Sounds delicious. Keep going, Aidan.
听起来很好吃。继续，艾登。
Thank you. All right.
谢谢你！好吧。
I need to make a huge batch of frosting.
我要做一大批糖霜。
I'm just going to put mascarpone and butter,
我要放马斯卡彭奶酪和黄油，
whip that up, and slowly sweeten it
搅拌一下，慢慢加糖
with powdered sugar.
加糖粉。
You know, I don't know if this is going to work.
你知道，我不知道这能不能成功。
I'm mixing my mascarpone buttercream,
我在搅拌马斯卡彭奶酪，
and it's yellow and thick and gross.
它又黄又厚又恶心。
What the heck am I doing?
我到底在做什么?
I need to start a new batch of frosting.
我得重新做一批糖霜。
This isn't working.
这行不通。
I'm just going to scrap this completely
我要把这个完全扔掉
and stick with my tried and true buttercream recipe.
坚持我久经考验的正宗奶油配方。
Shoot, I need a double... ooh!
该死，我需要一个替身…噢!
I almost walked in on your station!
我差点走进你的电视台!
What am I doing?
我在做什么?
What on Earth am I doing right now?
我现在到底在干什么?
I can do this.
我能做到。
Your cakes are going to be great.
你的蛋糕会很棒的。
My Swiss buttercream, I've made it a lot in the KBC.
瑞士奶油，我在KBC做过很多次。
Let's -- let me think about it. I'll be -- I'll be right back.
让我想想。我，我马上回来。
Okay. I've made it one,
好吧。我把它变成了一个，
two... Ooh, yummy.
两个……哦,美味。
I've made it three times -- four times already.
我已经成功三次了，已经四次了。
All the time, it's come out perfect,
一直以来，结果都很完美
so I'm just going to do that again.
所以我要再做一次。
To make my frosting, going to heat up egg whites
要做糖霜，先加热蛋白
and sugar, whip those into a meringue,
还有糖，把它们打成蛋白霜，
add my butter, and boom,
加入黄油，砰，
you have a nice, delicious buttercream.
你就有了美味的奶油。
I'm kind of sad that the mascarpone didn't work out,
我有点难过马斯卡彭奶酪没做成，
but I'm dressed and I did not want to spend more time
但我已经穿好衣服了，我不想再花时间了
on something that might not come out.
在一些可能不会说出来的事情上。
Nothing else could go wrong.
没有别的事情会出错。
There's no room for mistakes now.
现在没有犯错的余地了。
What's that smell?
那是什么味道?
There's a weird smell,
有一股奇怪的味道，
and it is freaking me out.
这把我吓坏了。
What did you smell, Aidan?
艾登，你闻到什么了?
It smells like scrambled eggs.
闻起来像炒鸡蛋。
DUFF: Scrambled eggs?
达夫:炒鸡蛋?
Somebody scramble their cake?
有人在炒蛋糕吗?
Hope it's not my cakes.
希望不是我的蛋糕。
Oh, it -- it smells like scrambled eggs in here.
这，这闻起来像炒蛋。
If you smell scrambled eggs, you probably have
如果你闻到了炒鸡蛋的味道，你可能有
some serious issues with your cake.
你的蛋糕出了严重的问题。
I may have to restart my cakes.
我可能得重新做蛋糕了。
I am so scared right now.
我现在好害怕。
I'm second-guessing myself.
我在事后怀疑自己。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
Something smells like scrambled eggs.
有东西闻起来像炒鸡蛋。
I may have to restart my cakes.
我可能得重新做蛋糕了。
DUFF: * Duh-duh-duh-duh! *
DUFF: * Duh-duh-duh-duh -duh!＊
Three hours and 30 minutes left!
还剩3小时30分钟!
Looks pretty good!
看起来很不错!
Original superhero cakes! Good.
原创的超级英雄蛋糕!好。
I'm worried that I put too much rosemary in.
我担心我放了太多迷迭香。
VALERIE: Well, get 'em done!
瓦莱丽:好吧，把它们做完!
What's going on with Aidan?
艾登怎么了?
Why does it smell bad in here?
为什么这里有股臭味?
Hey, buddy. What's going on?
嘿,哥们。这是怎么呢
I'm a little worried there's too much rosemary in my cake.
我有点担心我的蛋糕里迷迭香放多了。
It smells like scrambled eggs in here.
这里闻起来像炒鸡蛋。
VALERIE: The aroma of rosemary is much stronger
瓦莱丽:迷迭香的香味更浓
than the actual taste of it.
而不是真正的味道。
Okay. Don't want you to second-guess yourself too much.
好吧。我不想让你太怀疑自己。
Trust yourself. You've got good instincts.
相信自己。你的直觉很准。
Valerie says that my cakes are good,
瓦莱丽说我的蛋糕很好吃，
but I still smell scrambled eggs,
但我还能闻到炒蛋的味道
so I'm kind of freaking out.
所以我有点害怕。
If I make a mistake, there's no doubt about it,
如果我犯了错，毫无疑问，
I'm not going to win,
我不会赢的
so everything has to be flawless.
所以每件事都必须完美无缺。
No! They're burnt.
不!他们烧。
I am flipping the freak out,
我快疯了
ultimate terror moment.
终极恐怖时刻。
I ruined 'em.
我毁了他们。
I don't feel so good.
我感觉不太好。
It's one thing to burn a cake at home,
在家里烤蛋糕是一回事，
but it's another huge thing
但这是另一件大事
to burn a cake in the finale of the KBC.
在KBC的最后一集里烤蛋糕
My cakes are really brown.
我的蛋糕是棕色的。
I'm just going to shave it off.
我要把它刮掉。
I have to fix these burnt cakes,
我得把烤焦的蛋糕修好，
so I'm going to shave off the burnt part
所以我要把烧焦的部分刮掉
and put simple syrup in the middle.
中间放点糖浆。
Okay. I can do this.
好吧。我能做到。
Simple syrup is just water and sugar, boiled and cooled,
简单的糖浆就是水和糖，煮沸并冷却，
and it helps keep any cake, even burnt cakes, moist.
它能让蛋糕保持湿润，即使是烧焦的蛋糕。
I'm assembling my cake tiers
我在组装蛋糕层
by putting cake, simple syrup, frosting.
把蛋糕，简单的糖浆，糖霜。
I might be making myself be a little bit more nervous
我可能让自己更紧张了
than I need to be, but this is the finale
但这是最后一场了
and everything matters here.
这里的一切都很重要。
VALERIE: Three hours left, bakers!
瓦莱丽:还有三个小时，面包师们!
Show us you are a baking superhero!
让我们看看你是一个烘焙超级英雄!
My rose cakes are done,
我的玫瑰蛋糕做好了，
so I cut off the top to get it as flat as possible.
所以我把顶部切掉，让它尽可能地平整。
Yum.
好吃。
It tastes exactly the way it's supposed to be.
它的味道就是它应该有的味道。
I really taste the rose.
我真的尝到了玫瑰的味道。
It's really good. It's really moist.
真的很好吃。真的很潮湿。
DUFF: What's Kaniyah doing with all those toothpicks in her cake?
达夫:卡尼亚把那些牙签插在蛋糕里干什么?
Oh, wow.
哦,哇。
Kaniyah's using toothpicks
Kaniyah在用牙签
as a guide so she can carve it.
作为向导，这样她就可以雕刻了。
That's very smart. Yeah.
这很聪明。是的。
She's making it look like an octagon or something.
她把它弄得像个八角形什么的。
Good girl!
好女孩!
[ Gasps ] Yay!
(喘息)耶!
This lemon blueberry rosemary cake
柠檬蓝莓迷迭香蛋糕
is going to be Catastrophe Girl's
会是灾难女孩的吗
cool superhero shield.
酷酷的超级英雄盾牌。
I did it.
我做到了。
So good.
很好。
I want my cake to be tall,
我想要我的蛋糕很高，
so this cake is going to be four layers,
这个蛋糕有四层，
and it looks really cool.
看起来真的很酷。
It looks just like a shield.
它看起来就像一个盾牌。
Kaniyah! Hello.
Kaniyah !你好。
Have you ever made a $25,000 cake before?
你以前做过价值两万五千美元的蛋糕吗?
No! I have made a $26 cake.
不!我做了一个26美元的蛋糕。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Just a couple more zeros behind that, that's all.
后面再多几个零，仅此而已。
Have fun. Okay!
玩得开心。好吧!
I just need to figure out the design for my superhero.
我只需要想出我的超级英雄的设计。
I want Catastrophe Girl to have a cape,
我希望灾难女孩有斗篷，
her hands on her hips, and a ponytail.
她双手叉腰，扎着马尾。
I'm piping the design
我在做这个设计
and it's not coming out exactly how I wanted.
结果并不是我想要的那样
This is so hard, trying to draw a superhero.
画一个超级英雄太难了。
I have my design and I need to put it
我有我的设计，我需要把它
in the blast chiller before I put it on the cake.
在我把它放在蛋糕上之前，把它放进冷冻机里。
VALERIE: Two and a half hours, bakers!
瓦莱丽:两个半小时，面包师们!
Superhero cake.
超级英雄蛋糕。
JUSTICE: For my frosting, I'm using a normal vanilla buttercream,
贾斯蒂斯:我用的是普通的香草奶油，
because even if it would work well with other flavors,
因为即使它和其他口味搭配得很好，
I feel like just solid rose will taste really good.
我觉得纯玫瑰的味道会很不错。
I get all my crumb coats done
我把所有的面包屑外套都做好了
and I need to start working on my fondant.
我得开始做我的糖了
Ooh, it's hard. I've worked with fondant before.
哦，太难了。我以前用过软糖。
It's kind of hard to work with because it can rip,
它很难处理，因为它会撕裂，
and you do not want it to rip.
你不想让它裂开。
It'll be hard to put it on the cake.
很难把它放在蛋糕上。
Oh! My fondant rips.
哦!我的糖破了。
That's super annoying.
这太烦人了。
It's a little frustrating.
这有点令人沮丧。
I'm trying to patch together my fondant,
我正试着把我的糖粘在一起，
but it's looking horrible and messy
但它看起来很糟糕，很乱
and I'm really sad, but then I think,
我真的很难过，但我又想，
"Yes! I can make clouds and cover this up!"
“是啊!我可以造云，把它遮住!”
So I get white fondant and cut it into cloud shapes
所以我拿了白色的方糖，把它切成云的形状
and I put that over my cake.
我把它涂在蛋糕上
If you could have any superpower, what would it be?
如果你能拥有超能力，你会是什么?
Hmm.
嗯。
I think invisibility would be good.
我觉得隐身会很好。
If you could be invisible, you could, like,
如果你能隐身，你就能，
hide in the bank, wait till they close,
躲在银行里，等银行关门，
get the money, wait till they open, walk out.
拿到钱，等他们开门，然后走出去。
You're doing terrible things with your invisibility!
你隐身做了很可怕的事!
Okay, now let's just -- I'm just going to lay it out.
好了，现在，我要把它摆出来。
If I had superpowers, I would be a villain.
如果我有超能力，我会是个恶棍。
Just... You'd be a...
只是…你会是…
I'd be a villain. You are --
我会成为一个恶棍。你是——
you would be the cutest villain in the world!
你会是世界上最可爱的恶棍!
90 minutes left, bakers!
还有90分钟，面包师们!
Who will be the Kids Baking Champion?
谁将成为儿童烘焙冠军?
What type of superheroes are you guys doing?
你们演的是什么类型的超级英雄?
A weather one.
天气预报的。
Catastrophe Girl.
灾难的女孩。
What are you making, Aidan?
你在做什么艾登
I don't know yet.
我还不知道。
Oh.
哦。
Aidan doesn't know what his superhero is yet?
艾登还不知道他的超级英雄是谁吗?
What? That's crazy.
怎么啦？这太疯狂了。
I still don't know what my superhero's going to be.
我还是不知道我的超级英雄会是谁。
Attention, bakers!
注意,面包师!
Didn't think you'd get away without a twist, did you?
你没想过不来个大转折就能脱身，是吧?
No, please don't be bad.
不，请不要做坏人。
You must create an original archenemy
你必须创造一个真正的敌人
supervillain for your superhero.
超级反派换超级英雄。
[ Gasps ] Oh, my gosh.
(喘息)哦，我的天哪。
Every superhero needs a villain.
每个超级英雄都需要一个反派。
I don't even know what my superhero's going to be.
我都不知道我的超级英雄会是谁。
Okay.
好吧。
I am having a very bad day.
我今天过得很糟糕。
DUFF: You have one hour left.
达夫:你还有一个小时。
AIDAN: Okay. What can I do?
艾丹:好的。我能做什么?
DUFF: Superhero cake, an archenemy villain,
达夫:超级英雄蛋糕，一个大反派，
and $25,000.
和25000美元。
[ Exhales ]
[呼气]
My cakes are done, the frosting is done,
蛋糕做好了，糖霜也做好了，
but I don't know what I'm going to decorate my cake
但是我不知道要怎么装饰我的蛋糕
to look like or my superhero.
看起来像我的超级英雄。
Hmm.
嗯。
Okay.
好吧。
Uh, what's a really good superpower?
什么是真正好的超能力?
No, that won't work.
不，那不行。
This is the first time where I haven't really had
这是我第一次没有
a solid foundation idea yet, and I'm really worried,
一个坚实的基础想法，我真的很担心，
because this is where it matters most.
因为这才是最重要的。
I could do -- okay.
我可以——好的。
Okay, I have an idea.
好吧，我有个主意。
I'm going to do Color Guy versus Gray Guy.
我要讲的是有色人种和灰色人种。
My superhero prism gives light and color and emotion and life,
我的超级英雄棱镜赋予光、色彩、情感和生命，
and my villain is dismal.
我的反面人物是忧郁的。
Going to crush up some cream-filled cookies.
我要去压碎一些奶油曲奇。
He sucks the life and color and emotion
他吸干了生活，色彩和情感
out of everything and one around him.
除了他周围的一切。
He's the perfect villain.
他是个完美的反派。
I get my sandwich cookies in a bag
我把三明治饼干装在袋子里
and then I crush 'em up with the rolling pin.
然后用擀面杖把它们揉碎
You dancing over there, Aidan?
你在那边跳舞吗，艾登?
Yeah.
是的。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
This is kind of a great way
这是一种很好的方式
to relieve stress if you have any.
缓解压力，如果你有压力的话。
You go bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
砰砰，砰砰，砰砰，砰砰，砰砰!
Once my cookies are crushed, I mix them up
饼干压碎后，我就把它们混合起来
with some buttercream so they will hold together
再加些奶油，让它们粘在一起
and I can mold my villain.
我可以塑造我的反派
Perfect, my cream-filled cookie body.
完美，我充满奶油的身体。
I'm going to drape over
我要披上斗篷
a big black piece of fondant for his robe.
一块黑色的大块糖做他的长袍。
The villain.
的反派角色。
His hood is draping over his face
他的兜帽遮住了脸
and he's menacing and dark and mysterious.
他凶狠，阴暗，神秘。
Oh, yeah. Look at this villain.
哦,是的。看看这个恶棍。
He is one bad villain.
他是一个坏蛋。
VALERIE: 45 minutes! Superhero cakes!
瓦莱丽:45分钟!超级英雄蛋糕!
And their villain.
还有他们的反派。
KANIYAH: You want an evil supervillain,
你想要一个邪恶的超级反派，
you'll get it.
你会明白的。
I'm going to take my cream-filled
我要吃奶油馅的
chocolate cookies and butter and slap it in a mold
巧克力饼干和黄油，然后把它拍进模具里
and put it in the blast chiller
然后把它放进冷冻机
until they become really hard and frozen.
直到它们变得非常坚硬和冻结。
My supervillain is Mr. Rotten Potato.
我心目中的大反派是烂土豆先生。
He used to be good.
他以前很好。
Now he's bad because the person left it in the refrigerator
现在他坏了，因为那个人把它留在冰箱里了
and the potato turned evil.
土豆变成了恶魔。
It's the potato.
是土豆。
Kaniyah. Hmm?
Kaniyah。嗯?
Who's Catastrophe Girl's archenemy?
谁是灾难女孩的大敌?
Her villain is Potato Man, out of cream-filled cookies.
她的反派是用奶油曲奇做的土豆人。
Aidan and Kaniyah are both making
艾丹和卡尼亚都在做
the same-flavored cake, basically,
基本上，相同口味的蛋糕，
and they're both making their bad guys
他们都在塑造自己的坏人
out of cream-filled cookies.
没有奶油曲奇了。
I think this gives me a great opportunity to win.
我认为这给了我一个很好的获胜机会。
This is a cool twist, because I know exactly
这是一个很酷的转折，因为我很清楚
what I'll do for my archenemy of Weather Man.
我要为我的天气预报员大敌做些什么。
In my pot on the stove, I start to melt some butter,
在炉子上的锅里，我开始融化黄油，
and once that's melted, I put in the marshmallows,
融化后，放入棉花糖，
I add my cereal in,
我把麦片放进去，
and I stir that until it's all nice and good,
然后搅拌，直到搅拌均匀，
and then I just form a big ball of cereal treats
然后把麦片做成一个大球
and I cover that in my yellow fondant
然后在上面涂上黄色软糖
and then I cut some red fondant up
然后我切了一些红色的方糖
and I make more flames, like, dripping down him.
然后我制造更多的火焰，就像往他身上滴一样。
I get an edible marker
我得到了一个可食用的马克笔
and I draw his creepy eyes in and his teeth
我画了他那吓人的眼睛和牙齿
and he looks like a perfect super villain.
他看起来像一个完美的超级反派。
Mr. Sunshine hates weather.
阳光先生讨厌天气。
He just wants to be sunny all year round.
他只想一年四季都阳光明媚。
He's like, "Hi.
他说，“嗨。
I will make it sunny for eternity."
我会让它永远阳光明媚。”
Hey, did you guys ever think you would be
你们有没有想过你们会
in the finale of "Kids Baking Championship"?
在"儿童烘焙冠军赛"的决赛中?
AIDAN: I don't know, but it's pretty amazing!
艾丹:我不知道，但是真的很神奇!
DUFF: Who's it going to be?
达夫:会是谁呢?
30 minutes! Superhero cakes!
30分钟!超级英雄蛋糕!
KANIYAH: My city is not working out.
卡尼亚:我的城市不太好。
I want Catastrophe Girl in a non-catastrophe city.
我要灾难女孩去一个没有灾难的城市。
It's super duper hard trying to make a city
建造一座城市是非常困难的
on the side of a cake.
在蛋糕的侧面。
My city looks really sloppy, like the potato sat on it.
我的城市看起来很邋遢，就像被土豆压在上面一样。
No! Ugh.
不!啊。
I guess this rotten potato got to the whole city.
我猜这个烂土豆已经蔓延到整个城市了。
I'm decorating the top of the cake with a C versus P,
我用C和P来装饰蛋糕的顶部，
which is Catastrophe Girl versus Rotten Potato.
也就是灾难女孩对烂土豆。
And now, time to get out Catastrophe Girl.
现在，是时候让灾难女孩出场了。
No.
不。
My superhero broke apart.
我的超级英雄崩溃了。
So I put it on the cake without legs,
所以我把它放在没有腿的蛋糕上，
to make it look like she's flying.
让她看起来像是在飞。
AIDAN: $25,000 cake over here.
艾丹:两万五千美元的蛋糕在这里。
I'm going to roll my fondant out until it's nice and thin
我要把软糖擀开，直到它变薄
and I can drape it over my cake.
我可以把它挂在蛋糕上。
That's good.
这很好。
I place my first fondant over
我把我的第一颗方糖放上去
and everything's looking great.
一切看起来都很好。
Perfect. What?
完美的。怎么啦？
How did I just do that so greatly?
我怎么做得这么好?
This might be one of the best fondant jobs I've ever done.
这可能是我做过的最棒的翻糖手术之一。
Well, I have a lot of different colors.
我有很多不同的颜色。
I grab a big case of rock candy in every different color
我拿了一大箱不同颜色的冰糖
and I crush up each one and stick it into the fondant on top
我把每一个都压碎，然后把它粘在上面的软糖里
and in the middle of my cake.
在我的蛋糕中间。
How are you guys doing?
你们过得怎么样?
KANIYAH: Good! How are you doing?
KANIYAH:好!你好吗?
Better than earlier.
比以前好。
I was so stressed at the beginning,
一开始我压力很大，
but right now, I'm feeling really relaxed
但现在，我感觉很放松
and cool and calm.
而且冷静冷静。
All right, isomalt.
好的，异麦芽糖。
I'm going to get some isomalt on the mold to make my prism.
我要在模具上加点异麦芽糖来做我的棱镜。
Isomalt is a special type of sugar that
异麦芽糖是一种特殊的糖
when you melt it down, it resists humidity.
当你把它熔化时，它能抵抗湿气。
All right, it's at the temperature I need it.
好了，温度正合我意。
I get my isomalt melted on the stove
我把异麦芽糖在炉子上融化了
and I pour it in and I'm just going to let it cool down.
倒进去，让它冷却。
Wow! After a while,
哇!过了一会儿，
I take my isomalt out of the blast chiller
我把异麦芽糖从冷冻机里拿出来
and it looks good and it's hard to the touch.
看起来很好，摸起来很硬。
I have so many prisms to choose from.
我有很多棱镜可以选择。
I think it'll be perfect for a prism
我觉得做棱镜再合适不过了
because it looks just like glass.
因为它看起来就像玻璃。
There's the prism.
这是棱镜。
Prism shoots out every color of light and emotion
棱镜射出每一种颜色的光和情感
and life back into everything that's gray and lifeless.
让生命回归到灰色和死气沉沉的一切。
I'm painting almost dead branches,
我在画几乎枯死的树枝，
like corruption,
像腐败,
on the bottom gray part of the cake,
在蛋糕底部的灰色部分，
and I'm painting, like,
我在画画，就像
green ends to them, like the light is healing them.
绿色终结于他们，就像光在治愈他们。
VALERIE: 10 minutes left, bakers!
瓦莱丽:还剩10分钟，面包师们!
DUFF: Villains, superheroes,
达夫:反派，超级英雄，
cake is delicious!
蛋糕很好吃!
I still haven't made Mr. Weather Man.
我还没成为天气预报员呢。
I roll out some long,
我擀出一些长，
log-shaped sticks for his legs.
他的腿是木头形状的棍子。
I make his cape,
我给他做斗篷，
make it look like it's flying in the wind,
让它看起来像是在风中飞翔，
and I make his eyes, his mouth, and his hair.
我做他的眼睛、嘴巴和头发。
It looks like he's a superhero weather man.
他看起来像是超级英雄气象员。
And I'm going to make a letter W for "weather" on top of my cake
我要在蛋糕上画一个字母W代表“天气”
so it's like * Mr. Weather Man *
所以就像天气预报员一样
VALERIE: Two minutes, bakers, two minutes!
瓦莱丽:两分钟，面包师们，两分钟!
Give it everything you've got.
尽你所能去做。
Ooh. Upside down, upside down, upside down.
哦。倒过来，倒过来，倒过来。
I look at my W.
我看W。
I put it on backwards.
我把它戴反了。
It's an M.
是M。
So I pick it up and I turn it over,
所以我把它捡起来翻过来，
but now I have all this red, watery,
但现在我有了这些红色的，水汪汪的，
icky stuff all over my cake.
我的蛋糕上全是恶心的东西。
If I can't fix this,
如果我解决不了
I'll just go with Meteorology Man.
我就选气象人吧。
VALERIE: Ooh!
瓦莱丽:哦!
DUFF: 30 seconds! 30 seconds!
达夫:30秒!30秒!
Then it's all over.
然后一切都结束了。
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick!
快，快，快，快，快!
Make your cakes beautiful. This is not beautiful.
把你的蛋糕做得漂亮。这一点都不美。
If I was a artist, this cake would've been amazing,
如果我是个艺术家，这个蛋糕肯定很棒，
but I'm not.
但我不是。
I'm thinking outside the box,
我在跳出框框思考，
so I'm going to put candy on this to add some decoration.
所以我要在上面放些糖果来装饰一下。
VALERIE AND DUFF: Ten, nine, eight,
瓦莱丽和达夫:十，九，八，
seven, six, five, four,
七，六，五，四，
three, two, one!
三，二，一!
Hands up! AIDAN: Oh, my gosh.
举起手来!艾丹:哦，我的天哪。
I really hope they love the look of my cake
我真的希望他们喜欢我蛋糕的样子
and I hope that it tastes perfect.
我希望它尝起来很完美。
KANIYAH: My cake is not how I wanted it to look.
我的蛋糕不是我想要的样子。
I am so close to $25,000.
我离25000美元很近了。
I hope this cake tastes amazing.
我希望这个蛋糕好吃。
ANNOUNCER: Ordinary marshmallow cereal bars
播音员:普通的棉花糖麦片棒
suit up into superhero desserts right after this.
之后穿上超级英雄的甜点服。
ANNOUNCER: Gather together cereal treats, a star-shaped cookie cutter,
收集麦片点心，一个星形饼干切割机，
frosting and spreader,
结霜和撒胶机;
popping rock candy, and colored icing.
跳跳冰糖和彩色糖衣。
Cut out your stars.
剪掉你的星星。
Cover with frosting.
用糖霜覆盖。
Sprinkle on some popping candy.
撒上一些跳跳糖。
Decorate with your favorite superhero symbols.
用你最喜欢的超级英雄符号装饰。
Ka-pow!
Ka-pow !
For more treats like this,
想要更多这样的美食，
visit foodnetwork.com /kidsbaking.
访问foodnetwork.com /kidsbaking。
All right. These kids baked up a storm.
好吧。这些孩子大闹了一场。
But, proof is on the plate.
但是，证据就在盘子上。
Yep. Hey, Justice.
是的。嘿,正义。
This is the last time I'll ever walk into
这是我最后一次走进
this kitchen for judging, and it's going to be
这是评判的厨房，它将会是
the last time Duff and Valerie
达夫和瓦莱丽最后一次见面
will ever taste something I've made.
都不会尝我做的东西
This is really sad
这真的很可悲
but I'm also excited to see how it goes.
但我也很期待它的发展。
I think they'll really like my cake.
我想他们会很喜欢我的蛋糕。
All right, so, Justice,
好了，正义先生，
introduce your superhero and your villain.
介绍一下你的超级英雄和反派。
Mr. Weather Man.
天气预报员先生。
He is the ruler of all the weather on planet Earth.
他是地球上所有天气的统治者。
He can make it a beautiful day
他能让这一天变得美好
or he can make it stormy for a month straight.
或者他可以让暴风雨持续一个月。
But his evil enemy is Mr. Sunshine.
但他邪恶的敌人是阳光先生。
A lot of people want Mr. Sunshine,
很多人想要阳光先生，
but after a while, you would want Mr. Weather Man,
但过不了多久，你就会想要天气预报员
because Mr. Sunshine will make scorching heat
因为阳光先生会带来灼热
and sunburn all year round.
常年晒伤。
I like it. Yeah, me too.
我喜欢它。是啊，我也是。
Tell us all about your cake.
我喜欢它。跟我们说说你的蛋糕吧。
I made a rose extract cake with a buttercream frosting,
我做了一个玫瑰精华蛋糕，上面有奶油糖霜，
and my villain is made out of rice treats covered in fondant.
我的反派是用裹着软糖的米做的。
I love your cake. I love that you can
我喜欢你的蛋糕。我很高兴你能
totally see that he's in the sky.
完全看到他在天上。
I like the way his cape is off to the side
我喜欢他披风歪向一边的样子
so it looks like he's got some wind flowing under his cape.
所以看起来他的斗篷下有风在流动。
I think your cake looks really good.
我觉得你的蛋糕看起来很不错。
You know, it's three tiers.
你知道，它有三层。
You know, looks like your cake is pretty straight,
看起来你的蛋糕挺直的，
um, which is, you know, rare.
你知道，这很少见。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Yeah. There's a couple of dings.
是的。有几处凹痕。
You know, you can see, like, the fondant tore a little bit.
你可以看到，软糖有点裂开了。
You know, you got all these nice clouds on top.
你知道，你的头顶上有很多漂亮的云。
I think you could've gone clouds the whole way down
我觉得你可以一路飞下去
and covered up a lot of those things.
并且掩盖了很多事情。
Yeah. Let's taste that.
是的。我们来尝尝。
Now, why'd you go with, uh, rose extract?
你为什么要用玫瑰提取物?
I thought it was a really nice and elegant flavor.
我认为这是一种非常好的优雅的味道。
Definitely taste the rose.
一定要尝尝玫瑰的味道。
You can smell it first. Super moist.
你可以先闻一下。超级滋润。
And it's not too much.
而且不会太多。
No, it really is quite elegant.
不，它真的很优雅。
But I can tell you, I think you could've
但我可以告诉你，我觉得你可以
taken a chance and put some other flavors in there
冒险放了些别的口味进去
that would've gone with the rose.
那应该配玫瑰的。
You know, pistachios.
你知道，开心果。
Honey goes really well with the rose.
蜂蜜和玫瑰很配。
There's a lot that you could do with that.
你可以用它做很多事情。
Yeah.
是的。
I thought that if I added other flavors,
我想如果我加入其他口味，
it might overpower the rose, and come on, guys,
它可能会压倒玫瑰，来吧，伙计们，
you've got to stop and smell the roses!
你得停下来享受一下生活!
Tasty. I really like it.
好吃。我真的很喜欢。
It's really good. I want to try the villain.
真的很好吃。我想试试反派角色。
Cuts through nicely. Yeah.
很好地切入。是的。
Tired of this LA weather, Mr. Sunshine.
受够了洛杉矶的天气，阳光先生。
Duff put an end to the reign of the sun.
达夫结束了太阳的统治。
Oh, they're nice and gooey.
哦，它们又好又黏。
Thank you for putting butter in there, man.
谢谢你放黄油进去，伙计。
Mm! That's so good!
毫米!太好吃了!
Listen, Justice, I judge a lot of baking championships,
听着，法官，我当过很多烘焙锦标赛的评委，
and the execution of this cake here
还有这个蛋糕的制作过程
is on par with any of the adults.
和任何一个成年人都一样。
You did an amazing job.
你做得太棒了。
Way to go, Justice. Thank you.
干得好，正义。谢谢你！
All right.
谢谢你！好吧。
I feel like I did great.
我觉得我做得很好。
The forecast is cloudy with a chance of $25,000.
天气预报多云，有25000美元的赔率。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
Demented, right?
疯狂的,对吗?
Are you ready for Aidan? I certainly am.
准备好见艾登了吗?我当然是。
All right. Hey, Aidan.
好吧。嘿,艾丹。
AIDAN: I can't believe that I'm all the way here
艾丹:我真不敢相信我大老远来到这里
in the final judging.
在最后的评判中。
My superhero cake better be the best cake ever,
我的超级英雄蛋糕最好是史上最棒的，
because everything's on the line here.
因为所有的东西都在这条线上。
Hi.
嗨。嗨。
So tell us about your superhero.
跟我们说说你的超级英雄吧。
My superhero is Prism.
我的超级英雄是棱镜。
He is a being of pure light
他是一个纯光的存在
and shines it through color and emotion and life,
并通过色彩，情感和生命，
and Dismal over here, he does the exact opposite.
而这边的忧郁，他做的正好相反。
He takes away life and energy and color and emotion,
他带走了生命、活力、色彩和情感，
leaving people lifeless kind of beings.
让人成为没有生命的生物。
At the bottom is where dismal death is,
底部是令人沮丧的死亡，
and then over here, you can see it kind of
然后这里，你可以看到它有点
turns green towards the middle,
中间变成绿色，
like the light is healing it, giving it back its color.
就像光在治愈它，让它恢复颜色。
Oh, yeah! I love your story.
哦,耶!我喜欢你的故事。
It's more than just a comic book superhero,
他不仅仅是漫画中的超级英雄，
that there's light and life and love in your cake.
你的蛋糕里有光，有生命，有爱。
And I love the isomalt prism? Really smart.
我喜欢异麦芽糖棱镜?很聪明。
It looks like an actual prism.
它看起来像一个真正的棱镜。
Mm-hmm. Tell us about your cake.
嗯哼。跟我们说说你的蛋糕。
Well, I have a lemon olive oil rosemary cake
我有柠檬橄榄油迷迭香蛋糕
with a buttercream,
加上奶油奶油，
and Dismal over here has a fondant robe
那边的忧郁穿了件糖袍
and he is made of cream-filled cookies mixed with buttercream.
他是由奶油曲奇和奶油混合而成的。
Lemon rosemary olive oil cake.
柠檬迷迭香橄榄油蛋糕。
That sounds amazing.
听起来太棒了。
What made you choose that flavor?
是什么让你选择那种口味的?
My grandma loves lemon just as much as you
我奶奶和你一样喜欢柠檬
and I didn't want to do just plain lemon.
我不想做普通的柠檬
I'd heard of a lemon olive oil rosemary cake,
我听说过柠檬橄榄油迷迭香蛋糕，
so I had a little bit of chopped rosemary
所以我放了一点迷迭香碎
and I replaced the butter with olive oil.
我用橄榄油代替了黄油。
My knees feel like they're about to give out.
我的膝盖好像要不行了。
Just please tell me how it tastes.
请告诉我味道如何。
If it's so bad, please tell me now.
如果有那么糟糕，请现在告诉我。
It's always tough when this happens, isn't it?
每次发生这种事都很难受，不是吗?
I'm speechless.
我无话可说。
[ Exhales ]
[呼气]
I mean, you made such a beautiful cake.
你做的蛋糕真漂亮。
Yeah.
是的。是的。
You know, and then you go and do something silly like...
你知道，然后你就去做一些蠢事，比如……
make a delicious cake to go inside of it.
做一个美味的蛋糕放在里面。
That makes no sense.
这没有道理。
Gosh, don't ever do that again.
天哪，别再那样做了。
[ Laughs ]
[笑]
I was, like, about to have a heart attack.
我都快心脏病发作了。
This is so good!
这太好吃了!
Oh, my gosh! Wow.
哦，天哪!哇。
Ah, goodness! Man.
啊,天哪!男人。
The lemon, the subtle rosemary.
柠檬，淡淡的迷迭香。
I know you were really scared
我知道你当时很害怕
'cause you could smell the rosemary.
因为你能闻到迷迭香。
I was so scared there was going to be too much rosemary.
我很害怕会有太多迷迭香。
No. Mm.
不。毫米。
I'm a little disappointed that you didn't follow through
我对你没有坚持到底有点失望
with your mascarpone, because I think it
和你的马斯卡彭奶酪，因为我觉得
would've been so boss on this.
在这件事上我是老大。
Just wasn't coming together
就是没能走到一起
and I didn't want to risk too much.
我不想冒太大的风险
Look, if you thought that it was bad,
听着，如果你觉得这很糟糕，
you totally made the right decision.
你完全做了正确的决定。
It's still a bummer, because it would've been so cool if...
我还是很失望，因为如果……
It would've just pumped it up that much more.
它会把它泵得更大。
Right. Yeah. Yeah. In -- And I love your villain, man.
正确的。是的。是的。我喜欢你演的反派，伙计。
I love Dismal.
我喜欢忧郁。
He's got a lot of personality, you know what I mean?
他很有个性，你懂我的意思吗?
And he really kind of feels Dismal.
他真的觉得很沮丧。
Um, I would say you probably could've gotten away
我想说你本来可以逃开的
with about half that much buttercream.
加一半的奶油。
Okay. Thank you, Aidan.
好吧。谢谢你，艾登。
Bye. Thank you.
再见。谢谢你！
I hope that Prism can really shine a light through
我希望"棱镜"真的能照亮一切
and help me win.
帮我赢。
I guess it's in fate's hands.
我想这是命运的安排。
God, I do wish that there was that mascarpone on there.
天啊，我真希望那上面有马斯卡彭奶酪。
I know! It's just buttercream.
我知道!这只是奶油。
It just needed a frosting to make it stand out.
只需要一层糖霜来突出它。
Yeah.
是的。
You know why this is my favorite challenge of all?
知道为什么这是我最喜欢的挑战吗?
Why is that? Because it's cake!
为什么呢?因为这是蛋糕!
And I am the Cake Crusader.
我是蛋糕斗士。
I'm just incognito right now.
我现在只是隐姓埋名。
You like jump into the pantry.
你喜欢跳进食品储藏室。
[ Whirring ]
[呼呼声]
Come back out.
出来吧。
You want to call in Kaniyah? I think we should.
你想叫卡尼亚来吗?我想我们应该。
Hey, Kaniyah!
嘿,Kaniyah !
This should be interesting.
这应该很有趣。
I am so close to $25,000.
我离25000美元很近了。
My cake is not how I wanted it to look,
我的蛋糕不是我想要的样子，
but I hope it tastes amazing.
但我希望它尝起来很棒。
Hello. Hey.
你好。嘿。
Kaniyah, so, the last 10 weeks, did you have fun?
卡尼亚，过去的十周，你过得开心吗?
Yes, I had some up and downs. You won a few weeks.
是的，我有过一些起起落落。你赢了几个星期。
You came close to losing a few weeks.
你差点就浪费了几周时间。
You have had some ups and downs.
你经历了一些起起落落。
But it was fun.
但这很有趣。
Tell us about everything.
告诉我们一切。
My cake is a lemon blueberry infused rosemary cake,
我的蛋糕是柠檬蓝莓迷迭香蛋糕，
and the buttercream is a lemon and then
奶油是柠檬，然后
just the regular buttercream.
就是普通的奶油。
My superhero is Catastrophe Girl,
我的超级英雄是灾难女孩，
flying across there to go catch the bad potato.
飞到那边去抓坏土豆。
Oh, I see.
哦，我明白了。
My imagination was reeling about mashed potatoes,
我的脑子里满是土豆泥，
and I was like, "Hmm, how 'bout an evil potato?"
我说，“嗯，来个邪恶的土豆怎么样?”
He used to be a good ol' potato,
他曾经是一个很好的老土豆，
till somebody left him in the refrigerator.
直到有人把他丢在冰箱里。
He turned bad.
他变坏了。
Um, that's what happens when you
当你
leave a potato in the 'fridge.
在冰箱里放一个土豆。
He turned brown and black and destroyed the world.
他变成了棕色和黑色，毁灭了世界。
You know, you know what I love about your cake?
你知道我喜欢你的蛋糕哪一点吗?
It is colorful. I think it's really fun,
它是五颜六色的。我觉得这很有趣，
but I think that you probably had a plan
但我觉得你可能已经有计划了
and I think that the plan didn't work out.
我觉得这个计划行不通
No. And I think you just went to town.
不。我觉得你只是进城了。
And that's okay. You know what I like about it?
这没关系。你知道我喜欢什么吗?
I like the fact that it's shaped like a superhero shield.
我喜欢它的形状像超级英雄的盾牌。
It's good thinking. Let's taste it, Kaniyah.
这想法不错。让我们尝尝，Kaniyah。
I'm excited.
我感到很兴奋。
Thank you, Kaniyah.
谢谢你，Kaniyah。
Look at that beautiful blueberry in there.
看看那漂亮的蓝莓。
That's pretty. It looks like a muffin.
这是漂亮。看起来像松饼。
It does taste like a blueberry muffin, doesn't it?
尝起来确实像蓝莓松饼，不是吗?
Yeah. It's very dense cake.
是的。这是非常致密的蛋糕。
Ugh.
啊。
A tiny bit on the dry side.
稍微干一点。
I love blueberries and lemon together.
我喜欢蓝莓和柠檬一起吃。
It's one of my favorites.
这是我的最爱之一。
I think you just left it in the mixer a tiny bit too long,
我觉得你在搅拌机里放的时间太长了，
so it's a little chewy,
有点嚼劲，
but the taste is great.
但是味道很好。
It's a delicious cake.
蛋糕很好吃。
And what's your superhero --
你的超级英雄是什么
villain, Bad Potato, made out of?
反派，坏土豆，用什么做的?
Cream-filled cookies.
奶油饼干。
How did you get 'em together?
你怎么把他们凑到一起的?
Butter. Buttercream. Okay.
黄油。奶油乳酪。好吧。
Um, not buttercream, just plain old butter.
不是奶油，就是普通的黄油。
Just plain butter?
只是普通黄油吗?
Let's taste that villain.
让我们尝尝那个恶棍的味道。
All right.
好吧。
That's a buttery cookie!
那是一块黄油饼干!
It actually tastes really good with the butter.
加了黄油味道真的很好。
It would've been probably oversweet with the buttercream.
奶油可能太甜了。
Mm. Smart move.
聪明的举动。
I want some more of that.
我还想再来点。
Super creative. Thank you. Good job, Kaniyah.
超级创意。谢谢你！干得好，Kaniyah。
Thanks, Kaniyah.
谢谢你！谢谢,Kaniyah。
Mm.
毫米。
Judging's over and I'm not that confident right now,
评判结束了，我现在也没那么自信，
but I still think I have a chance to win.
但我仍然认为我有机会赢。
Maybe.
也许吧。
Cookies and butter? Why not?
饼干和黄油?为什么不呢?
Now, I know. I mean, come on.
现在，我知道了。我是说，拜托。
A new treat.
一种新的款待。
Uh-oh.
哦。
All right. Valerie, we are going to need
好吧。瓦莱丽，我们需要
all our superpowers to decide this one.
我们所有的超能力来决定这个问题。
Justice. Wow.
正义。哇。
You know, I love the Weather Man character that he created.
我喜欢他创造的天气预报员这个角色。
His cape was being blown by the wind.
他的斗篷被风吹着。
It really works.
真的有效果！
It's really clever. Fun story. Yeah.
这真的很聪明。有趣的故事。是的。
It is. His tiers were round.
它是。他的腿是圆的。
They were centered. They were flat.
它们在中间。它们是平的。
To execute a cake that clean is really impressive.
能做出这么干净的蛋糕真是令人印象深刻。
Very impressive. I loved Justice's cake.
非常令人印象深刻。我喜欢正义的蛋糕。
It was so elegant and so subtle but yet moist.
它是如此优雅，如此微妙，但又湿润。
It was a delicious cake, but I've got to tell you,
蛋糕很好吃，但我得告诉你，
I really think it could've used a little something.
我真的觉得它应该加点东西。
I really taste the rose.
我真的尝到了玫瑰的味道。
Even just some honey in the buttercream.
甚至在奶油里加点蜂蜜。
Mm, mm. Or just, you know, a little bit of lemon,
嗯，嗯，或者，你知道，加点柠檬，
a little bit of orange would've gone well with that rose.
一点橘色会和玫瑰很搭。
Let's talk about Kaniyah.
让我们来谈谈Kaniyah。
I really like the flavor of her cake
我很喜欢她做的蛋糕的味道
and the flavor of her buttercream.
还有奶油的味道。
I just think the cake itself is a little tough.
我只是觉得蛋糕本身有点硬。
KANIYAH: Oh!
KANIYAH:哦!
We had Catastrophe Girl and Rotten Potato.
我们有灾难女孩和烂土豆。
I think her story was a little weak.
我觉得她的故事有点弱。
Yeah. But really, that cake is colorful
是的。但说真的，那个蛋糕是彩色的
and feisty and fun,
活泼有趣，
just like Kaniyah is.
就像卡尼亚一样。
All right, let's talk about Aidan.
好吧，我们来谈谈艾登。
You know, I don't know if this is going to work.
你知道，我不知道这能不能成功。
Had he not told me that he was going to
他不是告诉过我他要去吗
make mascarpone frosting, I wouldn't have missed it,
做马斯卡彭奶酪糖霜，我不会错过的，
but it's just killing me that he didn't do it!
但这不是他干的，这让我很难过!
We've had a lot of buttercream.
我们吃了很多奶油。
Making a buttercream isn't really making it unique.
制作奶油并不是让它与众不同。
No. And I think he had
不。我认为他确实做到了
way too much buttercream in his cookies.
他的饼干里奶油太多了。
Yes. It just kind of overpowered the cookies.
是的。它的味道盖过了饼干。
You really couldn't taste 'em.
你真的尝不出。
But I love that there was a prism on top of his cake,
但我喜欢他蛋糕顶上的棱镜，
sending out color. It was beautiful!
发出颜色。它是美丽的!
And Aidan's lemon rosemary olive oil cake.
还有艾登的柠檬迷迭香橄榄油蛋糕。
It was delightful.
这是令人愉快的。
Pretty sophisticated for a 12-year-old.
对一个12岁的孩子来说相当老练。
Yeah.
是的。
But also sophisticated, a rose cake
但也精致，一个玫瑰蛋糕
that I ate the entire slice and then ate yours, too.
我把整片都吃了然后把你的也吃了
Oh, it's so close.
哦，太近了。
This is the closest it's ever, ever been.
这是有史以来最接近的一次。
This is -- yeah.
这是——是的。
It's never not a tight race.
这是一场势均力敌的比赛。
This is the tightest it's ever been.
这是有史以来最紧张的一次。
Bakers, you have competed
面包师们，你们参加了比赛
against the largest number of bakers
与数量最多的面包师竞争
in this baking championship's history,
在烘焙大赛的历史上
and it's all come down to three of you.
这一切都取决于你们三个人。
Of course, the only question remaining is,
当然，剩下的唯一问题是，
which one of you deserves
你们哪一个值得
to become Kids Baking Champion?
成为儿童烘焙冠军?
We asked you to create a one-of-a-kind,
我们让你创造一个独一无二的，
original superhero cake, and you all showed
原创超级英雄蛋糕，你们都来了
tremendous skill and creativity
高超的技巧和创造力
in carrying out this super task.
在执行这项超级任务时。
Kaniyah. Hmm?
Kaniyah。嗯?
Your lemon blueberry superhero cake was bright,
你的柠檬蓝莓超级英雄蛋糕很亮，
fun, and festive, just like you.
有趣，喜庆，就像你一样。
Your Rotten Potato villain,
你的烂土豆坏蛋，
made from crushed-up cookies with butter,
由压碎的饼干和黄油制成，
was very creative and darn tasty.
很有创意，也很好吃。
And your story of Catastrophe Girl
还有你的大灾难女孩的故事
versus Potato Man was pure Kaniyah --
和土豆人的对决是纯粹的Kaniyah
unexpected and entertaining.
出乎意料又有趣。
Aidan, your lemon olive oil rosemary cake,
艾登，你的柠檬橄榄油迷迭香蛋糕，
it took us to another dimension.
它把我们带到了另一个维度。
We loved it.
我们很喜欢。
The sponge was moist, the rosemary was subtle,
海绵是湿润的，迷迭香是淡淡的，
and your decorating was really artful.
你的装饰真有艺术感。
And your story of Prism versus the evil Dismal was powerful
你的棱镜大战邪恶的阴郁的故事很有力量
and it touched us both.
它触动了我们俩。
Justice, your Weather Man superhero cake
正义，你的天气预报员超级英雄蛋糕
proved you have baking powers well beyond your years.
证明了你的烘焙能力远远超出了你的年龄。
Your rose-flavored cake was sophisticated,
你的玫瑰味蛋糕很精致
moist, and delicious.
又湿又好吃。
You balanced the rose perfectly.
你把玫瑰平衡得很好。
Your villain, Mr. Sun, was yummy.
你的反派孙先生很好吃。
Mm-hmm. And your story of Weather Man
嗯哼。还有你的天气预报员的故事
versus Mr. Sun was inventive
对孙先生很有创造力
and it definitely played to one of your passions.
这绝对是你的激情所在。
You all made a heroic effort today,
你们今天都做了英勇的努力，
but only one of you can win the title
但你们中只有一个人能赢得冠军
of Kids Baking Champion and $25,000.
儿童烘焙冠军和两万五千美元
I feel like I'm about to fall on the floor.
我觉得我要摔倒在地板上了。
I so badly do not want to go home empty-handed.
我实在不想空手而归。
The winner of "Kids Baking Championship" is...
“儿童烘焙锦标赛”的冠军是……
Aidan!
艾丹!
JUSTICE: Good job, Aidan!
JUSTICE:干得好，Aidan!
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
I won? I won?
我赢了?我赢了?
Good job!
好工作!
Congratulations, Aidan!
恭喜,艾丹!
KANIYAH: You did it!
你做到了!
VALERIE: Aidan, you're the Kids Baking Champion! Congrat--
瓦莱丽:艾丹，你是儿童烘焙冠军!Congrat——
Thank you. Come here, you!
谢谢你！过来，你!
Come here. Come here, you.
到这里来。过来，你。
AIDAN: I have a whole butterfly migration
艾丹:我有整个蝴蝶迁徙
going through my stomach right now.
我现在就在胃里。
Aidan, good job, man. You guys, oh, my God.
艾登，干得好。你们，我的天啊。
Good job. I'm so proud of all that I've accomplished here.
好工作。我为我在这里取得的成就感到骄傲。
Kaniyah, I'm coming!
Kaniyah，我来了!
And it's been an amazing ride
这是一段奇妙的旅程
and I can't believe I won.
我不敢相信我赢了
It literally feels like I'm dreaming.
感觉就像我在做梦。
This was the tightest it's ever been.
这是有史以来最紧张的一次。
We argued for a long time.
我们争论了很长时间。
All three of you are amazing bakers.
你们三个都是很棒的面包师。
Yeah. "Kids Baking Championship"!
是的。“儿童烘焙锦标赛”!
Woo-hoo! Yay!
啊!耶!